<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boston on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/boston/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Boston on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 11:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/boston/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Ending</title>
      <link>/posts/perfect-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/perfect-ending/</guid>
      <description>The last true day of our vacation (the day before we headed home) was in my opinion the most relaxing day of the week.
We slept in, ate breakfast, (the kids did the dishes), and then we headed out for a morning hike along the beach.
 
The tide was out and we discovered many living creatures in tide pools on the rocky beach
.


We made our way to the other side of the island and even caught a glimpse of the Boston skyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh This Boy!</title>
      <link>/posts/oh-this-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 04:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/oh-this-boy/</guid>
      <description>It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t shock me, but yet it does. How completely DIFFERENT each of my children are. Their personalities are so unique, it truly amazes me.
Take my youngest.
Oh my goodness&amp;hellip; he is such a goof ball, and a FLIRT, but I&amp;rsquo;ll save that for another post&amp;hellip;
Here the kids are in Boston.
&amp;ldquo;Kids, get together so mom can get a picture of the four of you by the fountains.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peddocks Island Day 1</title>
      <link>/posts/peddocks-island-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 03:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/peddocks-island-day-1/</guid>
      <description>After our rain delay/rain out, we finally made it to Peddocks Island… one day late. After hiking the LONG hike uphill to our site, I am so glad we didn’t attempt it during the torrential rainstorm.
It was a big enough hassle getting our stuff from the van to the ferry, off the ferry, on to the other ferry, off that ferry, and then up the long hike up hill to our site… but the weather was gorgeous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birthday in Boston</title>
      <link>/posts/birthday-in-boston/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/birthday-in-boston/</guid>
      <description>The plan for today was to wake up and prepare to catch a ferry to Boston Harbor Island to begin the camping portion of our vacation.
However, we woke to this.

And after checking the weather saw that the day was going to be off and on rain showers for the remainder. This seemed like less than an ideal setting to haul all our camping gear onto a ferry, off a ferry, onto another ferry, to our campsite AND THEN set up a tent… a tent with a screen roof none the less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom Trail</title>
      <link>/posts/freedom-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/freedom-trail/</guid>
      <description>We chose Boston for a family vacation destination this summer because of our study this past year on the American Revolution. However, I had no illusions of dragging four kids through the entire 2 and 1/2 mile freedom trail on a hot and humid summer day. We are actually going to spend the bulk of our week camping on an island in Boston Harbor, but I did want to show the kids a few highlights of history, especially my oldest as he is the history buff of the crew.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
