<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>siblings on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/siblings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in siblings on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 12:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/siblings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deja Vu</title>
      <link>/posts/deja-vu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/deja-vu/</guid>
      <description>My kids have gotten the Minecraft bug. Started first with my oldest son. He shared the obsession with my 6 year old daughter… and then even my child who doesn’t really like to play games, joined in the fight against zombies. Yesterday they finally figured out how to do multi player, which means they can all play at the same time on various different wireless devices in the same world. Giggles could be heard as they found each other walking around in their worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precious Moment</title>
      <link>/posts/precious-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/precious-moment/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Muffins and Memories for Breakfast</title>
      <link>/posts/making-muffins-and-memories-for-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/making-muffins-and-memories-for-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>Not sure which I like best about this snapshot, the smiles on the girls faces, my daughters hand in the peanut butter jar or my son sneaking yet another lick out of the bowl….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life is Good</title>
      <link>/posts/life-is-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/life-is-good/</guid>
      <description>Years ago Aunt Karen gave our oldest child a Life is Good soccer shirt. Because the color and theme were gender neutral, I ended up passing it down to my daughter a few years later. It actually became that perfect shirt for younger siblings to wear to soccer games so she could feel like she was a part of the team too. By the time my third child wore it, it was worn with shin guards and sometimes even cleats TO WATCH the older 2 practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monkey See, Monkey Do…</title>
      <link>/posts/monkey-see-monkey-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 08:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/monkey-see-monkey-do/</guid>
      <description>Love this picture I snapped of my youngest trying to do a handstand like his sister!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melt this Momma’s Heart…</title>
      <link>/posts/melt-this-mommas-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/melt-this-mommas-heart/</guid>
      <description>As if the sight of one boy playing the piano, didn’t melt my heart enough…

2 boys just turns me to mush</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The way They Love Him</title>
      <link>/posts/the-way-they-love-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-way-they-love-him/</guid>
      <description>As Scott and I worked to put together the scrapbook and video collage for our son’s 1st birthday, we looked at lots and lots of pictures and video clips. As we did, one reoccurring theme, was brought to mind.
This boy is adored by his siblings.
He really has been from day 1. And by day 1, I mean, the day Scott and I told them about the baby in my belly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Lucky Brother</title>
      <link>/posts/one-lucky-brother/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-lucky-brother/</guid>
      <description>As I watch my kids play together, I can’t help but think how my son has no idea how good he has it. Growing up, it was just me and my little brother and we’d often play together. I vividly recall playing GI Joe with him. It pretty much went the same way every time. I had the Princess Lea action figure and she would be married to either Shipwreck or Sgt Slaughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Will Win??</title>
      <link>/posts/who-will-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/who-will-win/</guid>
      <description>There are many familiar and epic battles out there. At the circus, I am often subject to reading, watching, and even role playing in such battles over good and evil.
Darth Vader and Luke Skywalker fighting for the future of the galaxy.
Spiderman and Doctor Octopus dueling over the city of New York.
Optimus Prime and the autobots verses Megatron and the decepticons in their fierce battle over the fate of earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can’t Get Enough of You Baby</title>
      <link>/posts/cant-get-enough-of-you-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cant-get-enough-of-you-baby/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisters</title>
      <link>/posts/sisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sisters/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite things about parenting, is watching my children interact with each other (when they aren’t fighting that is). It’s fascinating to me to see the differences in their bonds and relationships. One relationship which I have observed recently growing is that between my two girls. 

With only 17 mths, and a few inches and pounds between them, they are in so many ways peers. They share much in common, and yet are so very different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Revealed</title>
      <link>/posts/mystery-revealed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mystery-revealed/</guid>
      <description>What were my kids doing on the quilt in that picture yesterday? Were they tracking an escaped ant from their ant farm? Were they studying the quilt pattern in preparation for making one of their own? Were they praying over their baby brother?
Not quite
Believe it or not, underneath that pile of circus cast members was our youngest child…
 You kinda get a little glimpse of him here…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slumber Parties</title>
      <link>/posts/slumber-parties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/slumber-parties/</guid>
      <description>I think I’ve mentioned before that my oldest three all share a room. This week the kids have started taking turns sleeping with the baby. Sunday night the boys got to sleep together. My oldest was so excited about sharing a room with his little brother. I couldn’t help but snap a picture as I peeked in on them before going to bed. 
When I went to look in on the girls I found them both cuddled up together on the floor… it appears they decided to have a sleep over of their ownThe next night my oldest daughter wanted to sleep with the baby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Was Good While it Lasted</title>
      <link>/posts/it-was-good-while-it-lasted/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/it-was-good-while-it-lasted/</guid>
      <description>Those of you with more than one kiddo know how insanely difficult it is to get a good picture of all your children together….if you don’t know what I am talking about, check out this post or this one, and you will get an idea of what I am referring to. You have aspirations of all three children sitting still, smiling, and looking at the camera. After about 30 clicks of the camera and at least 20 begs and pleas to “look at mommy” and “please sit down” you suddenly set your sights a bit lower and just hope for all of them smiling… who cares where they look and how they sit….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captive Audience</title>
      <link>/posts/captive-audience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 06:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/captive-audience/</guid>
      <description>They say newborns don’t do much other than sleeping, eating, pooping, and crying. While that may be true, I gotta tell you the circus crew has not yet tired of watching their baby brother do these things. It’s been a week since we brought our little man home from the hospital. And every-single-time we have to change his diaper, one can hear a stampede of feet as the three of them race for a spot by the changing table to watch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backyard Warfare</title>
      <link>/posts/backyard-warfare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/backyard-warfare/</guid>
      <description>There is a huge pile of bamboo in our backyard waiting for a run to the dump on Saturday. Until then, it provided the perfect landscape for my son to build a fort and play war. He stayed out there for hours and was so proud of his camouflage. 
Unfortunatly, his gun kinda gives him away.
When I showed this picture to my husband I said it should be called,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old School E-mail</title>
      <link>/posts/old-school-e-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/old-school-e-mail/</guid>
      <description>My oldest two have gotten into the habit of “e-mailing” each other at the beginning of nap time. And by e-mailing they really mean they are drawing pictures and writing messages back and forth to each other. We’ve worked out a system in which they are allowed to e-mail for the first 30 minutes of nap time. Then, they have to have quiet time in separate rooms for the remaining hour and a half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas from the Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/merry-christmas-from-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/merry-christmas-from-the-circus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony Rides</title>
      <link>/posts/pony-rides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 05:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pony-rides/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naptime E-mails</title>
      <link>/posts/naptime-e-mails/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/naptime-e-mails/</guid>
      <description>Naptime is sacred at my house. At night all three kids share a room b/c it really doesn’t bother me if they stay up late talking and singing. But at nap time every one goes to a different room. My son no longer naps, but he still goes to his “nap room” for quiet time where he may look at books or draw or play quietly for an hour and a half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holding Fast</title>
      <link>/posts/holding-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/holding-fast/</guid>
      <description>Every now and then at the circus, I find myself enjoying a moment of peace. All too often that peace and quiet is the result of complete and massive destruction going on quietly in another room of the house… say an overflowing sink, or crayon art on the wall, or something else which seems to bind my children in complete quiet. But sometimes, sometimes all is calm and when I fearfully peek around the corner, I catch a moment like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to the Chapel…</title>
      <link>/posts/going-to-the-chapel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/going-to-the-chapel/</guid>
      <description>I went to a wedding the other night.
The bride looked dashing in her floor length ball gown, with her shoulder length hair worn down. The groom was handsome in his navy blue jacket with a red and gray tie, and a simple black eyed susan taped to his jacket lapel. The bride carried matching black eyes susan’s picked fresh from her mother’s yard.  As the ceremony began the bride’s cell phone rang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partners for Life</title>
      <link>/posts/partners-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/partners-for-life/</guid>
      <description>The relationship between siblings is a funny thing. I once read a Times magazine article about siblings that really struck me. It’s funny, 3 years later and I still remember this one line “Our spouses arrive comparatively late in our lives; our parents eventually leave us. Our siblings may be the only people we&amp;rsquo;ll ever know who truly qualify as partners for life.”
Being the mother of three children, I think a lot about the bonds of siblings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
