<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>farm on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/farm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in farm on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 06:33:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/farm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Fall Tradition</title>
      <link>/posts/a-fall-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 06:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-fall-tradition/</guid>
      <description>Almost every fall, I enjoy taking the kids to the county fair. We’ve been going since my oldest was under a year old. This year my youngest was so super excited. He talked about it for months. “When are we going to go to the fair and see the animals?” We went on Friday morning for the preschool preview day. Then my parents and I returned on Saturday for the girls to perform a gymnastics demo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast with the Piglets</title>
      <link>/posts/breakfast-with-the-piglets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/breakfast-with-the-piglets/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I had a unique opportunity this morning to feed some orphaned baby piglets. The Momma Pig died at childbirth and the farmers were looking for extra hands to give bottles to the piglets. I literally leaped at the opportunity. And I am so glad that I did! What a delightful way to spend our morning!




Even my youngest had fun with the piglets…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Time Traditions</title>
      <link>/posts/spring-time-traditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/spring-time-traditions/</guid>
      <description>For the past 3 years the kids and I have gone to a local strawberry farm to pick our own berries. It is a tradition I cherish. 
We are suburbanites. We don’t even really garden. But, I love for my children to get some real life farm experiences. I love for them to walk down the rows upon rows of plants.

This year my son really went to town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Acres We are There</title>
      <link>/posts/green-acres-we-are-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/green-acres-we-are-there/</guid>
      <description>As the kids and I frolicked around the local farm park with friends the other day, I couldn’t help but smirk at my youngest in her “farm girl” attire.

As she eagerly peeked in on the baby piglets in with her dazzling shades and hot pink purse…

 She wrinkled her nose and said, “Mommy, something is stinky!”
 I couldn’t help but think of Za Za Gabor in Green Acres.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
