<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works For Me Wednesday on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/works-for-me-wednesday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works For Me Wednesday on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 10:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/works-for-me-wednesday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Packing the Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/packing-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/packing-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>After a week of fun, friends, field trips, house work, sleeping in, and even a camp fire, we’re topping off our Spring Break with a long weekend at Grandma and Papa’s.
I have found that packing up the circus crew of 6 for even a weekend away, can at times be a bit overwhelming. And while the kids love to help pack, sometimes they are anything but helpful. So, I found a system that works pretty well for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Little Trick that Has Been HUGE for us in School This Year</title>
      <link>/posts/the-new-little-trick-that-has-been-huge-for-us-in-school-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 09:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-new-little-trick-that-has-been-huge-for-us-in-school-this-year/</guid>
      <description>We are three weeks in to our new school year. I think I FINALLY have all the kids correct curriculum (missed a few things I when I ordered it this summer) and their books organized in a way that works for them, me, and their tutors at the tutorial. I’ve done things a little differently this year, and SO FAR, it has helped our days to run more smoothly. First of all, I’ve committed to waking up before the kids every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meatless Wednesdays… and Fish</title>
      <link>/posts/meatless-wednesdays-and-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/meatless-wednesdays-and-fish/</guid>
      <description>At the end of last year Scott and I went out for a big fun day date. As we thought back over the year and looked ahead at the new year we talked about things we wanted to do differently in the coming year. Scott had a few suggestions on the food front. One was that we eat more meatless dinners. He was not advocating we go vegetarian…(good thing too b/c this meat and potato loving gal would have surely lasted all of 2 days at best) the other was that we starting eating more fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping the Peace</title>
      <link>/posts/keeping-the-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/keeping-the-peace/</guid>
      <description>My kids love to draw and color and cut and create. And they are always, always, always asking me for paper. When my 4 year old doodled all over my check book, I knew I had to come up with something better. One day I stared at our empty popcorn tin and an idea hit me. For some reason the tin seemed perfect for storing crayons. Wouldn’t it be great, I thought, if we could have a roll of paper on our table like at Macaroni Grill?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cupcakes To Go!</title>
      <link>/posts/cupcakes-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cupcakes-to-go/</guid>
      <description>Ever tried to pack cupcakes in a lunch box? It creates a gooey mess all over the sandwich baggie and takes all the fun out of eating it when your hands are covered in icing. I saw this handy little trick in one of my student’s lunches back in my teaching days. Take your plain cupcake.

Slice it in half.

Take a glob of icing.
 Spread it in the middle of the cupcake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Valentine’s Tradition</title>
      <link>/posts/our-valentines-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-valentines-tradition/</guid>
      <description>I know that many think Valentine’s day is just a day created by Hallmark. Others think it’s a cheesy holiday for saps. Say what you will, I’ll jump at a chance for a date night with my hubby. And I don’t mind a sweet card and some cinnamon heart candy either.
But, after having kids, Scott and I found it rather difficult to go out for Valentine’s day. Since we don’t hire babysitters, we typically rely on friends or grandparents for babysitting and you can’t ask another couple to babysit for you on Valentine’s Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for the Stomach Flu</title>
      <link>/posts/preparing-for-the-stomach-flu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/preparing-for-the-stomach-flu/</guid>
      <description>The other night as we were driving home from out of town friends, our youngest complained that her belly didn’t feel good. A few minutes later I heard a cough and knew instantly what it meant. We pulled over and began clean up. For once I was thankful for our less than clean minivan as it provided numerous things for us to use as barf bags and clean up rags for the remaining hour drive home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Cookie Exchange: Saltine Brittle</title>
      <link>/posts/christmas-cookie-exchange-saltine-brittle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/christmas-cookie-exchange-saltine-brittle/</guid>
      <description>This year, I was looking for something simple and inexpensive that the kids could work together with me to make for their teachers. Too much to ask? I hoped not, but nothing was coming to me. And then I remembered this brittle that someone had brought to MOPS a few years ago. It uses saltine crackers. And you can pick up a box of Saltines at Aldi’s for 89 cents… which is perfect since I have to make gifts for SS and Bible Study teachers (times 3) plus neighbors and the tutorial teacher and “don’t forget my gymnastic teacher Mom!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up Close and Personal</title>
      <link>/posts/up-close-and-personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/up-close-and-personal/</guid>
      <description>Last week we took the kids to the local zoo. We have tried to go once a year for the past several years. We go in part b/c we want to give the kids a chance to see the exotic animals up close. It’s so fun to watch their reactions. But, I’ll be honest, we also go b/c I love to see the animals up close! It is amazing and awe inspiring and I don’t think I could ever tire of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Believe in Magic?</title>
      <link>/posts/do-you-believe-in-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/do-you-believe-in-magic/</guid>
      <description>I seriously wonder what moms did before the internet. Where did you go when you were looking for that cookie recipe you can’t find in your recipe box, or to check for tips on how to bring your child’s fever down, or to seek help tips for crayon removal?
A few weeks ago when I discovered this
 after my daughter’s naptime, I left a face book status that I was wondering how to get marker off of a baby doll face and within the hour I had 15 helpful tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Good Cookies Even Better</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-make-good-cookies-even-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-to-make-good-cookies-even-better/</guid>
      <description>Home made chocolate chip cookies are my favorite! I am partial to the recipe my mom got years ago. Perhaps you’ve seen the recipe as well. The story goes someone asked for Mrs. Fields cookie recipe and was told it cost two fifty. Upon receiving the recipe, she learned it cost two hundred and fifty dollars rather than two dollars and fifty cents. Outraged, she went on to share this recipe with the world to get back at them for charging so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Never Have to Do Dishes Again</title>
      <link>/posts/i-never-have-to-do-dishes-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/i-never-have-to-do-dishes-again/</guid>
      <description>I recently discovered a way to entertain and delight my children, while also getting some help in the kitchen. I let them wash dishes in the sink by hand. 
I don’t give them anything fragile. But at almost 3 and almost 5, they are quite capable of scrubbing pots and pans or large bowls…things I can’t squeeze into the dishwasher. They beg me for the opportunity and it keeps them content for up an hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Come Let Us Adore Him</title>
      <link>/posts/o-come-let-us-adore-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/o-come-let-us-adore-him/</guid>
      <description>I don’t remember what magazine or book I read it from, but a few years ago I found an idea for having a wise man celebration. For some reason I recall it being on January 6th. And I decided it was a good idea. But that year my entire family got struck with the stomach virus, so we skipped it. But last year and this year we celebrated, thus making it a tradition at our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Cookie Baking Time!!</title>
      <link>/posts/its-cookie-baking-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/its-cookie-baking-time/</guid>
      <description>After years of research in my test kitchen, I have found that Krusteaz sugar cookie mix tastes better than any of the &amp;ldquo;from scratch sugar cookies&amp;rdquo; I have made.
And not only do they taste good, but literally, you pour the mix, add water, and stir!!

This is crucial for me, because with my three preschoolers, Mommy needs to spend her time managing the flour and cutting out of the cookies, not measuring and mixing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crafty Tuesdays</title>
      <link>/posts/crafty-tuesdays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/crafty-tuesdays/</guid>
      <description>Crafty, I am not. But, I was an elementary education major, so I do know how to use scissors and glue. And, I have found that I really enjoy doing simple arts and crafts projects with my children.
But, the circus life can get rather busy. And as with most things, if I am not intentional, the opportunities and the moments pass me by.
So, this year I have designated Tuesday as &amp;ldquo;Crafty Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Potty Training Trick Ever</title>
      <link>/posts/best-potty-training-trick-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/best-potty-training-trick-ever/</guid>
      <description>Trekking out and about about with a toddler can be tricky enough, but running errands with a potty training toddler, her into everything ever curious, little sister and her energetic older brother is down right difficult. Those bathroom stalls were not meant for four people! But what do you do when your potty training toddler has to go and hasn&amp;rsquo;t learned how to hold it?
This genius idea is courtesy of my dear friend Rebecca.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Easy, Fun Fall Craft for You and Your Kiddos</title>
      <link>/posts/an-easy-fun-fall-craft-for-you-and-your-kiddos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/an-easy-fun-fall-craft-for-you-and-your-kiddos/</guid>
      <description>Last week the kids and I were looking for something fun to do during that difficult time of day between nap time and dinner. We went in the yard to collect some leaves for leaf rubbings and I got another idea of what to do with the leaves when we were finished with our rubbings.
We gathered leaves of various colors and types from the yard. I then took some strips of clear contact paper and peeled the backing off of the contact paper, leaving it sticky side up on the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Shop Online</title>
      <link>/posts/why-we-shop-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/why-we-shop-online/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago my hubby and I were shopping for a big purchase. We aren&amp;rsquo;t the type to make big purchases on the fly. They require lots of research and thinking and looking and more research then finally purchasing. Cameras, cars, computers, TV&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip; they&amp;rsquo;re all the same drill.
But with three kids under 4, it&amp;rsquo;s not quite as easy as it used to be.
We made two trips to the store in one weekend and I totally felt like a traveling circus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How We Enjoy the Game</title>
      <link>/posts/how-we-enjoy-the-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-we-enjoy-the-game/</guid>
      <description>Many of you know, that my hubby and I are big Pittsburgh Steelers fans. Sadly, many of the games are not televised here. We didn&amp;rsquo;t want to miss the big opening game on Sunday, so we took the kids to Glory Days restaurant to watch the game.
My hubby and I were a little nervous about how well this would go down. How would we keep 3 kids entertained sitting at a restaurant table for 3 hours?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Need for Goals</title>
      <link>/posts/my-need-for-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-need-for-goals/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t used to be a procrastinator, but now that I have 3 kids, I tend to take care of the urgent first. This means that sometimes my really good plans get altered when real life sets in. I have found that if I want to tackle a large project or extra thing (extra being not laundry, groceries, cleaning, cooking&amp;hellip; those necessities of life) I need to make a self-imposed deadline in order for it to happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Those Special Days</title>
      <link>/posts/remembering-those-special-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/remembering-those-special-days/</guid>
      <description>Wanna know how to get your husband to remember your birthday, anniversary, Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day, or other special occasion? I have a novel idea for you, that has worked well for me these past 7 years. Tell him!
My husband is horrible with calendars. His mind just simply doesn&amp;rsquo;t work that way. Quiz him on the date of my birthday and, given some time to think, he will probably get it. Ask him how far away that is and he will have no clue (He would need time to figure out which month we were in first).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks Mr Turtle</title>
      <link>/posts/thanks-mr-turtle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/thanks-mr-turtle/</guid>
      <description>When my oldest daughter was born my son wanted to get her this musical turtle he saw at Target for her crib. Every time we went to Target he would push the buttons to make it play music and he would ask if he could get it for his sister. We didn&amp;rsquo;t think it was necessary.
He was still insistent about it when our third child was born so we decided to let him get it for his sister for Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How far did I go?</title>
      <link>/posts/how-far-did-i-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-far-did-i-go/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned here, that I started running this summer. I am following a training schedule to help me reach my goal but it keeps changing the distance that I must run each day. Instead of guestimating (surely it&amp;rsquo;s been a mile by now) or driving the route with the car (like I really feel like loading the kids another time) to try to calculate the distance, my wonderful husband, the engineer, found me an online application made using google maps that is a HUGE help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A No Thank You Bite</title>
      <link>/posts/a-no-thank-you-bite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-no-thank-you-bite/</guid>
      <description>[] (https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/06/w4mewed1.jpg)
&amp;quot;Ew, gross!&amp;quot; &amp;quot;I don&amp;rsquo;t like it!&amp;quot; How many of you have had this response after working hard to prepare a new dish for you family? It can be quite frustrating especially if you know they&amp;rsquo;ll like it b/c they like every single one of the ingredients in it or worse yet, they devoured it the last time you made it and now won&amp;rsquo;t even try it.
My husband and I have always insisted the our kids at least try a bite of whatever it is we&amp;rsquo;re eating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are we there yet?</title>
      <link>/posts/are-we-there-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/are-we-there-yet/</guid>
      <description>Traveling for 5 hours in a minivan with 3 young children and one dog sounds like a kicking good time, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it? Since my parents live a little over 5 hrs from us, we&amp;rsquo;ve gotten quite adjusted to the trip. And surprisingly, it isn&amp;rsquo;t that bad. We&amp;rsquo;ve had our bad trips (like the time my son got the stomach flu the morning we were heading back home and puked every 30 min the entire way home), but overall we&amp;rsquo;ve found the key to happiness is letting the kids entertain themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Home Date Nights</title>
      <link>/posts/in-home-date-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/in-home-date-nights/</guid>
      <description>With three children under 4, it isn&amp;rsquo;t always easy to get out for a date night. Sometimes we do date nights at home. We feed the kids a simple dinner&amp;hellip; chicken nuggets or hot dogs. While I am getting the kids ready for bed, my husband grills us steak for dinner. We light a candle and enjoy a leisurely dinner together. We get to talk, uninterrupted and enjoy our food while it is still warm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everybody Dance Now</title>
      <link>/posts/everybody-dance-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/everybody-dance-now/</guid>
      <description>The other day I discovered a way to occupy my kids for a good 15-20 min, which many of you know is an eternity in Mommy time.
Wanna know the secret?
I let them play with my clock radio. I plugged it in and placed it on the floor in the living room. They had a blast taking turns turning it off and on and changing radio stations. It was more fun then Mommy turning on the stereo, because they had control of turning it on and off as well the fun of switching the music from station to station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving on a Jet Plane (don&#39;t forget to pack extra clothes)</title>
      <link>/posts/leaving-on-a-jet-plane-dont-forget-to-pack-extra-clothes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/leaving-on-a-jet-plane-dont-forget-to-pack-extra-clothes/</guid>
      <description>Last fall my husband and I took our three kids on a plane ride to CA to visit my husband&amp;rsquo;s grandparents and to take in some National Parks. The trip itself is worthy of a post, someday, but for now I&amp;rsquo;ll just share about our flight out there&amp;hellip;.
It seems obvious that when flying with three kids under 3 you bring a lot of stuff. We knew we would have to change flights half way so we tried to keep things to a minimum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behold the Power of Oxiclean</title>
      <link>/posts/behold-the-power-of-oxiclean/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/behold-the-power-of-oxiclean/</guid>
      <description>I have been singing the praises of oxiclean for some time now. It has gotten poop, tomato sauce, mud, and spit up out of my clothes for years. This Easter I REALLY put it to the test. We were dying eggs with the kids. My two year old had just plopped her egg into the red dye when she tipped the mug to peer into it and check out her handiwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurray for the Pack-n-Play!!</title>
      <link>/posts/hurray-for-the-pack-n-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hurray-for-the-pack-n-play/</guid>
      <description>If you read my blog post from Sunday you know that getting my laundry washed, dryed, folded, and put away is a big challenge for me. Today I found a way to help speed along that process. Even though my kids have an entire toy room which they can play in, they begged me to let them play in the pack-n-play while I folded laundry. Yes, that is correct, I actually said to my two and four year old, &amp;ldquo;If you fight or hit each other in there, you will have to come OUT of the pack-n-play.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
