<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sidelines on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/sidelines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sidelines on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 18:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/sidelines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Life is Good</title>
      <link>/posts/life-is-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/life-is-good/</guid>
      <description>Years ago Aunt Karen gave our oldest child a Life is Good soccer shirt. Because the color and theme were gender neutral, I ended up passing it down to my daughter a few years later. It actually became that perfect shirt for younger siblings to wear to soccer games so she could feel like she was a part of the team too. By the time my third child wore it, it was worn with shin guards and sometimes even cleats TO WATCH the older 2 practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Call it Crazy…</title>
      <link>/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</guid>
      <description>This spring I have 3 kids in sports. On 3 different teams. This in addition to the girls both taking gymnastics twice a week and Cub Scouts.
We are busy, busy, busy with games and practices most every night… some nights we’re even double booked.
Many people look at my schedule and call me crazy. Why do you do this to yourself?
The answer is, honestly, two fold. 1. We love it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting the bar</title>
      <link>/posts/setting-the-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/setting-the-bar/</guid>
      <description>Ever since my son dawned his shin guards and cleats for the first time, his little sister has been eagerly awaiting her opportunity. She’s watched longingly from the sidelines, eagerly taking the field during half time, yearning for her chance to tear up the field. Last fall during his practices, she would call me coach and ask me to assign her drills. I’d have her dribble the ball up and down the field, shooting under a bench as her imaginary goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Her Chance to Shine</title>
      <link>/posts/her-chance-to-shine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/her-chance-to-shine/</guid>
      <description>After spending many hours on the sidelines watching her big brother play soccer or baseball, today my middle child had a chance to shine in a sport of her own…
GYMNASTICS

And my fearless and flexible tumbler, LOVED it, much like I anticipated she would. 
She told me at the end of class, “Mommy, I’m a gymnast!”
Watch out Shawn Johnson, the 2020 Olympics could be all hers!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
