<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mess on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/mess/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mess on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 10:12:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/mess/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our Christmas Mess</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-christmas-mess/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-christmas-mess/</guid>
      <description>A traditional Christmas card will not be arriving in your mailbox this year from the circus fam, instead I give to you this greeting from me to you. I’ve thought a lot about what I want to say in this card. What image I want to share with you from my family to yours. We’ve had a lot of great moments this year. Many of them I’ve shared on here so I can look back and remember them in the years to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Need a Little Art</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-need-a-little-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-need-a-little-art/</guid>
      <description>We are on break here at the circus. And I couldn’t be more excited about it. I have been looking forward to this week for ages. The week before Christmas. All I want to do is enjoy the kiddos and catch up on some house work. And bake. And do some shopping. And maybe see some friends. (ha, ha… can you tell I am an introvert? read over that list, when I proof read this and re read it, it made me laugh)…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Late Night Cleaning Spree</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/late-night-cleaning-spree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/late-night-cleaning-spree/</guid>
      <description>The other night I came up to kiss the girls goodnight and found them voluntarily cleaning their room. And folks,I don’t mean stuffing toys under their beds and clothes down the laundry shoot. I found them in the closet sorting and they asked me for a laundry basket and a trashcan. It was already past their bed time, but they were clearly in the cleaning mode. And I know when it comes to things like Deep Cleaning you gotta embrace the mood when it hits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 year old in the House</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/2-year-old-in-the-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/2-year-old-in-the-house/</guid>
      <description>Number one sign you have a 2 year old boy in the house.
Nothing is safe. He will drag chairs to the counter to score out of reach cookies, he’ll fill cups with ice only to dump them on the floor, he’ll drink soda, coffee, whatever he finds left sitting out with reckless abandon. And he’ll sunscreen my dining room furniture. 
I had even seen the sunscreen lying out earlier and moved it to the center of the dining room table, “just incase”….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What? Do I have something on my face?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-do-i-have-something-on-my-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 06:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-do-i-have-something-on-my-face/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Does a 1 yr old Eat a Donut?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-does-a-1-yr-old-eat-a-donut/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-does-a-1-yr-old-eat-a-donut/</guid>
      <description>While we’re making him wait till the end of the month to savor his first taste of cake (at his party when his grandparents can be there to ooh and aah), we couldn’t let his day go by without some sort of yummy mess. Enter baby’s first donut for breakfast.

First, he ate each individual sprinkle off of the donut. 

Then, it was time to ditch the hat, and tack a dab at the icing… again using his fingers to scrape it clean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Busy…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-busy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-busy/</guid>
      <description>People often ask me what the girls do while I am doing homeschooling with my oldest child.

On Tuesday the answer was “take all the cushions off the couch and every single blanket and pillow they owned and build a fort”


 If I am distracted enough they even smoke a stogie or two in their fort. (just kidding those would be pretzel rods…I promise, but doesn’t this bottom picture look sketchy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Someone Stole a Cookie from the Cookie Jar</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/someone-stole-a-cookie-from-the-cookie-jar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/someone-stole-a-cookie-from-the-cookie-jar/</guid>
      <description>Who me?
 Couldn’t be

Then, who?

Visit here or here for more fun with pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
