<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cub scouts on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/cub-scouts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cub scouts on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 12:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/cub-scouts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Things about My Day at Cub Scout Camp</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/top-10-things-about-my-day-at-cub-scout-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/top-10-things-about-my-day-at-cub-scout-camp/</guid>
      <description>Last week my oldest son went to a week of Cub Scout Day Camp. This year he was a Webelos 1. I remember vividly his first year when he was but a wee Tiger Scout.  He loves Cub Scout camp. And who wouldn’t? 8 and a half hours outside each day, fishing, archery, BB guns, wood shop, specials, crafts…
Each parent is required to volunteer one day. Two years Scott served in this role, last year I went, but it was the last day of camp and I didn’t get to see as much of the action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eye on the Prize</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/eye-on-the-prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 06:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/eye-on-the-prize/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend was our Cub Scout Pack’s Pine Wood Derby race. It is one of the favorite Cub Scout traditions. Scott and our oldest son worked hard on the car.

My son had one focus: speed
He wanted his car to be as fast as possible. Whenever they discussed designs or modifications, speed was always his deciding factor. 


He designed his car to look like Bullet Bill from Wii Mario Kart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Cake You Can Play With</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-cake-you-can-play-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-cake-you-can-play-with/</guid>
      <description>It’s February and that means Blue and Gold banquet season for Cub Scout folks. An annual tradition at our Blue and Gold banquet is the Dad/Lad cake decorating contest. [
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/IMG_9501.jpg)

This is always a fun event in the circus household. Even though all of the baking and decorating is done by Dad and the cub scout… the rest of the kids greatly enjoy observing the fun in the kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3-2-1…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/3-2-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/3-2-1/</guid>
      <description>Despite wet ground and a rainy forecast all systems were go for the Cub Scout rocket launch this morning. 
And, I gotta come clean on this one… it was WAY cooler than I thought it would be. They built the rockets at home and then went to the field to stuff them and other technical stuff which I didn’t really follow all to closely.

Then they set the rockets up on their “launch pads”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping with the Cub Scouts</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/camping-with-the-cub-scouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/camping-with-the-cub-scouts/</guid>
      <description>This weekend the family went on a Cub Scout camp out from Friday- Saturday evening. The kids have been begging to go camping again, and this over nighter was the perfect little get away for us. As an added convenience it was at a State Park not far from our house, so it was quite easy to pop home if you needed something and made it no big deal when we got a late start on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Lil Cub</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-lil-cub/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-lil-cub/</guid>
      <description>6 years ago I watched my lil man proudly hold his head high during tummy time. I was so excited b/c he had recently learned to roll over. He was growing up so fast and I was thrilled with all he was learning and doing. I had no idea that in just 6 short years he’d be at Cup Scout camp with Daddy learning a whole slew of new things.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
