<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dinner conversations on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/dinner-conversations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dinner conversations on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 10:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/dinner-conversations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Many Miles Can We Get Out of This? or Milking This One for ALL its Worth</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-many-miles-can-we-get-out-of-this-or-milking-this-one-for-all-itsworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-many-miles-can-we-get-out-of-this-or-milking-this-one-for-all-itsworth/</guid>
      <description>Some of you may remember my post last December (as in 2009) in which I shared one of Scott’s moments of sheer brilliance at the dinner table. Well, I feel the need to tell you that 13 months later and my kids are STILL eating their vegetables to spite their Daddy. I am sure this says something of their character… for which we must spend some time rectifying, but meanwhile my mean spirited little children are eagerly gobbling up their vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Do It?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/can-you-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/can-you-do-it/</guid>
      <description>I remember very little from my college biology class. The one thing that sticks in my brain is the genetics unit. I can remember sitting there running through the calculations and thinking, “If Scott and I were to get married we’d have blue eyed kids.” The hopeless romantic, head over heels in love teen that I was, I enjoyed the game of “wonder if.” The other thing from the genetics unit that sticks out is that the ability to touch your tongue to your nose is genetically dictated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
