<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>beach on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/beach/</link>
    <description>Recent content in beach on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 01:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/beach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Pacific Ocean!!!</title>
      <link>/posts/the-pacific-ocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 01:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-pacific-ocean/</guid>
      <description>After leaving Joshua Tree, we were headed west for the Pacific Ocean. We checked out the visitor center and checked in with the boat company about our day trip the following day. Then we stopped at Subway to grab subs for dinner on the beach. 
We were camping at a State Park which had walking access to the beach. We all greatly enjoyed eating dinner overlooking the ocean and than splashing in the waves afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Ending</title>
      <link>/posts/perfect-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/perfect-ending/</guid>
      <description>The last true day of our vacation (the day before we headed home) was in my opinion the most relaxing day of the week.
We slept in, ate breakfast, (the kids did the dishes), and then we headed out for a morning hike along the beach.
 
The tide was out and we discovered many living creatures in tide pools on the rocky beach
.


We made our way to the other side of the island and even caught a glimpse of the Boston skyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Each Their Own</title>
      <link>/posts/to-each-their-own/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/to-each-their-own/</guid>
      <description>Some people like the feeling of sand beneath their toes. I must say I do enjoy the squish of wet sand beneath my feet as the waves lap at my ankles. My children, however, have a whole different kind of love of sand.

One which truly baffles my mind.

EVERY SINGLE TIME we visit our community beach, it’s the same routine. We drop our stuff in the sand and they make a mad dash for the water, they splash and play and swim and then, inevitably, they decide it’s time to hit the sand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He’s Still my Baby</title>
      <link>/posts/hes-still-my-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hes-still-my-baby/</guid>
      <description>My lil man reached a major milestone today as he played in the sand. We’ve been going to the beach, splashing in the water and playing in the sand all summer long. And all summer long he has wanted to put fist full upon fist full of sand into his mouth. You’d think eventually cause and effect would come in to play, but he never seemed to mind the mouth full of grit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Hour at the Beach</title>
      <link>/posts/an-hour-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/an-hour-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>Most people think that perfect beach weather is a bright sunny day, but we discovered unexpected joy in a trip to the Florida beach on an overcast evening following an afternoon rain storm.

Shuttle launch in the morning, nap in the afternoon, beach in the evening, and free Chick-Fil-A right before bed… it was a perfect day in Florida… totally worth the 32 hours of driving it took to get there and back.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
