<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keeping it Real on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/keeping-it-real/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Keeping it Real on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 03:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/keeping-it-real/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>When Superman Takes Up Permanent Residence in Your Dining Room</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-superman-takes-up-permanent-residence-in-your-dining-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-superman-takes-up-permanent-residence-in-your-dining-room/</guid>
      <description>Exactly one month ago today we had a Superman birthday party for my youngest. In addition to a slew of crepe paper, we hung a giant poster of Superman on the hutch in our dining room.
Last night I noticed that Superman still hangs in my dining room.

He’s hung there for an entire month.
We let him hang there until we moved it up to the boys room. This way it wouldn’t wrinkle or rip until we got around to it, and maybe by leaving it hanging in our dining room we’d be more motivated to get around to it sooner than later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Words</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-words/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, the kids spent a long weekend at my parents while Scott and I enjoyed St Louis. While they were there, my parents took the kids to a friends farm. The kids had a blast. Seriously, a day doesn’t go by that they don’t mention the horses or the chickens or the barn cats. They even got to ride on the horses. Right up there with all those memory making experiences, was another new life experience for my 4 year old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Christmas Mess</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-christmas-mess/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-christmas-mess/</guid>
      <description>A traditional Christmas card will not be arriving in your mailbox this year from the circus fam, instead I give to you this greeting from me to you. I’ve thought a lot about what I want to say in this card. What image I want to share with you from my family to yours. We’ve had a lot of great moments this year. Many of them I’ve shared on here so I can look back and remember them in the years to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Need a Little Art</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-need-a-little-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-need-a-little-art/</guid>
      <description>We are on break here at the circus. And I couldn’t be more excited about it. I have been looking forward to this week for ages. The week before Christmas. All I want to do is enjoy the kiddos and catch up on some house work. And bake. And do some shopping. And maybe see some friends. (ha, ha… can you tell I am an introvert? read over that list, when I proof read this and re read it, it made me laugh)…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Clean Once Again Proves Himself to be a Worthy tool in the Arsenal of Motherhood</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mr.-clean-once-again-proves-himself-to-be-a-worthy-tool-in-the-arsenalof-motherhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mr.-clean-once-again-proves-himself-to-be-a-worthy-tool-in-the-arsenalof-motherhood/</guid>
      <description>I don’t really know what it is that possesses a child to just randomly on a whim pick up that crayon and suddenly decide to make the world (or in this case the bathroom) his canvas. We have crayons out every single day in our house. I do my best when I see a stray one on the floor to nab it lest it suddenly look inviting to my toddler. But, truly they are laying on the school table, in reach, every single day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Her First Meet (the Good, the Bad, the UGLY)</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/her-first-meet-the-good-the-bad-the-ugly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/her-first-meet-the-good-the-bad-the-ugly/</guid>
      <description>Our 6 year old had her first gymnastics meet this past weekend. I can’t really put into words the feelings of pride I had in watching her. When we first enrolled her in gymnastics 3 years ago, we did so because she was tiny, tough and flexible. It seemed gymnastics might be worth a try for our then 3 year old.
Somewhere in the last 3 years, a light when on inside her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe One Day We Won’t Be So “Circus Like”</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/maybe-one-day-we-wont-be-so-circus-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 03:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/maybe-one-day-we-wont-be-so-circus-like/</guid>
      <description>Some days we wake up on “school at the building days” with clothes all lined up and ready the night before, I’ve gotten lunches packed complete with notes from Mom, and we’re out the door on time so we can arrive at the building with plenty of time to drop everyone&amp;rsquo;s books off in their classrooms and report to the sanctuary for opening with time to spare.
And some mornings Mom oversleeps when her alarm goes off, laundry isn’t put away so we find ourselves scrounging through baskets of laundry looking for matching socks, lunches are packed but without drinks b/c we couldn’t find water bottles, and we stumble out the door racing the clock, with bed head and arrive at school only to discover the socks were left on the kitchen counter so we’re going in with just sneakers and no cute knee socks…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A.Big.Fat.PANSY</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a.big.fat.pansy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a.big.fat.pansy/</guid>
      <description>I like to think of myself as a woman who can hold her own. I’m not a girly girl. I can follow a football game and I am currently 3-0 in my fantasy league. I love camping. Power outages don’t send me packing for the nearest Hilton. And I will happily kill and remove any bug that comes my way without even a squeal.
However, this “tough girl” fantasy that I have of myself falls apart rather quickly when confronted with my own personal kryptonite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Answer to Everyone’s Question</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-answer-to-everyones-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-answer-to-everyones-question/</guid>
      <description>Lately, I’ve been asked several times what I do with my 2 year old while I am teaching the older 3. Here’s your answer. 
Yes, that would be pen mark up and down the corner of the walls in my dining room. Yes, he did that yesterday morning while I was working with the big kids in the other room and thought that scraping sound was the sound of him scraping oatmeal of his cereal bowl with a spoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even the Otterbox Has its Limits</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/even-the-otterbox-has-its-limits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/even-the-otterbox-has-its-limits/</guid>
      <description>The morning was going well… kids on time for tutorial, load of laundry in the washer and dryer, even took the van to the garage for some repairs.
And then, because things can’t go THAT smoothly….. 
 Yea… turns out even the otterbox can’t protect your phone when it’s been thrown off the side of a van and run over on the side of a highway. And, no, this had NOTHING to do with the new iphone 5 coming out today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True Story</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/true-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/true-story/</guid>
      <description>Last night I fed my family a dinner so lacking in nutritional value or substance that it makes the time we had ice cream for dinner look healthy.
I kid you not.
We’ve been burning the candle at both ends round the circus parts the past week… finishing up projects at the old house, organizing the new house, having company, throwing a birthday party…having more company… somehow yesterday it ended up 8pm, the Olympics were on and we’d all been looking forward to watching them… we hadn’t eaten dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aren’t Clean Clothes Just a Little Over Rated?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/arent-clean-clothes-just-a-little-over-rated/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/arent-clean-clothes-just-a-little-over-rated/</guid>
      <description>In the midst of all the birthday party and Valentine’s day preparations and excitement, someone suffered from some severe neglect.

Excuse me while I attempt to make up with my overlooked and neglected washing machine. If you don’t hear from me in awhile, look under the pile of clothes… I may have surrendered in defeat!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Secret Ambition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-secret-ambition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 06:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-secret-ambition/</guid>
      <description>I’ve had a few shows over the past 10 years, that I’ve really loved. You know the ones where you connect personally with the characters in a manner some might find unhealthy? But, if I had to pick one, as my favorite (I’d probably kick and scream begging you to not make me limit it to just one) But, if I had to pick one, than I’d probably say it was Alias.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There is HOPE</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/there-is-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/there-is-hope/</guid>
      <description>For all those wondering if there is truly hope for the hopeless… those who’ve made their resolutions and long since broken them… for those that thought, perhaps your just destined for failure…. to those… I offer this little glimmer of hope….
Our last visit to the library—if that trip didn’t redeem us, I don’t know what will!
Those who have been long time readers here at the circus… might recall I have a bit of a bad history with the library… first, we have the whole circus family wing of the library thanks to the $18 fine visit and the $42 fine visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The one in which I question whether I should keep blogging…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-one-in-which-i-question-whether-i-should-keep-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-one-in-which-i-question-whether-i-should-keep-blogging/</guid>
      <description>I feel busy… these past few months have probably been the busiest I’ve been in quite awhile. Scott worked a ton of overtime, the oldest three played soccer, the girls both did gymnastics, my oldest son started piano lessons, cub scouts is back in action, the home school year began—it takes up way more of my day than it used to…. I am not complaining… I willingly signed up for all of these things (ok… except for the overtime part) and I enjoy them… it’s a stage of life for us that is fleeting, I know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life With 2</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-with-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-with-2/</guid>
      <description>Now that my oldest 2 are at their tutorial two days a week, I find myself with just 2 children at home on those mornings. It is a truly odd feeling and a dynamic I am not yet used to. Though I am sure it is nothing compared to the strangeness I’ll feel next year when I am left with only my lil man two days a week. I am hoping to use this time to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circus Family Sayings</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/circus-family-sayings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/circus-family-sayings/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I have a few sayings that we use often with the kids.
Life is not Fair
Life isn’t Always About You
You Can’t Cry to Get What You Want
and….
Never Trust a Bad Guy
1 -3 are pretty self explanatory… in a family of 6, you learn quickly that your not going to get what you want when you want it, you gotta wait, and that’s just the way it goes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Re-Entry is Rough</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/re-entry-is-rough/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/re-entry-is-rough/</guid>
      <description>While our world wind trip to and from Florida went off really without a hitch, the 48 hrs since pulling into our driveway have been anything but smooth sailing.
Allow me to complain… We got home at 9pm on Sunday night… we unloaded what we had to, put the kids to bed and sat on the couch. Monday morning was back to reality… Scott had to be at work at 8, and the oldest two had to be at church at 8:45 for VBS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few Little Gems</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-few-little-gems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-few-little-gems/</guid>
      <description>While looking through pictures recently, I stumbled across a few which truly captured life at the circus in its essence.
Exhibit A: taken in December of 2010

Here they are working on the pine wood derby car for Cub Scouts. Notice how everyone, even the baby, is in on the action? Noticed the leotard? My girls wear leotards every.single.day…. even though gymnastics is only twice a week, I can guarantee you those leotards are on more often than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Insignificant?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/feeling-insignificant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/feeling-insignificant/</guid>
      <description>Last week after telling my kids the Bible story of baby Moses, I decided to offer a little application for them. I pointed out how neat it was that God took care of Moses as a baby by allowing the princess to find him. I even told how amazing it was that his own mother was allowed to take care of him before he went to live at the palace. After discussing how Moses grew up in the Egyptian palace, I pointed out how God used that later in his life when Moses led the Israelites out of captivity in Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Sufficient…to a point…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/self-sufficientto-a-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/self-sufficientto-a-point/</guid>
      <description>One of the many reasons why life is easier this time around is that my older three kids are much more self sufficient.
When we need to head out the door, I can instruct the kids to get their shoes on, go to the van and buckle up. A few minutes later the baby and I arrive at the van. I buckle him in, do a quick seatbelt check on the big kids and we hit the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning the Day Around</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/turning-the-day-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2011 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/turning-the-day-around/</guid>
      <description>This morning I was reminded what a great gift forgiveness is. It was a rough morning… the last day of a very busy week with not as much down time as we’re accustomed to. I felt the fatigue that morning with heavy eyes searching for the remote to buy me a few more moments of rest before I hit the to do list. I noticed the fatigue in children who quickly burst into tears or whiny screams over rather insignificant things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keepin it Real Circus Mom Style</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keepin-it-real-circus-mom-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keepin-it-real-circus-mom-style/</guid>
      <description>In the interest of keeping it real, and hopefully finding out I am not alone… thought I’d share a few “Not Me Monday” moments on this Tuesday afternoon….
*It was not me that showed up with the girls at gymnastics last Wednesday with their feet and legs covered in mud from our morning play date at the park. And as I wiped their legs down with wet paper towels it wasn’t me who was saying out loud so the other moms could over hear how “I gave them baths that morning but then took them to the park to play” Silly me should have known they’d find a pond and sea weed and a muddy field….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You think I’d know by now…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-think-id-know-by-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-think-id-know-by-now/</guid>
      <description>When my son asked if he could bring his light sabers or guns to his sisters first soccer practice, I said no. Because sometimes it is awkward to deal with the whole gun issue out in public.
Obviously I forgot that little boys will turn absolutely anything into a gun.
So today I said what the heck, bring the gun. Which apparently translated to, go crazy, carry a gun in each hand and a concealed weapon… Heck, why not wear the entire uniform!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banner Week</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/banner-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/banner-week/</guid>
      <description>Exciting things are happening round the circus parts this week and it’s only Tuesday!!
Sunday, I ran a half marathon with my FIL. My friend, who had to run a half marathon in order to see me in real life, also ran but she was so stinking fast that I am glad I caught her in line for the potty before the race, b/c there was no seeing her after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Priceless</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/priceless/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/priceless/</guid>
      <description>Container of dish soap: $2.00

Chip in my favorite coffee mug: $10.00

Keeping 2 sisters happy and entertained for an hour: Priceless</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking on Sunshine</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/walking-on-sunshine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/walking-on-sunshine/</guid>
      <description>Those of you that follow me on facebook or twitter, or have spent any time round these circus parts, know that I whine quite a bit about laundry. Recently, however, I made a startling discovery. Rather than being the bane of my existence as I once thought, it is in fact, the key to my happiness?
Say wha??
Last May, I set out with a quest to get entirely caught up on my laundry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/today/</guid>
      <description>Today I had planned to write a sweet and nostalgic motherhood type post about my littlest cast member. But, when quiet time rolled around my head was aching, my mind racing, and the right words and sentiments weren’t coming to me. Because today…
*Today I tried to do 2 days worth of school in one morning since we’ll be out of town on Monday
*Today I made banana chocolate chip pancakes for breakfast</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Ya Gotta Go….</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-ya-gotta-go./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2010 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-ya-gotta-go./</guid>
      <description>The outing started out so beautiful and picturesque. The drive there was lovely… leaves just starting to change, sipping my pumpkin spice latte, even the clouds looked “fall like” (amazing how everything looks lovely when the kids aren’t requiring you to referee from the drivers seat…thank you Psalty the Singing Songbook) We got to the farm and the kids happily ate their lunches while I nursed the baby. Then we were off to pick apples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worst Garden Ever</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/worst-garden-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/worst-garden-ever/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to stop pretending. The act is over. Who am I kidding?
I am not a gardener.
Each spring, I get bitten by a gardening bug and I think that I will turn over a new leaf and suddenly spawn a green thumb. So, I buy some plants and seeds and the kids and I set off to garden. Each spring Scott asks why am I doing this when I know what will happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimme a Break</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gimme-a-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gimme-a-break/</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to make oral reading more fun, I gave my son the option of picking any location in our house to do his reading time.  He chose my closet.
Would not have been my first choice, but no worries, to the closet we went… I brought a pillow for me to sit on as the floor isn’t so comfy for this 9 mth pregnant momma. My son looked at me and said, “Hey, how come you aren’t sharing that pillow with me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Welcomes The US Govt</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-welcomes-the-us-govt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-welcomes-the-us-govt/</guid>
      <description>We had really good intentions, I swear.
We got the envelope in the mail and when it came, I remember Scott perusing it and saying, “We must mail this in soon. We can’t forget to do this.” And so I did what I do with all of our important papers and I put it on the counter so I wouldn’t lose it and so I’d know right where they were.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross Country Fashion Consult</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cross-country-fashion-consult/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cross-country-fashion-consult/</guid>
      <description>As I’ve already made well aware, I am not exactly a fashion guru. You won’t find me flipping through the pages of Cosmopolitan in my free time. My nails are rarely done and my idea of styling my hair involves taking the time to blow dry rather than air dry.
I wanted to look cute when Scott and I went on a date a few weeks ago. I was so excited because my friend had just lent me some adorable maternity clothes so I didn’t really give my thought to my wardrobe till about 30 min before we were going to leave when I began to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numbers</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/numbers/</guid>
      <description>It’s been ** 2 ** years since I began writing “Life At The Circus.”
** 2 ** years and 654 posts
2 years, can you believe it? I can’t.
When I look back at my first posts, I laugh at how much my life has changed… and how much it hasn’t. It’s the end of the month and I gotta tell you, my fridge looks pretty much exactly the same as it did here two years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comfort Clothes</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/comfort-clothes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/comfort-clothes/</guid>
      <description>I know you’ve heard of comfort foods…typically something warm and gooey that reminds you of home or growing up or just makes you feel good inside. Well, this preggo woman has comfort clothes. And they aren’t pretty. OK, let me explain. (oh, how I wish there was a good explanation…) When I was pregnant with my son I got to be so, ahem large, that I started stealing shirts from Scott’s tee shirt drawers…Not to wear in public mind you, but I did wear them around the house so I could save my “cute “maternity clothes for when I saw people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filing this one under &#39;Conversations I never expected to have with my little girl&#39;</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/filing-this-one-under-conversations-i-never-expected-to-have-with-mylittle-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/filing-this-one-under-conversations-i-never-expected-to-have-with-mylittle-girl/</guid>
      <description>I was cleaning the bathroom yesterday (I know, miracles never cease, huh?) when my 2 and 1/2 year old daughter came in to use the potty. “Go ahead,” I told her. (Have I mentioned that I LOVE the fact that all 3 kids can use their potty on their own, ah sweet bliss—for 11 more weeks!) Well I turned from scrubbing the tub to see her standing beside the potty. “I want to go this way!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Crew Visits the OB</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-crew-visits-the-ob/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-crew-visits-the-ob/</guid>
      <description>I typically schedule my OB appointments for first thing in the morning so that the kids can stay home with Scott. This time however, his work schedule didn’t cooperate, so I brought the circus crew with me for my check up. I knew at 28 weeks they wouldn’t be doing an exam, so I felt comfortable having them tag along. I did come prepared with coloring books, crayons, snacks, and even lollipops which I saved for the very end if they were “super stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You take the good, you take the bad…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-take-the-good-you-take-the-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-take-the-good-you-take-the-bad/</guid>
      <description>“You take the good, you take the bad, you take them both and there you have The Facts of Life, the Facts of Life.”
Blogging is funny, as many of you bloggers know, because when you write a post, you’re really writing a snapshot of a moment in time. And as as the author (or photographer, if you will) you get to choose which moment in time you post and thus you can largely shape the perception of your self and your family life that you present to the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My REAL and honest thoughts on all this SNOW</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-real-and-honest-thoughts-on-all-this-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-real-and-honest-thoughts-on-all-this-snow/</guid>
      <description>If your from the midatlantic region (as most of my readers are, b/c I think most of my readers stalk me from facebook) then you have probably seen and read and heard all you want about snow this past week. Seriously, I have scrolled through and looked at gazillions of pictures of face book friends back decks overflowing with snow and seen kids waste high in it, which is kind of funny since I can look out my own windows and see the very same images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Inner Struggle</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-inner-struggle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-inner-struggle/</guid>
      <description>January has been hard for me. We have our Christmas decorations down, but still not put away. There is a underlying sense of clutter and chaos lurking around the circus, rather than the clean slate, fresh start of a new year. I long for a good, deep clean to get things in order, top to bottom and help me to feel on top of things once again. But, it seems each day I am pulled by the more immediate needs of the day… sick kids… volunteering at school, entertaining guests, New Years cards (never got to the Christmas cards, did print New Years cards and really wanted them mailed before Feb), and school work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Life…Back to Reality…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/back-to-lifeback-to-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/back-to-lifeback-to-reality/</guid>
      <description>Vacation was wonderful.
Honestly, it was more of a “staycation” and stay and cation I did.
Scott redid all the plumbing in our house this past week. He also used his new Christmas gift-a smoker to make us dinner twice. 
I, on the other hand, staycationed.
And as I surveyed the house this morning, boy did it show.
With Scott plumbing all week, I actually had a reasonable excuse for my laundry neglect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procrastinate Much?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/procrastinate-much/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/procrastinate-much/</guid>
      <description>Only 2 days till Christmas and my to do list today looks like this.
 Clean bathroom- scrub toilet, scrub sink, scrub tub and tile (I write each individually so I can feel more satisfaction when I am done by crossing off 4 things instead of one) Clean guestroom- My parents always say, don’t worry or stress about cleaning up for them. And I appreciate the fact that I can keep things real and not stress out, but… I think I need to clear off a place for them to sleep, don’t you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Me Humble</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-me-humble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2009 16:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-me-humble/</guid>
      <description>I was feeling pretty good about myself this week. Got a little boost of energy with week 12 and began to tame this household which I had slacked off on over the first trimester. Finally, I can leave the guest bedroom door open as well as the master bed room. I even cleaned out the van which had reached its height of total messiness, threw away all that trash crammed in around the car seats and brought in the plethora of coats and shoes which were strewn all over the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Any other sneaks out there?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/any-other-sneaks-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 08:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/any-other-sneaks-out-there/</guid>
      <description>OK, so Halloween was 6 days ago, and I gotta tell you this circus mom has had more than her fair share of the loot. The kids are doing quite well with an occasional piece after a meal here or there. Mom on the other hand seems to go for the candy bowl come nap and bed time and she rarely stops with one. The other morning when the kids came out to the living room my son spotted a few candy wrappers sitting on the couch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost and Found</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lost-and-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lost-and-found/</guid>
      <description>Remember my confession back in May about my hefty library charge? I am happy to report that I’ve actually gotten much better about returning library books since then. And no, it’s not because I’ve stopped going to the library. Sure, I’ve paid an occasional fee here or there, but nothing close to the $42.09 I paid back in May. Perhaps they won’t be naming the local branch after the circus family after all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Really, I did…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-really-i-did/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-really-i-did/</guid>
      <description>As I’ve returned to the classroom these past few weeks (though in a very different atmosphere), I can’t help but reflect on my years of teaching prior to becoming a stay at home mom. I was blessed to teach for 3 years at a small, Christian school. I learned a lot and grew from the experience. I honestly think it shaped the way I parent today.
That being said, I can’t help but reflect on the single.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping it Real: Potty Training Edition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-it-real-potty-training-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 19:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-it-real-potty-training-edition/</guid>
      <description>In the interest of keeping it real and not pretending to be something I am not, I feel the need to come clean.
Remember how excited I was when my 2 year old was wearing underwear at her 2nd birthday?
Yea, I believe I received many a pat on the back and comments of “You’ll have to come potty train my kid.”
Well, I must come clean and say for the past few weeks she has totally regressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number One Rule of Camping</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/number-one-rule-of-camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/number-one-rule-of-camping/</guid>
      <description>**Updated Below!
Once we finally departed, the kids were ecstatic about our camping trip this weekend. As we were preparing to leave, my son already started talking about the very, important rules of camping, as he’s discovered them over the years.
And the number one, most exciting rule is that **
camping is messy!
**
This one cracked me up, because while it is true, to hear him talk you would think he grew up in a house where he was never allowed to get dirty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But, of course!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/but-of-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 11:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/but-of-course/</guid>
      <description>I am a home body. Truth be told, I can go a good four days of staying at home before I go stir crazy and need to get out and about. And as a home body, I love, LOVE days where we go no where and just stay home all day. These days don’t happen all too often, maybe about once a week. Because, my kids LOVE to go out. Even if it is grocery shopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millions of Peaches, Peaches for Me</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/millions-of-peaches-peaches-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 20:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/millions-of-peaches-peaches-for-me/</guid>
      <description>As much as I like to think I am not, I am a city girl. My “garden” consists of 6 plants in a square patch on the side of my house. We get our eggs in a carton at the grocery store and our milk in gallon jugs just down the aisle from the milk.
So, I try to give my kids farm fresh experiences as much as possible. It takes a bit of driving, but seems like a small price to pay in my book to give my kids prior knowledge experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wasn’t Me…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wasnt-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wasnt-me/</guid>
      <description>Nothing like a week of Vacation Bible School to leave this circus mom with more “not me” moments than I care to admit. Because I love to keep it real, here’s a few highlights from our week.
 Meet my dear friend. When it comes to friends, she’s one of the bestest. For many reasons. An example of which is the fact that she willingly cuts my girls hair for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Do It?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/can-you-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/can-you-do-it/</guid>
      <description>I remember very little from my college biology class. The one thing that sticks in my brain is the genetics unit. I can remember sitting there running through the calculations and thinking, “If Scott and I were to get married we’d have blue eyed kids.” The hopeless romantic, head over heels in love teen that I was, I enjoyed the game of “wonder if.” The other thing from the genetics unit that sticks out is that the ability to touch your tongue to your nose is genetically dictated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Problem Solved</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/problem-solved/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 17:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/problem-solved/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for all who wrote last week with your thoughts and suggestions on my dinner time dilemma.
No worries though.
Tonight my kids sat down and ate their dinner without one complaint.
Not one. And let me tell you there was no dilly dallying. They sat on the curb, gobbled it up with relatively little mess and we were on our merry way, walking around downtown enjoying the boats and the harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Jam Circus Style</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/making-jam-circus-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/making-jam-circus-style/</guid>
      <description>If you’re anything like me, you don’t really need one more reason to enjoy carbs. Yet, I can’t help but share my favorite. One of my mom’s most highly requested recipes growing up was for her strawberry jam. She always got a kick out it when people asked her if she would please share it.
So, here’s the family secret.
Yup, buy yourself a box of Sure Jell, add 4 cups of crushed berries, and 4 cups of sugar, and you are set!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Summer of Swimming</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-summer-of-swimming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-summer-of-swimming/</guid>
      <description>This spring I declared that this summer, summer of 2009 would be the circus family’s summer of swimming. The past several summers I’ve either had an infant or been ready to pop and really haven’t devoted the time necessary to teach my crew how to swim. I’ve given some half hearted attempts, but the bottom line is my kids can’t swim.
And when you live near the bay as we do, it really is a necessity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And You Wondered Why I Call it Life at the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-you-wondered-why-i-call-it-life-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-you-wondered-why-i-call-it-life-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes a mother’s ability to multitask isn’t a good thing… as I attempt to juggle one to many balls, I find that I can accidentally drop one and not even realize it for several hours.
Last week while I was talking on the phone and cleaning up the living room, I noticed the kids sitting on the floor with some stuffed animals and scissors.
I keenly observed that something looked amiss, so I grabbed the scissors from my sons hands, quickly told him that they needed to be used only at the table, and went to the other room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the Elevator</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/in-the-elevator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2009 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/in-the-elevator/</guid>
      <description>There is something alluring, almost magical about the buttons on an elevator. My kids enthusiastically clamor for the opportunity to press the shiny buttons both outside and inside of the elevator. We have a routine when entering elevators which typically works flawlessly. One child pushes the button on the outside. The second child then pushes the same button. Once inside they each get a turn pushing the button for the floor we want to go on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who, Me???</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2009 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-me/</guid>
      <description>Keep it real… I try really hard to make that my mantra in blogging and in life. That is why I leap at the chance to participate in carnivals like this one, where I can join up wither other real bloggers and rip off any fake facades of perfection. Because really, who has time for facades when you’re chasing three naked kids around the house, trying to find matching shoes, and attempting to get out the door on time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confessions of a Circus Mom</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/confessions-of-a-circus-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/confessions-of-a-circus-mom/</guid>
      <description>I have become a procrastinator. Actually I am worse than a procrastinator b/c procrastinators put things off till the last minute and then get them done. I didn’t used to be this way but now I tend to put them off till the last minute and then the deadline passes and I am still left with the job undone. Case in point: I bought my mom her mothers day card at the end of April.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WOW Have I Gotta Lot to Do!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wow-have-i-gotta-lot-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2009 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wow-have-i-gotta-lot-to-do/</guid>
      <description>If you’re anything like me then perhaps you’ve got a project or two that’s been sitting on the back burner for awhile… in the daily struggle to get dinner on the table and clean underwear out of the dryer, some how those bigger projects get pushed off until “later.”
Well, Becky’s got a carnival going on this week to inspire us to tackle those projects we’ve been meaning to get to, but haven’t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shame on Me</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shame-on-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 18:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shame-on-me/</guid>
      <description>Much like I do almost every day, I loaded my sweet baby girl into her car seat. I buckled her in and then handed her a purple sippy cup.
After strapping her sister in her seat and after double checking her brother, I went to my spot in the front. About 20 minutes later I looked back and saw my sweet baby girl holding two purple sippy cups.
“Where did that other cup come from?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re Ruining Her</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-ruining-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2009 06:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-ruining-her/</guid>
      <description>Since we first brought my youngest home from the hospital at two days old, she has been a good sleeper. You could just lay her down and walk away and she would soothe herself to sleep. Scott and I commented a few months ago that we haven’t had to go in the middle of the night to help soothe her back to sleep. Even when she threw up in her crib in the middle of the night, she just rolled back over and went to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Gonna Have To” Leave Alone Bars</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gonna-have-to-leave-alone-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gonna-have-to-leave-alone-bars/</guid>
      <description>Tonight my son had his very first baseball practice and he was as cute as could be and I am dying to share some pix of the occasion, but my brain is complete mush after taking care of my sick girls all day (and it’s clear we still have a very long night ahead of us). I will save it for later this week when I can give it the time it deserves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Through the Eyes of My Soon To Be 5 Year Old</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/through-the-eyes-of-my-soon-to-be-5-year-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/through-the-eyes-of-my-soon-to-be-5-year-old/</guid>
      <description>When my oldest doesn’t take a nap, I am often looking for creative ways for him to play quietly while the girls sleep and I do “whatever I do” during nap time. Often time he plays quietly in his nap room (I separate the kids during nap time so they aren’t sleeping in the same room) or will play a computer game. Some days, however, I give him the point and shoot and let him have fun with his artistic side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T.G.I.F.</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t.g.i.f./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t.g.i.f./</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;It&amp;rsquo;s Friday night/And the mood is right/Gonna have some fun/Show you how it&amp;rsquo;s done, TGIF..&amp;quot;
Remember those days? Nothing better topped off a hard week of going to school and talking on the phone like a little Full House, Family Matters, and Perfect Strangers. T.G.I.F.
If ever there was a week that needed an end, this week here at the circus, was it.
What with puke, and then puke, then a missed gymnastics performance due to puke, and then missing your best friends birthday party thanks to your sisters puke, followed by more puke, then a power outage, puke, snow, still more puke, then Daddy away on a business trip, his homecoming strangely enough followed the next morning by still more puke…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Circus Hodgepodge</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-circus-hodgepodge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2009 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-circus-hodgepodge/</guid>
      <description>I have been going non stop the past several days. Friends over for dinner, going to other friends homes for dinner, attending a party, hosting a surprise party…it has been social function after social function for 5 days straight. I have enjoyed each experience greatly, but I am an introvert and after spending time with people I need time alone to recharge. I have one more event tonight (a MOPS Family Fun Night at our church…being as I am the coordinator, I need to be there and be fun).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Me!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 04:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-me/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Not Me! Monday! This blog carnival was created by MckMama. You can head over to her blog to read what she and everyone else have not been doing this week.
While I was posting about my true love story each day last week, a whole circus load of activity was going on around here.
I did not…
 put my kids to bed without having them brush their teeth because we got home late from a church meeting and I was trying to rush the bedtime routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Communism Began</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-communism-began/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 05:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-communism-began/</guid>
      <description>We have a few daily battles here at the circus which I have to mediate carefully. One involves who buckled their top straps first in the car seat and the other is over who gets to eat off of the coveted plate at meal time. I made the innocent mistake of purchasing three different animal face plates last year at Target. I also bought some basic color plates as well. I was careful to make sure I got red and purple (my son and daughter’s favorite colors as well as 2 others since they baby didn’t yet have an opinion on colors and it was nice to have extras for when friends are visiting).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where’s My Shoe??</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wheres-my-shoe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wheres-my-shoe/</guid>
      <description>I often don’t bother scrambling around the house looking for shoes before heading out the door. We give a good attempt, but if we’re running late, I bank on the fact that we’ll be able to find a pair in the van.
One afternoon when my husband asked where to find my daughter’s shoe and I told him, these are what he found on the floor of our van (and believe it or not, there are more that just didn’t fit into the shot).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She’s lucky!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shes-lucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shes-lucky/</guid>
      <description>Lucky for Maggie today is her special day, otherwise, I don’t think I’d have been so nice about finding this on my couch cushions today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
