<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sports on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sports on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 11:51:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A New Sport for the Circus Fam</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-sport-for-the-circus-fam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-sport-for-the-circus-fam/</guid>
      <description>As a mom, there are several roles I play in the lives of my children. One of my favorite roles is that of cheer leader. I truly enjoy watching them compete/perform in whatever activity they are involved in and cheering them on as they do so. Yes, that’s right. I am that Mom you hear above the crowd cheering and squealing. This fall my son began a new sport. After years of wanting to try martial arts, he started Brazilian Jiu Jitsu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proud Momma</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proud-momma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proud-momma/</guid>
      <description>My girls had their Mini Olympics Show yesterday afternoon and I gotta tell you, I was one proud Momma as I watched them perform. Their class did a floor routine (which was super cute to watch) and then each girl had a chance to perform on the bars, trampoline, and tumble track. 


The event concluded with a trip to the medal stand for each girl and then the opportunity to pose for pictures afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Call it Crazy…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</guid>
      <description>This spring I have 3 kids in sports. On 3 different teams. This in addition to the girls both taking gymnastics twice a week and Cub Scouts.
We are busy, busy, busy with games and practices most every night… some nights we’re even double booked.
Many people look at my schedule and call me crazy. Why do you do this to yourself?
The answer is, honestly, two fold. 1. We love it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
