<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gingerbread house on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/gingerbread-house/</link>
    <description>Recent content in gingerbread house on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/gingerbread-house/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fun in Va</title>
      <link>/posts/fun-in-va/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/fun-in-va/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I escaped down to VA for just shy of 24 hours to spend some time with my SIL and her family. I adore Scott’s sister so a visit to her house was a bright spot in our week. We arrived in the early afternoon with time for me to take the 4 boys to the park while Aunt Karen took the girls to run a few errands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Best House Yet</title>
      <link>/posts/our-best-house-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-best-house-yet/</guid>
      <description>We decorated our gingerbread house this weekend…before Christmas this year—astonishing, I know.
The big 3 had a fabulous time.


Unfortunately, our youngest found the experience quite confusing and a tad frustrating. “Why, oh why, aren’t they letting me eat that candy?”

I might have snuck the lil guy a few pieces of candy while they were busy working.


The kids were quite proud of their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Said Gingerbread Houses Were For Christmas?</title>
      <link>/posts/who-said-gingerbread-houses-were-for-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/who-said-gingerbread-houses-were-for-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Much like the decorating of the pumpkin, the constructing of the gingerbread house didn’t happen according to the traditional time line. We here at the circus like to do things in our own time, thank you very much!
I mentioned before that this year I decided to go with the kit over baking from scratch. I bought the kit in early December and kept waiting for that evening when we were all home and not already busy with something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gingerbread Real Estate</title>
      <link>/posts/gingerbread-real-estate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2008 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gingerbread-real-estate/</guid>
      <description>My first memories of making a gingerbread house are at my high school friend Katie&amp;rsquo;s birthday party. It became a tradition. Each year her mom would bake the houses and make the icing and supply all the candy. We&amp;rsquo;d all come over for her birthday in December to decorate our houses. It was a ton of fun! We&amp;rsquo;d sit and talk, sneak candy and decorate our houses. I believe we made an all night affair out of it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
