<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About Me on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/about-me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About Me on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 06:39:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/about-me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Secret Ambition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-secret-ambition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 06:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-secret-ambition/</guid>
      <description>I’ve had a few shows over the past 10 years, that I’ve really loved. You know the ones where you connect personally with the characters in a manner some might find unhealthy? But, if I had to pick one, as my favorite (I’d probably kick and scream begging you to not make me limit it to just one) But, if I had to pick one, than I’d probably say it was Alias.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banner Week</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/banner-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/banner-week/</guid>
      <description>Exciting things are happening round the circus parts this week and it’s only Tuesday!!
Sunday, I ran a half marathon with my FIL. My friend, who had to run a half marathon in order to see me in real life, also ran but she was so stinking fast that I am glad I caught her in line for the potty before the race, b/c there was no seeing her after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Switch to the Dark Side</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-switch-to-the-dark-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-switch-to-the-dark-side/</guid>
      <description>It began innocently enough. It kind of drew me in with its rich, sweet aroma. For years I’d enjoy the hint of the flavor… in mud pies or Frappuccino&amp;rsquo;s…even an occasional cappuccino. But I wasn’t quite ready to sell out and drink a cup of joe for breakfast on a regular occasion. Then I went to our annual Labor Day getaway. Which, in addition to being a house full of my closest life long friends and their chillin’, was also a house full of serious coffee drinkers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little Bit of This and A Little Bit of That</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-little-bit-of-this-and-a-little-bit-of-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-little-bit-of-this-and-a-little-bit-of-that/</guid>
      <description>Few random thoughts to share with you, my dear readers… consider it some random musings or a brain dump, or catching up with an old friend you haven’t visited with for awhile, none the less, here’s my bulleted list of things which don’t quite make for a post on their own….
*I recently made the wonderful discovery of sharp Monterey Jack cheese. I’ve seen it mixed with cheddar in bags at the store, and knew you could put it in tacos or what not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet Another Reason Why I Won’t Be Teaching The Kids to Drive</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/yet-another-reason-why-i-wont-be-teaching-the-kids-to-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 18:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/yet-another-reason-why-i-wont-be-teaching-the-kids-to-drive/</guid>
      <description>I seriously stink at parking. (Not parallel parking. I’ve got a secret for that. I never do it. Ever. Yes, I will walk twice as far when parking downtown to avoid parallel parking on the street). But, my struggle is with the ol’ pull in parking lots. More specifically, backing out of said spots. I’ve been known to wait around in my car for the car beside me or in front of me to leave so I can get out of my spot b/c I parked too close to the line and can’t get out without damaging one of our cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Really, I did…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-really-i-did/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-really-i-did/</guid>
      <description>As I’ve returned to the classroom these past few weeks (though in a very different atmosphere), I can’t help but reflect on my years of teaching prior to becoming a stay at home mom. I was blessed to teach for 3 years at a small, Christian school. I learned a lot and grew from the experience. I honestly think it shaped the way I parent today.
That being said, I can’t help but reflect on the single.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Age</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/old-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/old-age/</guid>
      <description>A strange thing has happened to me in my ripe, “old” age. Since turning thirty I have discovered my taste buds are changing quite a bit. For years I have loved the smell of coffee. And while I do enjoy a cappuccino or especially a good frappuchino, an actual cup of coffee was too strong for my liking. However, I enjoyed the smell so much, I once begged my husband to drink it in the morning, just so we could fill our home with its rich aroma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One Where My Cell Phone Sends My Son Running Out of the House in Fear</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-one-where-my-cell-phone-sends-my-son-running-out-of-the-house-infear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-one-where-my-cell-phone-sends-my-son-running-out-of-the-house-infear/</guid>
      <description>I am an old fashioned girl. If you want to get a hold of me, your best bet is calling my land line. Yes, we have an actual land line (b/c my cell phone is typically buried at the bottom of my purse and the battery is quite often dead).
My cell plan is simply that - a cell phone. While I can send and receive texts it costs a pretty penny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One Where I Go To Work For Marvel</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-one-where-i-go-to-work-for-marvel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-one-where-i-go-to-work-for-marvel/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I didn’t now Bruce Banner from Bruce Wayne and I couldn’t have named an X-Man to save my life. Since my son’s Spiderman party, I’ve been studying up. Doing some self inflicted homework. In the past month I have seen all 3 Spiderman Movies, The Incredible Hulk, The Punisher, and the 3 X Men movies…and tomorrow Scott and I are going on a double date to see the new Wolverine movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Straddling the Line</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/straddling-the-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 05:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/straddling-the-line/</guid>
      <description>I am quickly approaching a new age bracket. The thirty somethings. It hit me rather squarely in the face yesterday when I looked into a women’s Bible study at a nearby church. I got so excited when I found a Beth Moore study meeting at a church less than 5 minutes from my house. I quickly e-mailed an acquaintance from that church before even reading the small print. The study I mentioned to her was for 18-30 year old women, she replied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Non Athletic Team</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-non-athletic-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2009 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-non-athletic-team/</guid>
      <description>I am not an athlete. Those of you blog readers who knew me in high school can vouch for me on this. My position on the HS sport team was bench warmer, my role, “team encourager.” When my recent blog friend turned IRL friend accompanied me this weekend to pick up my runners pack for the Pittsburgh Half Marathon and called me athletic, I almost laughed in her face.
Me athletic?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ambitious or Crazy?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ambitious-or-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ambitious-or-crazy/</guid>
      <description>We made it. And more amazingly than that. So did our 5 suitcases, pack-n-play, and 3 car seats! We had a very gracious man checking us in who gave us time to sort our bags and let one slide which was slightly over the 50lb limit. Then we were blessed when we went to the car rental agency and got a stow and go van (which will make carting our 5 suitcases around much easier) and Scott was somehow able to talk them into a price several hundred dollars cheaper than the estimate we had gotten online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Year Ago Today…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-year-ago-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 00:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-year-ago-today/</guid>
      <description>One year ago today I entered into this crazy blogging world. My initial post was very short and my commenter&amp;rsquo;s were only IRL friends and family. For awhile I only received comments from my mom, my mother in law or one of my two sisters in law. Now I have by no means “made it” in the blogging world. If anything, I have learned that there are a gazillion mommy bloggers out there with cute kids and tales to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Its PARTY time!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-party-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-party-time/</guid>
      <description>[5 Minutes for Mom] (http://www.5minutesformom.com)is hosting their annual blog party and this year I am joining in the fun! So kick your shoes off, change in to some comfy pants and make yourself at home, because the best thing about a blog party is you can join in the fun from the comfort of your couch!
I’ve been blogging for almost a year now. What started as a fulfillment of my new years resolution, has grown into a means of making new friends and reconnecting with old ones as I share my circus life as a wife and stay at home mom of three active preschoolers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little Help from My Friends</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-little-help-from-my-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-little-help-from-my-friends/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday when I was taking a picture of my son with his “baby” to post on the blog, he asked what I was going to do with the picture.  Son: “Are you going to send it away to people?”
Me: No, I’m just putting it on my blog. Son: But I want this picture for my scrapbook.
Me: That’s fine, you can still have the picture, they’re not taking it, just looking at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symptoms of Watching 24 Before Bed</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/symptoms-of-watching-24-before-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/symptoms-of-watching-24-before-bed/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I enjoy watching those “thrill drama series” such as 24, Alias, Heroes… I can remember when we would watch Alias, I would often have dreams where I would save the day with my mean back side kick and my “kickn” purple air. Ya, if only…
Well this morning I woke up and told Scott I had the strangest dream. In part of it we were going away for our honeymoon only it wasn’t really because we already had the kids and we were staying in this hotel like room underground in my parents yard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bit Mixed Up</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-bit-mixed-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-bit-mixed-up/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever been singing along to a song in front of your friends when you learn that the lyrics you thought you knew weren’t quite right?
I can remember in high school singing along to Amy Grant’s “Baby Baby” and when she says, “Baby Baby, I’m taken with the notion to love you with the sweetest of devotion” I instead belted out “love you with the sweetest talk of ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Think I May Have a Problem…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-think-i-may-have-a-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 04:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-think-i-may-have-a-problem/</guid>
      <description>I had a dream last night that I went to the movies and when it was my turn to order the tickets, I couldn’t remember the name of the movie we wanted to see. For some reason they didn’t list them on the wall behind the register like normal. I tried to call someone for help, but suddenly my phone had been replaced with a different phone and every time I hit the buttons for my contact list, it took me to some funky screen and I couldn’t find anyone’s number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Back, and Looking Ahead...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/looking-back-and-looking-ahead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/looking-back-and-looking-ahead/</guid>
      <description>2008 was a good year at the Circus.
In February, I was blessed with a new niece. You wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have known this though because I didn&amp;rsquo;t begin blogging until the end of March. The spring was also filled with fun family activities like going to a real circus, celebrating Easter, and watching the Blue Angels. Summer held a trip to the beach, patriotic celebrations, my birthday, camping, sailboat races, and a reunion with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Stopped Listening To Country Music</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/why-i-stopped-listening-to-country-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/why-i-stopped-listening-to-country-music/</guid>
      <description>Isn&amp;rsquo;t it amazing how something so simple can trigger a memory so deep? You hear a song from your past and suddenly you can feel all those emotions and feelings you felt so long ago&amp;hellip;it&amp;rsquo;s like it just propels you back in time.
Yea&amp;hellip; Faith Hill does that to me.
When Scott and I were dating in college, I spent one memorable Thanksgiving at his family&amp;rsquo;s home. That evening we were sitting around the dining room table playing Rummikub when I remembered that the Faith Hill TV special was on that evening, and I commented on that fact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Those Who Care...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/for-those-who-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/for-those-who-care/</guid>
      <description>I am one happy girl tonight.
Why, you ask?
** The Steelers beat the Ravens **&amp;hellip; and if that wasn&amp;rsquo;t reason enough to rejoice, doing so clinched them a spot in the play offs AND a first round bye.
I had a realization about myself while watching the game though. I don&amp;rsquo;t really enjoy watching the game unless we are winning. Really. I was literally sick to my stomach with worry for much of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Going Head to Head</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-going-head-to-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-going-head-to-head/</guid>
      <description>Update: This round of playoffs takes two weeks. So the winner is decided by totaling the points scored both weeks, and whoever scored the most points goes on to the championship round. Looks like a close one&amp;hellip;Scott scored 80 and I had 76. There is def still time for me to pull out a victory!!
There are 10 teams on our fantasy football league this year. Four teams make it to play offs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go NAVY beat Army</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/go-navy-beat-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2008 06:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/go-navy-beat-army/</guid>
      <description>My father in law graduated from the Naval Academy, so I became a Navy fan by marriage. And the biggest game of the year for them is the Army/Navy game.
Knowing this, you might better appreciate the conversation I had with my son yesterday&amp;hellip;
 Mom: Tomorrow is the Army/Navy football game
Son: Army doesn&amp;rsquo;t play football, they fight bad guys
Hmmm see he&amp;rsquo;s seen Navy football games with his Dad and Pop, and all he knows about the Army is that his Uncle Jim and our cousin Joel are in the Army and they fight bad guys&amp;hellip;better clear up this misconception before he goes around saying Navy plays football and Army fights bad guys&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swept Away in Dream Land...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/swept-away-in-dream-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/swept-away-in-dream-land/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I stumbled across this article in Wonder Magazine.
My husband and I have been doing lots of talking and planning regarding our family&amp;rsquo;s future&amp;hellip; Do we want a fourth child or are we content with three? Do we want to send our son to public school next year or will we home school? Do we start saving now so we have the option of sending the kids to private school for Middle or High School?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crank Up the Christmas Music!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/crank-up-the-christmas-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/crank-up-the-christmas-music/</guid>
      <description>At our house, the rule is No Christmas anything until after Thanksgiving. My hubby is pretty strict about this&amp;hellip;He even scolded my grandma on Thanksgiving for wearing a Christmas sweater.
But, come the day after Thanksgiving you better believe we are cranking those yuletide carols as loud as we can as we head out for some good ol&#39; fashioned Black Friday Shopping!
I LOVE CHRISTMAS!! It is by far my most favorite holiday of all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because I Can</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/because-i-can/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/because-i-can/</guid>
      <description>I voted today. For some reason this year more than any other, I was grateful for the opportunity to let my voice be heard. Often I am rather cynical about it, voting because I know it is the right thing to do but wondering &amp;ldquo;why bother&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Does my vote really matter anyway?&amp;rdquo;
But today I felt convicted.
There was a time in American history when woman couldn&amp;rsquo;t vote and there are many countries today where women still can&amp;rsquo;t vote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday Monday</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/monday-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 10:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/monday-monday/</guid>
      <description>cue song from Mamas and Papas
I do not heart Mondays. AT.ALL. And my reasons why are numerous, so numerous, I&amp;rsquo;ve composed a list for you.
 Scott is back to work and after having him home for 2 days, I miss him. LOTS. Because he is truly my best friend and the house is lonely with him gone. I know we are only 29 but can I just tell you I look forward to retirement when we can spend all day every day just being together&amp;hellip; don&amp;rsquo;t even care what it is we are doing, just that we won&amp;rsquo;t be a part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time to Meet the Circus Crew</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-time-to-meet-the-circus-crew/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-time-to-meet-the-circus-crew/</guid>
      <description>I am all about keeping it real, folks. And Jessica at Farm Fresh Iowa has a carnival called, It&amp;rsquo;s Real Life which I totally love because it&amp;rsquo;s all about showing the real you. This week the assignment is to create a real life video introducing yourself to the blogging world.
I wish I could tell you that we staged the video because I just thought it would be so funny for you to see my kids fighting with each other while I am videoing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of a Baby</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-power-of-a-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 18:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-power-of-a-baby/</guid>
      <description>What is it about baby animals that pull at a Mommy&amp;rsquo;s heart and make a genuine Cruella Deville like myself yearn to take them home? Seriously, I am not an animal person. You won&amp;rsquo;t catch me bending down to pet your dog, ever. And yet I found myself asking my husband if we could bring a goat home because they were &amp;ldquo;so cute&amp;rdquo;. Really they were&amp;hellip; a mere 4 weeks old&amp;hellip;look at them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just an Ordinary Day of Circus Life</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-an-ordinary-day-of-circus-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-an-ordinary-day-of-circus-life/</guid>
      <description>Jessica over at Farm Fresh Iowa is sponsoring another It&amp;rsquo;s Real Life carnival this week. The assignment this time is to do a post with a photo tour of &amp;ldquo;an ordinary day.&amp;rdquo; So, step right up and come see an ordinary day in the life at the circus&amp;hellip;
Our day begins here typically around 7 am or shortly after. My son is usually the first to wake, followed quickly by our middle child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That much anticipated Weekend Review</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/that-much-anticipated-weekend-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 20:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/that-much-anticipated-weekend-review/</guid>
      <description>Yea, so let me explain my absence&amp;hellip;
I must confess Friday night was more laziness than anything else, as I started a post, still have it in my draft, but the creative juices weren&amp;rsquo;t flowing like I wanted so I opted to read a book and go to bed early (as in before midnight) to get ready for my BIG morning&amp;hellip;

I ran in the Baltimore Half Marathon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mommy&#39;s Leaving on a Jet Plane!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mommys-leaving-on-a-jet-plane/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mommys-leaving-on-a-jet-plane/</guid>
      <description>That&amp;rsquo;s right folks, tomorrow Mommy is out of here till Sunday morning. I&amp;rsquo;m packing my bags and flying to Dallas for the MOPS Convention. And while I am really excited at the opportunity to grow as I listen to great speakers and attend workshops, I am also sad to be away from my hubby and kiddos for almost 3 full days. I know from past experience that when I get there I will have a great time as I am listening to live music, eating dinner out with my friends (experiencing uninterrupted adult conversations for 9 meals), and learning from dynamic speakers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because I needed one more reason to spend time online...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/because-i-needed-one-more-reason-to-spend-time-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/because-i-needed-one-more-reason-to-spend-time-online/</guid>
      <description>Even though the Steelers don&amp;rsquo;t play until Sunday afternoon, football season kicked off in our house last night. We had our Live Draft for our Fantasy Football League last night.
The kids were in bed a half hour before their bed time tonight with no story or teeth brushing as we had a 7:45 draft time and were both scurrying to research and formulate our plans right up until it started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two of My Favorite Things</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/two-of-my-favorite-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/two-of-my-favorite-things/</guid>
      <description>Updated with new picture from today below
Today I get to celebrate two of my favorite things&amp;hellip;
Chick-Fil-A and Football. :-)
Today, Chick-Fil-A is giving away their new chicken strips (which, by the way, are delicious, and my hubby and my new fav menu item) to anyone who visits their store wearing a football logo. Check it out here for more details.
You better believe that all 5 of us will be sporting our Steelers pride at Chick-Fil-A today when we stop for lunch on our way back from our annual Labor Day get together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Struck</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/star-struck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/star-struck/</guid>
      <description>My hubby and I are huge Pittsburgh Steelers fans. I was born a Steelers fan. My husband&amp;rsquo;s allegiance was born in college when he began faithfully watching the home team in Western, PA. There&amp;rsquo;s no way to distinguish who is more devoted now, we are both hard core. Living in Ravens territory is tough. We watch every game televised here, head to Glory Days for big games that aren&amp;rsquo;t televised, make a few treks to my parents house in PA, read the play by plays online, listen on the radio&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facing One of my Biggest Fears</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/facing-one-of-my-biggest-fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/facing-one-of-my-biggest-fears/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t like heights. Never have, but my trip to Mexico definitely didn&amp;rsquo;t help.
When I was pregnant with my son I developed an irrational fear of driving. I was driving over a bridge one day and felt light headed, which triggered a complete panic attack. After that I had trouble driving the 5 miles to work each day. My dear husband and sympathetic friends taxied me around for a few months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talkin bout the REAL thing!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/talkin-bout-the-real-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/talkin-bout-the-real-thing/</guid>
      <description>Some may call it a sickness.
Others may think of me more as a loyalist.
It all stems back to an experience I had as a middle schooler.
Who knew that a trip to the grocery store could have such a lasting impact on a girl?
I was shopping with my mom one day when I was an early teen and they were conducting a blind taste test for Coke and Pepsi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks for the Advice</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thanks-for-the-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thanks-for-the-advice/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to all of you that wrote with song suggestions last weekend to help me Pump it Up as I ran 7 miles on Sunday. Some of you asked me to let you know which songs I picked so here goes&amp;hellip;
 Bootylicious-Destiny&amp;rsquo;s Child (b/c when I run I think about looking good for my hubby ) Can&amp;rsquo;t Get Next to You&amp;hellip; Temptations (b/c KP you were right I love the oldies so I went with some Temptations, picked the song b/c I liked to imagine I was running soooo fast no one could get next to me&amp;hellip; ha ha) Unbelievable-EMF (You were right StellaG this song totally brought me back to middle school) Getting Jiggy Wit It&amp;ndash; Will Smith ( b/c I really like Will Smith and it is just so fun) MMMBop-Hanson Bros (again thanks to Stella for a trip down memory lane) Straight Up- Paula Abdul (took KP&amp;rsquo;s advice and went for an 80s&amp;ndash;maybe it is early 90s not sure&amp;hellip; tune I remember singing out loud in the old days&amp;hellip; ya know before American Idol)   This wasn&amp;rsquo;t the only music I download on my MP3 player though&amp;hellip; my friend Megh had made me a mix CD for Christmas of fun, upbeat Christian songs&amp;hellip; I took them and combined them with my 6 new tunes for a fabulous running soundtrack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Thought I Couldn&#39;t Wait till the Weekend to Share</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-thought-i-couldnt-wait-till-the-weekend-to-share/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 18:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-thought-i-couldnt-wait-till-the-weekend-to-share/</guid>
      <description>The Lord convicted me of something this morning at church and I had the urge to share it here on my blog, which is incredibly ironic when you read what it is I&amp;rsquo;m convicted about. Our pastor spoke to us about idols. He shared an idol that he frequently struggles with worshipping in place of God. See an idol doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be an object. It isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily a little gold man that you bow to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sunday Game of Tag (or two)</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-sunday-game-of-tag-or-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-sunday-game-of-tag-or-two/</guid>
      <description>It seems the blogging world loves to play a good game of tag. I&amp;rsquo;ve received two tags in the past few weeks. So, for those of you looking for some Sunday reading here is way more than you could possibly want to know about little ol&#39; me!!

 Busy Mamas tagged me over a week ago with this Meme&amp;hellip; (Sorry Busy Mamas for taking so long to respond)!
Think back on the last 15 years of your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Need Some Advice People</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-need-some-advice-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 05:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-need-some-advice-people/</guid>
      <description>Thanks so much for your encouragement on Monday. I am happy to say that on Tuesday I ran 6 miles!! My dear husband has given me the gift of 6 songs to download to my MP3 player as an encouragement for completing this goal and to help me as I strive to make it the next 4 miles in the next 3 weeks. Here&amp;rsquo;s where you come in&amp;hellip;
I need your suggestions for great running songs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Agony of Defeat</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-agony-of-defeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-agony-of-defeat/</guid>
      <description>I had a great post written &amp;quot;in my head&amp;quot; Saturday morning. I was setting off to do a 6 mile run. It would have been the longest run I had ever done in my life. Before training for the Annapolis 10 Mile that I am working towards at the end of the summer, the farthest I had run was a 5K (3.1 miles) So, this would have been about twice that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess For A Day</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/princess-for-a-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 20:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/princess-for-a-day/</guid>
      <description>This week I celebrated my birthday. As I mentioned yesterday, I love birthdays. Even though I am a &amp;quot;grown up&amp;quot; now and I am not supposed to care about my birthday, I do. A lot. I don&amp;rsquo;t just look forward to it. I count down the weeks and days until it arrives. When I was a kid I used to have my parents wake me up to say Happy Birthday at the exact minute I was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Those Special Days</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/remembering-those-special-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/remembering-those-special-days/</guid>
      <description>Wanna know how to get your husband to remember your birthday, anniversary, Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day, or other special occasion? I have a novel idea for you, that has worked well for me these past 7 years. Tell him!
My husband is horrible with calendars. His mind just simply doesn&amp;rsquo;t work that way. Quiz him on the date of my birthday and, given some time to think, he will probably get it. Ask him how far away that is and he will have no clue (He would need time to figure out which month we were in first).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve been tagged again!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ive-been-tagged-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ive-been-tagged-again/</guid>
      <description>Megan tagged me with this a little over a week ago, and I thought it was past time to play along. So, in case you didn&amp;rsquo;t learn enough about me on my 100th post &amp;hellip; here&amp;rsquo;s more!!
_
_
1) What was I doing 10 years ago?
It was the summer after my freshman year of college. My parents moved to PA so I was spending the summer with them and preparing to transfer from Towson University to Slippery Rock Univeristy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Know It&#39;s Bad When...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-know-its-bad-when/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2008 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-know-its-bad-when/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;your son won&amp;rsquo;t sit on your lap because your legs are &amp;ldquo;too spiky.&amp;rdquo;
My four year old son told me yesterday that my legs &amp;ldquo;are prickly like a cactus.&amp;rdquo;
You better believe I made sure to get up early enough to shave my legs before leaving for church this morning. They are silky smooth now (a fact that my son and my husband are both glad about).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clearly I Don&#39;t Wear Enough Bling</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/clearly-i-dont-wear-enough-bling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/clearly-i-dont-wear-enough-bling/</guid>
      <description>I was shopping at BJ&amp;rsquo;s the other day with the kids when we passed the jewelry counter.
My son asked, &amp;quot;Why is there jewelry at BJ&amp;rsquo;s?&amp;quot;
I responded, &amp;quot;So people can buy it.&amp;quot;
He then said, &amp;quot;Yea&amp;hellip; I guess if they were getting married and didn&amp;rsquo;t have a ring they could come here.&amp;quot;
Hmmm&amp;hellip;. clearly this Mommy doesn&amp;rsquo;t wear much jewelry, since my son thinks wedding rings are the only kind of jewelry one wears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping It Real</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-it-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-it-real/</guid>
      <description>Our pastor has been talking a lot lately about being transparent. As a Christian I too often present the world with a false squeaky clean image that gives the appearance that I think am perfect. Of course, everyone knows that no one is perfect so, when they see me ACTING perfect they know it is a false charade. What kind of credibility does that bring? No, I am far from perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 100th Post!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-100th-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-100th-post/</guid>
      <description>It’s my 100 th post, so I thought I’d post a hundred things about myself…
 I love the smell of play dough. I like to have a night light on in our room at night. When I am baking cookies I tend to eat at least half of the dough. I hate vanilla ice cream. I also don’t like cake, especially chocolate cake. So, you don’t think I am crazy, I do have a weakness for ice cream, especially hand scooped, particularly chocolate peanut butter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Running</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-running/</guid>
      <description>Last week I registered for a 10 mile run at the end of August. For over a year now I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to do this. I ran a 5K for the first time when my son was a year old. I ran two more when my 2 year old was 6 mths old. Until last Tuesday, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t run since.
I waited through one of the mildest winter and spring seasons I&amp;rsquo;ve seen here and decided to start running during the week of record breaking heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did this happen??</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-did-this-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-did-this-happen/</guid>
      <description>I fear I have become a gadget person. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how or when it happened, but recently I have noticed the signs. Two weeks ago when on my date night with hubby, we had some extra time after our Toys R Us date, so I asked if we could run in the mall to look at the new iphone at the apple store. Yes, you read that correctly. I asked my husband if we could go look at technological equipment that I knew we couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford and weren&amp;rsquo;t going to buy, just b/c I wanted to play with one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
