<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>seasons on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/seasons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in seasons on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 11:36:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/seasons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blueberries!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/blueberries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/blueberries/</guid>
      <description>I love, LOVE picking fruit with the kiddos. Apple picking in the fall and strawberry picking in the spring are two of my favorite annual excursions with them. I was delighted when I found out that a family from our tutorial owns a pick your own blueberry patch. The younger three and I went Monday morning while my oldest was a day camp with the cub scouts. 
I hope to go back with all four of them and really stock up on some berries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Flip Side</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-flip-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-flip-side/</guid>
      <description>The thing that we most fell in love with when we first saw our new house was the back yard. We loved, LOVED the big, private back yard.
Clearly, it was not the fall when we had our love at first sight experience.

We spent the entire day tackling that beloved backyard.

Thankfully, we also made time for a little fun in the leaves.

Leaves can provide a great back drop for some smiley pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Fun 2011</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fall-fun-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fall-fun-2011/</guid>
      <description>If we gotta rake and bag all these leaves, we may as well take advantage of the seasonal photo op they provide first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phil, You Couldn’t Have Been MORE wrong</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/phil-you-couldnt-have-been-more-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/phil-you-couldnt-have-been-more-wrong/</guid>
      <description>March in Maryland is always fickle. Short sleeves one day and winter coats the next.
You always know when the first “jacket less” day arrives, that it is just a tease. And try as you may to simply embrace and enjoy it, the next day when you have to scramble for your winter coat and hat, it is always a bit disappointing.
Having lived in Maryland for most of my life, I know this and expect it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign of the Season</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sign-of-the-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sign-of-the-season/</guid>
      <description>You know warm days are once again upon us, when you stumble across your bathroom sink looking like this. 
Probably had something to do with the hours my kids spent digging in the dirt in our backyard this afternoon.
 While they didn’t quite make it to China, they were thrilled to dig down to clay.  I love spring… even with the rings round my tub and the dirt deposits left in my sinks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Thoughts on Spring</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/random-thoughts-on-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/random-thoughts-on-spring/</guid>
      <description>Guess what the kids and I spotted outside this afternoon?  Crocuses!!! Oh, how I love those little purple blooms… they are the signal to me that spring is around the corner! And as much as I have loved, (and truly, I know I whined that one day, but really, I have loved this record breaking snowy winter), but I am excited for spring.
And I am really excited… I am looking forward to taking walks with the kids in the evenings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
