<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>baby on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/baby/</link>
    <description>Recent content in baby on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 19:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/baby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>He Spoils Us</title>
      <link>/posts/he-spoils-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/he-spoils-us/</guid>
      <description>Time and time again our fourth child has blown us away with his easy going, flexible, happy-go-lucky approach to life. It has made the transition to a family of 6, for this family on-the-go, SO MUCH easier—a fact I am truly, truly grateful for.
This weekend, he really went above and beyond our expectations though.
Not only did he fall asleep in the tent both nights, while the rest of us were out at the camp fire, but he even napped in the tent Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast with the Piglets</title>
      <link>/posts/breakfast-with-the-piglets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/breakfast-with-the-piglets/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I had a unique opportunity this morning to feed some orphaned baby piglets. The Momma Pig died at childbirth and the farmers were looking for extra hands to give bottles to the piglets. I literally leaped at the opportunity. And I am so glad that I did! What a delightful way to spend our morning!




Even my youngest had fun with the piglets…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning Back Time</title>
      <link>/posts/turning-back-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/turning-back-time/</guid>
      <description>Ya know that feeling you get when you look at your kids and you just wanna freeze time? You don’t want them to grow up, not one bit, so you just try your best to hold on to the moments while you can.
Well, we figured out a way to freeze time here at the circus…just a little…

Our littlest crew member turned one earlier this month. Not sure how that year flew by so fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do ya Notice?</title>
      <link>/posts/what-do-ya-notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/what-do-ya-notice/</guid>
      <description>Notice anything different about his smile?

Take a closer look…

See it on the bottom right? Say goodbye to his cute toothless smile.
My baby got his first tooth!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Will Win??</title>
      <link>/posts/who-will-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/who-will-win/</guid>
      <description>There are many familiar and epic battles out there. At the circus, I am often subject to reading, watching, and even role playing in such battles over good and evil.
Darth Vader and Luke Skywalker fighting for the future of the galaxy.
Spiderman and Doctor Octopus dueling over the city of New York.
Optimus Prime and the autobots verses Megatron and the decepticons in their fierce battle over the fate of earth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
