<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>zoo on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/zoo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in zoo on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 02:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/zoo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our Cloud Sure Had a Silver Lining Today</title>
      <link>/posts/our-cloud-sure-had-a-silver-lining-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 02:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-cloud-sure-had-a-silver-lining-today/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a few years since we have been to the zoo, and our youngest has been eager to go and see real animals up close. He was super excited about the lions and tigers. He’s been asking for several months if we could go to the zoo. I thought fall would be a nice time as it wouldn’t be too hot. I was hopeful we could see animals being more active than in the summer months that we typically visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Half Life Anniversary Excursion</title>
      <link>/posts/our-half-life-anniversary-excursion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 06:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-half-life-anniversary-excursion/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I started dating our senior year of high school, when we were both 17. A few years ago we were out for an anniversary date and realized that we were approaching the point in our life when we would have been together as much of our life as we weren’t together. We decided we wanted to celebrate such a momentous occasion and so we (and by we, I really mean Scott) calculated out when exactly that would be… our dates are different since we don’t share the same birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ending the Year on a Wild Note</title>
      <link>/posts/ending-the-year-on-a-wild-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ending-the-year-on-a-wild-note/</guid>
      <description>Since we were blessed with yet another mild December day on the 31st, we decided to take advantage of the time off, unseasonably warm weather, and the last day of our pass for a family fun afternoon at the zoo.  Make a mental note… for a really good visit to the zoo, try going on a mild day in the off season, shortly before closing time… hardly any people were there and the animals were quite active.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up Close and Personal</title>
      <link>/posts/up-close-and-personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/up-close-and-personal/</guid>
      <description>Last week we took the kids to the local zoo. We have tried to go once a year for the past several years. We go in part b/c we want to give the kids a chance to see the exotic animals up close. It’s so fun to watch their reactions. But, I’ll be honest, we also go b/c I love to see the animals up close! It is amazing and awe inspiring and I don’t think I could ever tire of it!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
