<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chick-Fil-A on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/chick-fil-a/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chick-Fil-A on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 19:13:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/chick-fil-a/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Winner, Winner Chicken Dinner</title>
      <link>/posts/winner-winner-chicken-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/winner-winner-chicken-dinner/</guid>
      <description>Anyone who knows me, knows that I love Chick-Fil-A. So, when I found out that they were opening a new one in Pasadena AND they had a “Raving-Fan” contest on face book in which the winner would win a year of free Chick-Fil-A, I had to enter.
The contest: submit a photo of your favorite memory at Chick-Fil-A and explain it in 100 words or less.
My favorite memory at Chick-fil-A?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incase You Were Wondering…</title>
      <link>/posts/incase-you-were-wondering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/incase-you-were-wondering/</guid>
      <description>This would be why more than one of my children thought chicken came from cows…
 Cow Appreciation Day at Chick-Fil-A is a tradition here at the circus.
We start them young with our indoctrination!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two of My Favorite Things</title>
      <link>/posts/two-of-my-favorite-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/two-of-my-favorite-things/</guid>
      <description>Updated with new picture from today below
Today I get to celebrate two of my favorite things&amp;hellip;
Chick-Fil-A and Football. :-)
Today, Chick-Fil-A is giving away their new chicken strips (which, by the way, are delicious, and my hubby and my new fav menu item) to anyone who visits their store wearing a football logo. Check it out here for more details.
You better believe that all 5 of us will be sporting our Steelers pride at Chick-Fil-A today when we stop for lunch on our way back from our annual Labor Day get together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
