<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>family dinners on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/family-dinners/</link>
    <description>Recent content in family dinners on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 20:09:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/family-dinners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kicking off the Holidays with Family and SNOW</title>
      <link>/posts/kicking-off-the-holidays-with-family-and-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/kicking-off-the-holidays-with-family-and-snow/</guid>
      <description>Nothing like a back seat driver. Especially a 3 year old back seat driver.
At 1 am. On a Snow covered back country road.
[
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/IMG_1958.jpg)
As we slip slided around the roads approaching my parents the other night, I seriously thought we might end up in a ditch and all the while my 3 year old was WIDE awake and chattering non stop about all the snow. He kept saying, “Dad, don’t get in an accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One of My Favorite Things…</title>
      <link>/posts/one-of-my-favorite-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-of-my-favorite-things/</guid>
      <description>There are lots of things that I truly appreciate about our new house. Among the top is the location. This came as a surprise to many of our friends, because at first glance the location seems less than ideal. A large majority of our life is centered 20-25 minutes away from our house… our church, our tutorial, gymnastics, and many of our friends. However, one of the most important and integral parts of our family life is located a mere 2 miles away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to Once Again Roll that Beautiful Bean Footage</title>
      <link>/posts/time-to-once-again-roll-that-beautiful-bean-footage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 12:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/time-to-once-again-roll-that-beautiful-bean-footage/</guid>
      <description>One of my very first blog posts ever was on my children’s love of kidney beans. It is now 3 years later and my girls have moved on to baked beans. Seriously, the love my daughter has for baked beans can NOT be overstated. Last week I figured it was time to try the kidney beans out on number 4. (let the playgroup mocking begin).


What do you mean I shouldn’t eat too many at once?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Months Old Today</title>
      <link>/posts/9-months-old-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/9-months-old-today/</guid>
      <description>Look at those chubby hands stuffing his face

I seriously couldn’t stop clicking the camera

Oh, little man, you have captured your Momma’s heart</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Many Miles Can We Get Out of This? or Milking This One for ALL its Worth</title>
      <link>/posts/how-many-miles-can-we-get-out-of-this-or-milking-this-one-for-all-itsworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-many-miles-can-we-get-out-of-this-or-milking-this-one-for-all-itsworth/</guid>
      <description>Some of you may remember my post last December (as in 2009) in which I shared one of Scott’s moments of sheer brilliance at the dinner table. Well, I feel the need to tell you that 13 months later and my kids are STILL eating their vegetables to spite their Daddy. I am sure this says something of their character… for which we must spend some time rectifying, but meanwhile my mean spirited little children are eagerly gobbling up their vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Savoring Each Bite</title>
      <link>/posts/savoring-each-bite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/savoring-each-bite/</guid>
      <description>It became quite clear to us that our little man was ready to try solid foods when he started opening his mouth like a baby bird anytime we were eating with him on our lap. We couldn’t help but laugh when he started reaching out for Daddy’s fork, mouth wide open, just begging for a taste.

Here he is holding our Smores ingredients while on vacation… his poor pathetic face seems to be saying, “They aren’t even nice about it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Valentine’s Tradition</title>
      <link>/posts/our-valentines-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-valentines-tradition/</guid>
      <description>I know that many think Valentine’s day is just a day created by Hallmark. Others think it’s a cheesy holiday for saps. Say what you will, I’ll jump at a chance for a date night with my hubby. And I don’t mind a sweet card and some cinnamon heart candy either.
But, after having kids, Scott and I found it rather difficult to go out for Valentine’s day. Since we don’t hire babysitters, we typically rely on friends or grandparents for babysitting and you can’t ask another couple to babysit for you on Valentine’s Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Memories</title>
      <link>/posts/christmas-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/christmas-memories/</guid>
      <description>We have had a wonderful couple of days here at the circus celebrating Jesus’ birthday. We decided to spread the celebrating out over several days rather than cram it all into one day. On Christmas Eve we went to the Children’s service at our church at 4:30. Then we went to Boston Market for our now traditional Christmas Eve dinner before heading back to church for the candlelight service at 6:30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Is He Going With This?</title>
      <link>/posts/where-is-he-going-with-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 18:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/where-is-he-going-with-this/</guid>
      <description>My husband is a genius.
Pure genius, I tell you.
We were sitting around the table the other day at dinner. Nothing out of the ordinary. The kids were complaining about eating their green beans. Like I said, nothing unusual.
Then Scott asked my son, “Do you know why parents raise kids?”
“Because their fast.”
Pause…Confusion…
“No, not race, raise, as in, why do they have kids and help them grow up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Long?</title>
      <link>/posts/how-long/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 03:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-long/</guid>
      <description>Dinner time….the family all gathered around the table, enjoying a delicious meal, talking about the day, laughing and enjoying one another…statistics say that families that consistently eat dinner together tend to raise healthier, more well behaved children, then families that don’t. So, what are we doing wrong?
More often than not the Circus Family eats breakfast and dinner together as a family. More often than not our dinner “hour” is more like a dinner hour and a half.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
