<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weekend Thoughts on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/weekend-thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weekend Thoughts on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 10:49:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/weekend-thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blessed Assurance</title>
      <link>/posts/blessed-assurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blessed-assurance/</guid>
      <description>5 years ago this month, God took her home to heaven. Though the truth is, Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s/Dementia took Grandma from us long before then. At first she’d just forget what time we’d be leaving for church the next day or when we’d be eating dinner. Later she forgot her grandchildren, children, and eventually even her own identity. Bit by bit the disease took more of her. I remember walking into the care facility the weekend Scott and I had gotten engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Praying for my Kids</title>
      <link>/posts/praying-for-my-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/praying-for-my-kids/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago a woman from my church passed out these prayer cards written by Bob Hostetler to the ladies in our MOPS group. Each card had 31 Biblical Virtues to pray for your children, with verses included. I thought this was a great idea and instantly tucked it away inside my Bible.
Only to forget about it and lose track of it with all the other papers stuffed in there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Step Closer</title>
      <link>/posts/one-step-closer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2010 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-step-closer/</guid>
      <description>Since before each of my children were born, my hearts deepest desire has been for them to know the Lord Jesus as their Savior. My son has demonstrated to us numerous times through various conversations that he recognizes he is a sinner and Christ died on the cross to forgive his sins.  My girls have not come to that point yet, but this Easter season we got one step closer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergoing the Change</title>
      <link>/posts/undergoing-the-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/undergoing-the-change/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes the music in my car radio really serves as nothing more than background noise to the chattering or squabbling going on in the back seat and the to do lists and other random thoughts going on in my brain. One day though something about the lyrics caused me to take pause and listen. I turned the radio up and even though I’ve heard the song countless times before, I listened to it for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving Thanks for a Wonderful Year</title>
      <link>/posts/giving-thanks-for-a-wonderful-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/giving-thanks-for-a-wonderful-year/</guid>
      <description>As 2009 came to a close, we spent some time as a family discussing the highlights. It really was a wonderful year! I feel so blessed for the many opportunities for family fun that we had in the past year.
 In January Scott and I were able to go to a Steelers home AFC championship and watch them beat the Ravens and make it to the Super bowl. Shortly after we hosted a Super bowl party with our family and watched our beloved Steelers bring home a 6th Super bowl victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Since There’s No Place to Go…</title>
      <link>/posts/and-since-theres-no-place-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/and-since-theres-no-place-to-go/</guid>
      <description>Let it Snow, Let it Snow, Let it Snow!!!
Growing up and living in the midAtlantic region means that snow is something we are familiar with, but we don’t encounter on a regular basis. It’s not like we’re living in Houston and a dusting of snow occurs once a decade. But, it also isn’t unreasonable that I don’t go out and purchase snow suits for my kids every winter either. We can typically anticipate seeing snowfall at least once a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: That’s What It’s All About</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-thats-what-its-all-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-thats-what-its-all-about/</guid>
      <description>I am reposting this post from last year because, it’s still what it’s all about and I love reminding myself of that as often as possible.  That’s What It’s All About… December 20, 2008
in Weekend Thoughts
As we were getting ready to go to the tree lighting ceremony downtown my son asked, “Mom, can I tell Santa that he is not what Christmas is all about?”
I love that as we anticipate Christmas, my kids know that we are preparing to celebrate Jesus’ birth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lucky Few</title>
      <link>/posts/the-lucky-few/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-lucky-few/</guid>
      <description>“To think that we were just the lucky few And all along I never even knew” – Bebo Norman
Growing up, I didn’t realize how truly blessed I was. In fact, I don’t think it was till I went away to college that I truly recognized how good I had it. I was blessed to grow up in a home with two parents who truly loved each other as well as my brother and I.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Community</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2009 05:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-community/</guid>
      <description>When my son started preschool last fall, I told him he’d have a chance to make some new friends. His response? “I don’t need new friends. I have enough friends already.” I then proceeded to explain that sometimes maybe they need us. It took a little while, but he warmed up and made some new friends at preschool.
Hmmm… ever notice how sometimes you see something about yourself reflected in your child?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Lessons from the Samaritan Woman</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-lessons-from-the-samaritan-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-lessons-from-the-samaritan-woman/</guid>
      <description>This year in my Bible Study we are studying the book of John. Last week we read in John 4 about the Samaritan woman at the well. It’s funny to me how I can read a passage I’ve heard many times before and this time see it in a new light with fresh application. I love how living and breathing the Word of God is. Many things challenged me about this passage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: What About Thanksgiving?</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-what-about-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-what-about-thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>Long before the costumes and candy were even consumed for Halloween, stores already had their Christmas products on the shelves. I saw Santa and Jack-o-lanterns literally across the aisle from each other at Target a few weeks ago. And now, while the candy still lingers in our pumpkin bowls, if you walk into any department store, mall, or craft store, you’d swear it was December as the sights, sounds, and smells all tell of Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: A True Gent</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-a-true-gent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-a-true-gent/</guid>
      <description>Gentleman. I am convinced that if you were to look the word up in the dictionary, you’d have to find a picture of this man.  I first met him at our high school graduation. I remember being taken with the fact that he had one of those sweaters with the reinforced elbows and remarked to Scott how much I loved his genuine “Grandpa sweater” and was convinced he’d be the perfect Worthers Original grandpa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thought: God’s Love Story</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thought-gods-love-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2009 05:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thought-gods-love-story/</guid>
      <description>This week we took the kids to see a performance at the Sight and Sound theatre in Lancaster, Pa. If you ever get the opportunity to go (they also have a location in Branson, Mo) I highly recommend you go. (thankfully we were able to use a home school discount and take our family for less than the cost of one regularly priced ticket). We saw their production of In the Beginning, which was a rendition of the Creation story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Psalm 119: 33-36</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-psalm-119-33-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-psalm-119-33-36/</guid>
      <description>I am afraid I don’t have much for you this weekend in terms of deep thoughts. But I did stumble across this passage of Scripture. Doesn’t it make a wonderful prayer for us to offer up to our Lord? I am particularly challenged by verse 36. Oh, that I would turn my heart towards God’s statues rather than my own selfish gains. Teach me Oh God. Psalm 119:33-36
_ 33 Teach me, O LORD, to follow your decrees; then I will keep them to the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: My Turn</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-my-turn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2009 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-my-turn/</guid>
      <description>In my last weekend thought post, I mentioned my desire to teach my children to live their life in full and not let fear keep them from enjoying life’s pleasures. Ironically enough a week later I found myself having to choose between sitting on the sidelines or facing my fear.

15 years ago I got on a Gerris wheel with my friends. It seemed harmless enough at the time. But the combination of the height and the swaying car sent me into a full fledge panic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What was she thinking this weekend?</title>
      <link>/posts/what-was-she-thinking-this-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 17:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/what-was-she-thinking-this-weekend/</guid>
      <description>I’m sorry. Really I am. I had every intention of posting a thought this weekend and here it is Sunday night and I haven’t posted since Thursday!! Last week was my first week back into the real world. For the past 5 years I for the most part lived without an alarm. I’d wake when the kids woke, and our day would begin, sloooooowly after that. Now that we’re in Kindergarten I’m up at 6 and getting the circus crew fed, dressed and ready to start the day by 8 am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Fear</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-fear/</guid>
      <description>My child has been permanently scarred by a helium balloon.
I’m sure you think that I am kidding or exaggerating, but I promise you I am not. Remember this? Well two months after that traumatic experience, Scott took the kids to buy a balloon for my birthday, and needless to say my son (being the oldest child, and the overly cautious one that he is), was very nervous about the balloon flying away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: I’m a Survivor</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-im-a-survivor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-im-a-survivor/</guid>
      <description>Last week I survived the Annapolis 10 Mile Run. I’d like to say that I raced it or ran it, but in actuality I just survived it.
While one might wonder why I am not more excited and proud of such an accomplishment, it is because the year prior, I ran it well. I trained for it all summer and come race day I did my best. Now my best is only about 15 min faster than my survival pace, but the feeling I had when crossing the finish line was worlds different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: One Tiny Match</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-one-tiny-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2009 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-one-tiny-match/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever experienced complete darkness? I’m not talking about shutting out the lights before you crawl under the covers, but total darkness. In our electronic world of LEDs, it’s something we don’t often experience. During our time exploring Carlsbad earlier this week, the ranger brought us into a cavern 830 feet below the earth and shut off the lights. No flash lights. No matches. No floor lights. Nothing.
It was dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Discipline</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-discipline/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-discipline/</guid>
      <description>When the summer began I had big goals and plans for myself. I signed up for the Annapolis 10 Mile Run again this year, this time running with several of my high school friends. I had high hopes of running 3 or 4 times a week all summer. I had already envisioned how great my new, sleek running body would look come the end of August. I also enrolled in a Bible Study at a nearby church that was a hosting a Beth Moore study on the book of Esther.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Prayer</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2009 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-prayer/</guid>
      <description>One of the sweetest parts of my day is listening to my kids pray. I love to hear the things they are thankful for at the end of the day. It gives me a glimpse into the things they value most. I can only imagine the smile their heartfelt prayers bring to our Lord as He listens to the cries of their heart.
Tonight as my daughter was praying she thanked God for many things and then said very specifically, “but I am not, not thankful for thunderstorms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Memoirs</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-memoirs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 05:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-memoirs/</guid>
      <description>I’ve mentioned before, that the situation in Sudan has been heavy on my heart lately. During my attempt to do something about it, I felt it was of utmost importance to learn more about it. Recently, I decided to read some memoirs written by people who are from the region and whose lives have been affected by the atrocities. A few weeks ago I read Halima Bashir’s memoir of Survival in Darfur entitled Tears of the Desert .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Our Power Song</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-our-power-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-our-power-song/</guid>
      <description>You know your family is a techno family when your 5 year old requests that you add a song to your ipod so he can listen to it. Today, my son did just that and I was more than happy to oblige him with this choice. The “theme song” for our Vacation Bible School this year was “Today is the Day” by Lincoln Brewster. They sang it every morning at the start of VBS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: What do you think?</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-what-do-you-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 05:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-what-do-you-think/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been hosting this little carnival of mine for a few months now and was hoping for some feedback. I am wondering how often you think we should run weekend thoughts? Is once a week too much? Would you prefer once a month? Or every other week? Any other suggestions for improving the carnival? Anything I can do to make it easier? For those that have linked up in the past, thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Shopping for Sudan</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-shopping-for-sudan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 22:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-shopping-for-sudan/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you hear about something so big and so awful and while you know you just can’t ignore it and do nothing, you have no idea what to do.

And sometimes not knowing what to do leads to inaction. How can I make a difference to such a big problem? What can I do to help someone hurting half a world away?
That’s kinda how I felt after writing this weekend thought about Sudan two weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: The Costly Barbeque</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-the-costly-barbeque/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-the-costly-barbeque/</guid>
      <description>This weekend our family, like many across the country, will gather together, and after watching a small town parade, we’ll enjoy some barbeque and corn on the cob, and conclude the evening with a gorgeous fireworks display. Meanwhile, our troops are away from their friends and families. They are not sipping lemonade on the back porch, while grilling up some burgers. Tonight they will not be holding their children on their laps as they watch the fireworks burst in the air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why?</title>
      <link>/posts/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2009 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/why/</guid>
      <description>Last summer I took a Sunday School class in which I was introduced to a concept called solidarity and I realized I had very little of it. Before that class I was really very uneducated and honestly uncaring about events and situations going on in other parts of the world. If a plane crashed in Illinois, I’d be all over cnn.com reading the footage and following the case. “How tragic,” I’d think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Free Falling</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-free-falling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-free-falling/</guid>
      <description>My youngest child is fearless. FEARLESS
When we go to the playground she’s off and running, climbing to the top of the big slide, coming and going without looking back. She’ll slide down the stairs of my house with the speed of a bob sled racer. She tries very hard to keep up with her older siblings and she does it well.
The other day we were at a cookout and the kids were clamoring around a tree stump catching toads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thought: What I Believe</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thought-what-i-believe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2009 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thought-what-i-believe/</guid>
      <description>My friend and I were riding in the car one day when the song “Creed” by Third Day came on. I told my friend something to the effect of, “I love this song, it’s like everything I believe.”
To which she laughed (not exactly the response I was expecting) and said, “Your kidding right? You know this is the Apostles Creed.”
No wonder I was so impressed with the statement of faith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Day at a Time</title>
      <link>/posts/one-day-at-a-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-day-at-a-time/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I wrote about our kindergarten dilemma for next year.
After months of praying, discussing, putting of decision making, visiting, observing, and more discussing, I found it refreshing to have it out of my hands.
 Last week my son graduated from preschool. At the class picnic I was bombarded with questions about where he would go to school in the fall. I was telling one friend about our situation and she responded, “Well, it sounds like one of those things that will obviously be God working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t forget to share your thoughts tomorrow…</title>
      <link>/posts/dont-forget-to-share-your-thoughts-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dont-forget-to-share-your-thoughts-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>Just a friendly reminder to link up late tonight or tomorrow morning with your weekend thought. You can write something new or link up a thoughtful post from earlier in the week! I’m eager to read your thoughts!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Growing a Garden</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-growing-a-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2009 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-growing-a-garden/</guid>
      <description>I’m trying to cultivate my garden so I did a lot of weeding this past week. And as I did I found there are two ways to weed. You can pick each individual weed out by hand, or you can whack them all with a hoe. Both are effective and appropriate methods for weeding.
But, each has an appropriate time and place. In my old garden which was empty of any vegetation except for weeds, the hoe was the method of choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Waiting on His Timing</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-waiting-on-his-timing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2009 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-waiting-on-his-timing/</guid>
      <description>My son recently discovered the term “Summer Vacation” and in the innocence that only youth gives, he was quite disheartened when he learned that preschool didn’t last all summer long.
The fact that he’ll be in Kindergarten and not returning to his preschool didn’t help the matter.
It’s been so fun to watch him grow this past year at preschool. When we were looking at school’s last spring, I wasn’t sure where we wanted to send him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Have Faith Like a Child</title>
      <link>/posts/to-have-faith-like-a-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2009 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/to-have-faith-like-a-child/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes after reading the kids their bedtime Bible story we start to wonder, are they listening? Are they getting the point of the stories? Every once and a while they offer up another reminder that they really are.
Tonight after reading our children the story of Daniel and the Lions Den, my husband tried a little follow up to see if our 5 year old son was connecting…
 Scott: “What if President Obama made a law that said that everyone had to bow down and pray to him?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He is Risen Indeed!</title>
      <link>/posts/he-is-risen-indeed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/he-is-risen-indeed/</guid>
      <description>While I have enjoyed the many ups and downs of our vacation to Texas, I have decided that I never again want to go on vacation the week prior to Easter. I was very careful when planning our trip to make sure that we would be with family for Easter so that we could go to church and worship our Lord. I didn’t want to be camping or in the middle of nowhere for Easter Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Out Loud</title>
      <link>/posts/live-out-loud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 04:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/live-out-loud/</guid>
      <description>This winter Scott and I watched the movie The Pursuit of Happyness starring Will Smith. Few movies have stuck with me as much as this one. My heart was so heavy as I watched this very smart man struggle to provide for his son. The thing that got Scott and I the most, was how immensely blessed we are. We were given so many opportunities that others don’t get. We don’t have what we do because we deserve it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making New Friends</title>
      <link>/posts/making-new-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/making-new-friends/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I have found a new way to spend a Saturday night together.
For two and half years now Scott has been going into a nearby city to distribute bagged lunches to the homeless as part of our church’s homeless ministry. Typically, I stay home with the kids while he goes. In January, I had the opportunity of joining him. I had been once before about a year ago, but still I was nervous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Care of Business</title>
      <link>/posts/taking-care-of-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 20:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/taking-care-of-business/</guid>
      <description>This week Scott had a business trip.
It could not have come at a worse time for him. He has some big deadlines at work and this trip meant 3 days away from the office. He knew before he left that he would return swamped. It seemed there were more reasons for him not to go, than to go. And while it seemed not to make any sense, away he went.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Deeper Understanding</title>
      <link>/posts/a-deeper-understanding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-deeper-understanding/</guid>
      <description>Last week in church the pastor gave an illustration in which he mentioned the number of American lives lost during various wars in our history. My son looked over at me and asked why he was talking about American soldiers getting killed.
This led to a discussion later in the week in which it was brought to my attention that my son was under the impression that good guys don’t die in war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eggnog Talks Part 2</title>
      <link>/posts/eggnog-talks-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/eggnog-talks-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes little snippets of the extraordinary appear in the midst of everyday life. Right smack in the middle of a messy kitchen with trashcans overflowing, and kids walking around half naked, a conversation took place at our dining room table. Scott was having eggnog with the two oldest children and I had gotten the video camera out to catch my littlest one playing with the tripod. She was walking around setting up the tripod and exclaiming, “Cheese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s What It&#39;s All About...</title>
      <link>/posts/thats-what-its-all-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/thats-what-its-all-about/</guid>
      <description>As we were getting ready to go to the tree lighting ceremony downtown my son asked, &amp;ldquo;Mom, can I tell Santa that he is not what Christmas is all about?&amp;quot;
I love that as we anticipate Christmas, my kids know that we are preparing to celebrate Jesus&#39; birth. Yes, they know we are going to have presents under the tree, and they even sat on Santa&amp;rsquo;s lap at Scott&amp;rsquo;s work party, but when I asked my son what he likes best about Christmas, he answered, &amp;ldquo;celebrating Jesus&#39; birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still More Questions than Answers</title>
      <link>/posts/still-more-questions-than-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/still-more-questions-than-answers/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned before that Scott and I have been spending a great deal of thought, prayer, and discussion lately on a few big family decisions.
1. How will we educate our son next year?
I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it, but my oldest will be ready to start kindergarten next year. Since he was only months old, I&amp;rsquo;ve been hounded with questions from friends, family, and acquaintances about where we will send him to school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Time to Give Thanks</title>
      <link>/posts/a-time-to-give-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-time-to-give-thanks/</guid>
      <description>My son came home from school the other day with a craft he had made listing the things he was thankful for. They were
 Mommy and Daddy (yea, we made the list) his sisters (doesn&amp;rsquo;t this just warm your heart) toast ice cream  This list was quite insightful to me. Who know that toast got such high billing? I&amp;rsquo;ll be sure to have toast around more often now that I know how much he values it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Am I Choosing to be a Slave?</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-am-i-choosing-to-be-a-slave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2008 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-am-i-choosing-to-be-a-slave/</guid>
      <description>My son was playing in the backyard swinging his stick like an ax into the mound of dirt when he announced in an overly dramatic voice, &amp;ldquo;I am working like a slave!&amp;rdquo; I am sure it&amp;rsquo;s not hard for you to guess what we&amp;rsquo;ve been studying this year in Bible Study Fellowship.
That&amp;rsquo;s right&amp;hellip;the life of Moses.
I was recently reading in Exodus 16 about the Israelites wandering in the desert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Who Makes the Rules</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-who-makes-the-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-who-makes-the-rules/</guid>
      <description>A recent dinner conversation resulted in one of those, &amp;ldquo;wow&amp;rdquo; moments for my husband and I as we listened to our four year old speak truths that truly made us rejoice.
We had been talking about voting and my husband asked if my four year old son new what voting was&amp;hellip;
 Son: Yea I do I learned it at school&amp;hellip;it&amp;rsquo;s the government who makes all the rules
Dad: Right&amp;hellip; and we get to vote on who will make those rules</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Patience</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-patience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-patience/</guid>
      <description>Last month the topic of our MOPS (Mothers of PreSchoolers) meeting was patience. As we shared in our discussion groups, one mom shared a verse that she had read which had really helped her control her anger.
James 1:20
&amp;ldquo;for man&amp;rsquo;s anger does not bring about the righteous life that God desires.&amp;quot;
When she read the verse every mom around the table sat up. &amp;ldquo;Woa, that&amp;rsquo;s a good one, where is it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: True Beauty</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-true-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-true-beauty/</guid>
      <description>I was brushing my daughter&amp;rsquo;s hair the other day when I noticed how long and pretty it was getting.
 Me: Wow, your hair is getting long and so pretty
Daughter: No I&amp;rsquo;m not
Me: Why not? What do you want it to be?
Daughter: I want to be nice and kind.
(My son starts giggling at this point)
Me: Hmmm that&amp;rsquo;s good, but you can be nice and kind and still have pretty hair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Thoughts with Father Abraham</title>
      <link>/posts/deep-thoughts-with-father-abraham/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 04:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/deep-thoughts-with-father-abraham/</guid>
      <description>Ya know the kids song, &amp;ldquo;Father Abraham&amp;rdquo;? It&amp;rsquo;s typically popular with Sunday School and VBS kids everywhere. When I taught third grade it was a fav of my students.
Not such a hit with my four year old. I&amp;rsquo;ve said he&amp;rsquo;s analytical, and he proved that point.
We&amp;rsquo;re driving along in the minivan listening to a Kids Praise CD when &amp;ldquo;Father Abraham&amp;rdquo; comes on. I&amp;rsquo;m singing along in my head not really paying much attention when my son asks, &amp;ldquo;Why does it say I am one of them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Are You Letting Your Light Shine?</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-are-you-letting-your-light-shine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-are-you-letting-your-light-shine/</guid>
      <description>Last week in our Catechism Class, I taught the kids the song &amp;ldquo;This Little Light of Mine.&amp;rdquo; We talked about how we can let our lights shine and how we can hide our light. We played a game where I would name some actions (like obeying your parents, or hitting your sister) and then the kids had to say if that action let their light shine or covered it up. (They got to turn the flashlight off or on when it was their turn to answer the question).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Teaching Children Biblical Truths</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-teaching-children-biblical-truths/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-teaching-children-biblical-truths/</guid>
      <description>Our church has a catechism class for 4-9 year olds that meets weekly on Sunday evenings. This year I will be co-teaching my sons class on the beginning catechism. Throughout the course of the year he will work to memorize the first 48 questions in the Westminster Shorter Catechism.
I am really excited about this because the catechism provides an easy way to teach and remember vital Biblical truths.
For example here are the first five catechism questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Moses</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-moses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2008 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-moses/</guid>
      <description>This Thursday I began a new year of Bible Study with an organization called BSF. One of the biggest reasons I chose this study over others is that it has a children&amp;rsquo;s program unlike any other I&amp;rsquo;ve seen. My kids will be going through a preschool curriculum based on the same study I will be doing. I am so excited about talking with my older two children about what we are learning each week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Teeny Little Toe</title>
      <link>/posts/one-teeny-little-toe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-teeny-little-toe/</guid>
      <description>I hurt my toe this week. Really Badly. As in, it&amp;rsquo;s not a pretty picture, all black and blue and bleeding. Gonna lose the nail. See I told you it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a pretty picture!
I realized this week how much I take that little toe for granted. Until it started hurting, I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize the impact one little phalange could have on the entire body. (I also didn&amp;rsquo;t realize how many times a day my feet are stepped on by my kids).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: More</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2008 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-more/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve sung along to these lyrics dozens of times as I drove along in my minivan. But when I was running last week and this song came through my headphones, they hit me unlike any other time. God loves me, Crystal, more than the sun and the stars. As I listened to the words, I just imagined my Creator singing them to me and I was overwhelmed that He would chose to love me, wretched sinner that I am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facing One of my Biggest Fears</title>
      <link>/posts/facing-one-of-my-biggest-fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/facing-one-of-my-biggest-fears/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t like heights. Never have, but my trip to Mexico definitely didn&amp;rsquo;t help.
When I was pregnant with my son I developed an irrational fear of driving. I was driving over a bridge one day and felt light headed, which triggered a complete panic attack. After that I had trouble driving the 5 miles to work each day. My dear husband and sympathetic friends taxied me around for a few months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: I Don&#39;t Want to Do This on My Own</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-i-dont-want-to-do-this-on-my-own/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-i-dont-want-to-do-this-on-my-own/</guid>
      <description>Applying Sunday&amp;rsquo;s lesson this week has been quite a joy. I&amp;rsquo;ve started each day by working on a lesson from Beth Moore&amp;rsquo;s Bible study of the Psalms of Ascent. Some mornings I did it in bed before ever leaving my room. Other mornings, I was working on it on the couch with a kid snuggled on my lap. Either way, it was the beginning of my day and it helped me to get my focus in the correct place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Thought I Couldn&#39;t Wait till the Weekend to Share</title>
      <link>/posts/a-thought-i-couldnt-wait-till-the-weekend-to-share/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 18:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-thought-i-couldnt-wait-till-the-weekend-to-share/</guid>
      <description>The Lord convicted me of something this morning at church and I had the urge to share it here on my blog, which is incredibly ironic when you read what it is I&amp;rsquo;m convicted about. Our pastor spoke to us about idols. He shared an idol that he frequently struggles with worshipping in place of God. See an idol doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be an object. It isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily a little gold man that you bow to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: The Best Book I Never Read</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-the-best-book-i-never-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-the-best-book-i-never-read/</guid>
      <description>When Scott and I were engaged everyone was reading this book. While we never sat down and read the book we did peruse the chapter headings to determine what the 5 love languages were and it didn&amp;rsquo;t take long for us to figure out which love language each of us spoke. We will both tell you that this is the best marriage book we ever didn&amp;rsquo;t read. The concepts in this book have truly helped our marriage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Join Me in Praying for This Family</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-join-me-in-praying-for-this-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-join-me-in-praying-for-this-family/</guid>
      <description>There were a few blogs I read regularly this winter before I started blogging myself. One of these is Confessions of a CF Husband. Nate and his wife Tricia have had an incredible year, filled with many scary and uncertain moments. It is obvious to me from reading their blogs that they love the Lord and they truly trust in His sovereign will for their lives. It is both humbling and inspiring to read about their journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am One Busy Mama Tonight!!</title>
      <link>/posts/i-am-one-busy-mama-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/i-am-one-busy-mama-tonight/</guid>
      <description>Just a heads up for anyone who might care, I won&amp;rsquo;t be posting my weekend thought until Sunday. Tonight I am busy baking and decorating a birthday cake and finishing a scrapbook for my baby girl&amp;hellip; we are celebrating her first birthday tomorrow!! 
Where did this year go??? 
 Weekend Thoughts: My posts typically relate funny anecdotes about the happenings here at the circus. While my days are seldom “normal” enough to leave me without a “post worthy” moment, I use my last post of the week to highlight something a little more “thoughtful” and significant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Vacation Bible School</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-vacation-bible-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 04:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-vacation-bible-school/</guid>
      <description>This past week our church hosted Vacation Bible School. I love that we do vacation Bible School because it provides a tangible way for our church to reach out and serve our surrounding community. Parents eager for a mid summer break are offered something fun for their kids to get involved in. Kids come to play games, make crafts, meet friends, eat snacks, sing songs and the leave having had a great time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: The Integrity Factor</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-the-integrity-factor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-the-integrity-factor/</guid>
      <description>This week I wrote about my daughter&amp;rsquo;s hang up call to the local police station. We have no idea how long we were &amp;quot;on the air&amp;quot; before she hung up. I immediately started thinking, &amp;quot;What did they hear during that time?&amp;quot; Thankfully It wasn&amp;rsquo;t one of those meltdown moments when everyone was whining and crying, but what exactly did we say?
I remember the day we discovered that our baby monitor could pick up the signal of our neighbor&amp;rsquo;s baby monitor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Unthinkable Heartache Too Real For Too Many Moms</title>
      <link>/posts/an-unthinkable-heartache-too-real-for-too-many-moms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 20:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/an-unthinkable-heartache-too-real-for-too-many-moms/</guid>
      <description>You know I&amp;rsquo;ve complained before about having nothing to eat. I posted a picture of my fridge and said it was &amp;ldquo;the end of the world as we know it.&amp;quot; But the truth is, I know nothing about going hungry. When I look at my fridge and complain about making dinner, there are millions of mothers who would look at the contents and shout with joy. I can&amp;rsquo;t even begin to imagine the heartache of watching my baby go hungry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: The Perfect Father</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-the-perfect-father/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-the-perfect-father/</guid>
      <description>I love my children immensely and would do anything for them. When my children disobey, I do not love them any less. My love for them is not based on whether or not they behave in the store or if they place nicely with each other. I have loved my children since before they were born and the moment I held them for the first time that love multiplied and has grown daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: Giving Thanks</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-giving-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-giving-thanks/</guid>
      <description>Updated with posts below to people willing to contribute to Weekend Thoughts!
Psalm 100:4
&amp;ldquo;Enter His gates with thanksgiving and His courts with praise; give thanks to Him and praise His name.&amp;quot;
I often take things for granted and then when something happens and they don&amp;rsquo;t go as usual, I feel a sense of entitlement and am quite put out. I was listening to the Christian radio station today and someone was talking about a ministry (Blood Water Mission) they work for which helps provide clean water to people in Third World countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thought: We Praise You for Your Creation</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thought-we-praise-you-for-your-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thought-we-praise-you-for-your-creation/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we went camping with 2 other families. (More to come on the adventure later)! As we sat under the stars Friday night, I was in awe of our awesome creator God. Sitting around the fire, I could see the big dipper and I saw 2 shooting stars. The stars were so bright. Thank you Father for the beautiful picture of your handiwork.
Psalm 8:3-4
When I consider your heavens,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: What a Man!</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-what-a-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-what-a-man/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we are celebrating my husband&amp;rsquo;s 29th birthday. As I look back at some of his baby pictures, (isn&amp;rsquo;t he such a cutie) I am so thankful for the man he is today and feel incredibly blessed to call him my husband.
There are many things I respect about him, but at the top of the list would be his integrity, his perseverance, and his wisdom. We&amp;rsquo;ve been married almost 7 years now and since I get to live with him day in and day out, I truly get to see all sides of him and I can honestly say that he is consistent and that he genuinely strives each day to glorify God in all he does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week End Thoughts: Comfort in Dark Nights</title>
      <link>/posts/week-end-thoughts-comfort-in-dark-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/week-end-thoughts-comfort-in-dark-nights/</guid>
      <description>Last night the power went out for 3 hours. My 2 year old woke up in pitch darkness and obviously was scared. I fumbled my way to her room using the glow from our glow in the dark stars to guide my way. I then slept on her floor to help her fall back asleep. Occasionally she&amp;rsquo;d wake up scared and I would reach my hand up to let her know I was still there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week End Thoughts: My Mom</title>
      <link>/posts/week-end-thoughts-my-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/week-end-thoughts-my-mom/</guid>
      <description>Since Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day is this weekend, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d make my thoughtful post about my mother. Growing up my mom was my best friend. She was approachable and always willing to listen. I could ask her about anything and she never made me feel awkward or silly. Mom knew how to make things special. She decorated the house for the seasons and holidays and made our birthdays into something we looked forward to all year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where did Thoughtful Thursday go?</title>
      <link>/posts/where-did-thoughtful-thursday-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/where-did-thoughtful-thursday-go/</guid>
      <description>Week End Thoughts&amp;hellip;
I decided to move my Thoughtful Thursday since I am participating in We Are THAT Family&amp;rsquo;s Sincerely Fro&#39; Me to You carnival on Thursdays. Since &amp;ldquo;Thoughtful Thursday&amp;rdquo; is something I made up, it seems trivial to move the day&amp;hellip; same theme, only we&amp;rsquo;ll call it Week End Thoughts&amp;hellip;
Week End Thoughts:
My posts typically relate funny anecdotes about the happenings of a stay at home wife and mom with three kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughtful Thursday: Going the Extra Mile</title>
      <link>/posts/thoughtful-thursday-going-the-extra-mile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/thoughtful-thursday-going-the-extra-mile/</guid>
      <description>My son&amp;rsquo;s Sunday School teacher approached me on Sunday and said that my son has invited her to our house several times and wanted to know if it would be ok if she and her teenage daughter stopped by for a bit on Tuesday. I told her of course and made arrangements to get in touch the next day. I e-mailed her on Monday and told her I didn&amp;rsquo;t want her to feel obligated to come over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughtful Thursday: Answered Prayer</title>
      <link>/posts/thoughtful-thursday-answered-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/thoughtful-thursday-answered-prayer/</guid>
      <description>Last week as we were running errands the Christian radio station played one of those 60 sec minisermons. The person was speaking on 1 John 4 and read the passage which states, &amp;ldquo;This is love: not that we loved God, but that he loved us and sent his Son as an atoning sacrifice for our sins.&amp;rdquo;
Son: &amp;quot; Mom, why did she say we don&amp;rsquo;t love God?&amp;quot;
Me: &amp;ldquo;They were saying that we didn&amp;rsquo;t love God first, but that God loved us and then we loved him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UGH!!</title>
      <link>/posts/ugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ugh/</guid>
      <description>Last night I got a chocolate craving. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like doing a ton of work to feed this craving so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d bake some No Bake Cookies. Growing up this was often the cure for a chocolate craving with minimal effort. When I opened my cabinet to get out the sugar I noticed a sticky brown residue on the container.
&amp;quot;Uh-oh&amp;quot; I thought.
Upon further investigation I found molasses covering the entire shelf, the box of aluminum foil, the pancake box, the corn muffin box and still no molasses jar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catechism 714</title>
      <link>/posts/catechism-714/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 04:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/catechism-714/</guid>
      <description>Our good friend Bob posted this on his blog and I wanted to link to it in my Weekend Thought. Since his blog is for invited readers only, he gave me permission to post it on my blog and link to it that way. I was struck by the beauty of his poem.
Catechism 714

Of all things
she wanted to know
the colors of heaven
Not the sky</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
