<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>homeschool on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/homeschool/</link>
    <description>Recent content in homeschool on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 10:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/homeschool/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Week at School…</title>
      <link>/posts/this-week-at-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/this-week-at-school/</guid>
      <description>I feel like we are off to a pretty good start this school year and we are settling into a routine.
The hardest part for me about home schooling and the part I like the LEAST is the juggling act of wearing both the hat of mom and the hat of teacher. The kids don’t understand that my making them do a subject they don’t like doesn’t make me a mean mom, it makes me their teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to the Building!!!</title>
      <link>/posts/back-to-the-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 06:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/back-to-the-building/</guid>
      <description>And so a new year begins… this morning was our first day back at the tutorial. I can’t believe it marks our 6th year of homeschooling. What a blessing this community had been to our family. Here we are starting 2nd, 3rd, and 5th grades!

“And this is my prayer: that your love may abound more and more in knowledge and depth of insight, so that you may be able to discern what is best and may be pure and blameless for the day of Christ, filled with the fruit of righteousness that comes through Jesus Christ—to the glory and praise of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nesting</title>
      <link>/posts/nesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nesting/</guid>
      <description>I feel like the month of August is much like the 9th month of pregnancy. I go into crazy nesting mode as I gear up for another school year. There is the ordering of curriculum… then the purchasing of school supplies… then the organizing of the binders… and cracking open that homeschool cabinet which ALWAYS turns into the junk closet over the summer. Ya know, the “Company is coming and I need a place to hide all these papers and misc junk from the kitchen counters,” place….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching My Breath</title>
      <link>/posts/catching-my-breath/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/catching-my-breath/</guid>
      <description>Gah! It seems MORE than a month has gone by since I last updated the ol’ blog. What a time it was too. The whirlwind of the end of the school year. Last week we had our last day at the tutorial followed by their year end assembly. Wahoo!!! All those snow days we kept our nose to the grind stone are paying off now baby! I was so proud as I watched them get up front and recite all of the things they had memorized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Field Trip</title>
      <link>/posts/family-field-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/family-field-trip/</guid>
      <description>This year in History we are studying American History from the explorers to the war on 1812. I love history. It is my favorite part of home schooling. And I am so grateful that we live within driving distance of so many great historical sites. I really wanted to take the kids to Philadelphia for a day trip over spring break. Scott graciously rearranged his work schedule so that he could join us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“We are Scientists”</title>
      <link>/posts/we-are-scientists/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/we-are-scientists/</guid>
      <description>This week I took my girls on a field trip with their classmates from our tutorial. We visited a Science Center run by the local school system. The kids learned how to observe the world around them and record those observations. They studied bugs and wild life found in our area as well as learned about camouflage and even played a game to reinforce the concept.
They got to use almost all of their senses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Field Trip Fun</title>
      <link>/posts/family-field-trip-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/family-field-trip-fun/</guid>
      <description>When we switched out history curriculum this year so that the whole family studies the same period of history (with varying level of work catered to their age level), one of the reasons I was MOST excited was that our field trips would be applicable to all. When our tutorial gave off for Presidents Day, I was eager to take advantage of the day free of book work to go on a field trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures of our Life</title>
      <link>/posts/pictures-of-our-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pictures-of-our-life/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t had time to really update the blog lately. In fact, I have found my days to be quite full now that we are in full swing with our school and extra curricular activities. Bursting at the seams full. But, I have whipped the camera out a few times, so I decided today to download them and at least try to preserve some memories of everyday life around here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to School!!!</title>
      <link>/posts/back-to-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/back-to-school/</guid>
      <description>Because our homeschool tutorial meets on a Mon-Thurs schedule and the board doesn’t like to start the year on a partial week, we are THE LAST PEOPLE IN THE WORLD (or so it feels like) to start back to school. But, today we finally had our turn for the morning poses on the front step. 
Another school year is upon us. We had an EPIC summer. One for the record books… and I while I didn’t tackle every project on my summer to do list, we are starting the year off a little more organized than last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another School Year Complete</title>
      <link>/posts/another-school-year-complete/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/another-school-year-complete/</guid>
      <description>That’s right, today is our last day of school at the building. 
As we prepare to leap into summer… let’s take a quick peek back at day 1.

Look how much they’ve grown just physically this year! I can’t believe it’s our last day of Kindergarten, 1st grade, an 3rd grade.

They got to dress down for the last day of school. (Can you tell it’s been a chilly spring?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Little Trick that Has Been HUGE for us in School This Year</title>
      <link>/posts/the-new-little-trick-that-has-been-huge-for-us-in-school-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 09:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-new-little-trick-that-has-been-huge-for-us-in-school-this-year/</guid>
      <description>We are three weeks in to our new school year. I think I FINALLY have all the kids correct curriculum (missed a few things I when I ordered it this summer) and their books organized in a way that works for them, me, and their tutors at the tutorial. I’ve done things a little differently this year, and SO FAR, it has helped our days to run more smoothly. First of all, I’ve committed to waking up before the kids every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Answer to Everyone’s Question</title>
      <link>/posts/the-answer-to-everyones-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-answer-to-everyones-question/</guid>
      <description>Lately, I’ve been asked several times what I do with my 2 year old while I am teaching the older 3. Here’s your answer. 
Yes, that would be pen mark up and down the corner of the walls in my dining room. Yes, he did that yesterday morning while I was working with the big kids in the other room and thought that scraping sound was the sound of him scraping oatmeal of his cereal bowl with a spoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Beginning</title>
      <link>/posts/a-new-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-new-beginning/</guid>
      <description>Scott commented the other day that he feels the passage of time more noticeably at the beginning of the school year, rather than on the kids birthdays. I think he’s right.

Especially this year, when I packed up three backpacks and three lunch boxes and lined up 3 kids for pictures at the front door. We have our Kindergartener, on her very first day of school ever. 
Followed by our first grader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Reading</title>
      <link>/posts/summer-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/summer-reading/</guid>
      <description>I love to read. I love when you get to that point in the novel, where you literally can not put it down and find yourself speed reading/skipping words just to quickly make it to the next part and find out what happens. One of our goals in educating our children was to make readers out of them. This was hard at first with our son as reading didn’t come naturally to him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting</title>
      <link>/posts/reflecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/reflecting/</guid>
      <description>I don’t homeschool because I hate the government. Nor do I homeschool because I think the public school system is all evil. Nor do I homeschool because I want my kids to be smarter than yours. In fact, raising super smart kids isn’t even my main goal of education.
I homeschool because I want to spend the time with my kids. That’s it, in a nut shell.
But, if I may be honest and come clean with you, it’s hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Book Smarts</title>
      <link>/posts/beyond-book-smarts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/beyond-book-smarts/</guid>
      <description>Education is about so much more than book smarts. I’ve known this for awhile and believed it to my core. In fact, this fact alone has dictated so many decisions we make in raising our children, especially since we home school and want to make sure that they are learning more than just “reading, writing, and arithmetic.”
Yesterday and today our school time was “interrupted” so that I could spend time one on one disciplining a child for behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life With 2</title>
      <link>/posts/life-with-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/life-with-2/</guid>
      <description>Now that my oldest 2 are at their tutorial two days a week, I find myself with just 2 children at home on those mornings. It is a truly odd feeling and a dynamic I am not yet used to. Though I am sure it is nothing compared to the strangeness I’ll feel next year when I am left with only my lil man two days a week. I am hoping to use this time to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another New School Year</title>
      <link>/posts/another-new-school-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/another-new-school-year/</guid>
      <description>While we’ve been “doing school” at home for the past few weeks for the purpose of reviewing and getting used to the routine, today was the first official start of our new school year.
We homeschool, but also use a tutorial. The kids attend the tutorial twice a week and study at home with me three days a week. So far, I feel it provides the balance our family needs between homeschooling and traditional schooling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banner Day at the Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/banner-day-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/banner-day-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>Dishes piled in the sink, pjs on till 2:00 in the afternoon, laundry waiting to be folded, counter cluttered…
But today, it doesn’t bother me. (ok, it doesn’t bother me too much anyway)…
because…
Today, I finally took the time to snuggle on the couch with my almost 5 year old and work with her on reading… and today that precious light bulb went off as she first went up and down the blend ladders and then graduated to three letter words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You take the good, you take the bad…</title>
      <link>/posts/you-take-the-good-you-take-the-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/you-take-the-good-you-take-the-bad/</guid>
      <description>“You take the good, you take the bad, you take them both and there you have The Facts of Life, the Facts of Life.”
Blogging is funny, as many of you bloggers know, because when you write a post, you’re really writing a snapshot of a moment in time. And as as the author (or photographer, if you will) you get to choose which moment in time you post and thus you can largely shape the perception of your self and your family life that you present to the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Big and Yet So Small</title>
      <link>/posts/so-big-and-yet-so-small/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/so-big-and-yet-so-small/</guid>
      <description>After months of deliberating, praying, waiting, and a little second guessing, the first day of school finally arrived this week. As you may recall we decided to home school, but with a twist. We’ve enrolled our son in a home school tutorial that he attends two days a week. So he has school at home with me three days a week, and at his tutorial 2 days a week. In a lot of ways, it’s the best of both worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Nye’s Got Nothing on my Little Guy</title>
      <link>/posts/bill-nyes-got-nothing-on-my-little-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 03:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bill-nyes-got-nothing-on-my-little-guy/</guid>
      <description>The kids have been into “experimenting” these days. We even have science journals with which to record our results. (Yes, we can thank Sid the Science Kid for that brilliant idea).
It started with freezing stuff.
I overheard my son tell his sister with a hushed voice of excitement, “Sis, you watch…we’ll put this cup of water into the freezer and then later when we come back it will be ice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
