<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>american girl doll on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/american-girl-doll/</link>
    <description>Recent content in american girl doll on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 08:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/american-girl-doll/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reunited At Last</title>
      <link>/posts/reunited-at-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/reunited-at-last/</guid>
      <description>Just one day over 2 weeks from shipping her off to the doll hospital, Kit arrived on our door step during lunch today.

Her arm has been reattached and they even sent her home in a pretty hospital gown, with new socks, and her hair pulled up in a bow. 


It just so happened that Daddy popped home for lunch today and she eagerly greeting him on the steps to tell him the good news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Circus First</title>
      <link>/posts/a-circus-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-circus-first/</guid>
      <description>We’ve had stitches, numerous trips to Right Time Care and even an over night hospital stay, but so far we haven’t had any broken limbs.
Until this week.
I was upstairs when I heard the blood curdling screams and sobs of my 5 year old. I raced downstairs to see her sobbing and holding her beloved Kit in one hand and Kit’s arm in the other. (I had noticed the day before, that her arm seemed wobbly and something wasn’t right, so it wasn’t a total shock to me).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Daddy/Daughter Date…</title>
      <link>/posts/a-daddydaughter-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-daddydaughter-date/</guid>
      <description>Scott took a vacation day on Thursday so he could spend the day with our oldest daughter. First they went with the other kids in her Kindergarten class to see a performance of The Night Before Christmas. Apparently the sets were gorgeous and the play was very well done. Such a treat to go to a live theatre AND to get to see it with her school friends and Dad. I think it was also a treat for Dad to get to see her with her school friends, it’s an aspect of her life that he doesn’t get to see very often.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
