<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>library on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/library/</link>
    <description>Recent content in library on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 17:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/library/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Why</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/remembering-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/remembering-why/</guid>
      <description>So it was one of _ those _ library trips where I was really regretting going. We were pushing close to past bed time and Momma was tired. But, I knew there were some books on the hold shelf waiting for me and I had two bags of books in the van to return, so I figured we’d run in “real quick.” But, of course, it wasn’t real quick. I had to help my Kindergartner find a book on cats for her science book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I keep Going Back</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/why-i-keep-going-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 03:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/why-i-keep-going-back/</guid>
      <description>I’ve written time and time again of my hot/cold, love/hate, on again/off again relationship with the library. Despite the fines (and my husband can attest to the fact that we have paid MANY), I keep going back again and again….and the reasons are…

 1. the hush that falls over the circus van on the ride home as everyone is absorbed in their books (I’ve even been known to sit in the van in the parking lot soaking in that silence)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There is HOPE</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/there-is-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/there-is-hope/</guid>
      <description>For all those wondering if there is truly hope for the hopeless… those who’ve made their resolutions and long since broken them… for those that thought, perhaps your just destined for failure…. to those… I offer this little glimmer of hope….
Our last visit to the library—if that trip didn’t redeem us, I don’t know what will!
Those who have been long time readers here at the circus… might recall I have a bit of a bad history with the library… first, we have the whole circus family wing of the library thanks to the $18 fine visit and the $42 fine visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life With 2</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-with-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-with-2/</guid>
      <description>Now that my oldest 2 are at their tutorial two days a week, I find myself with just 2 children at home on those mornings. It is a truly odd feeling and a dynamic I am not yet used to. Though I am sure it is nothing compared to the strangeness I’ll feel next year when I am left with only my lil man two days a week. I am hoping to use this time to</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
