<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christmas on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christmas on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 14:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with Grands and Cousins</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-with-grands-and-cousins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-with-grands-and-cousins/</guid>
      <description>I LOVE hosting Christmas. And I am so thankful that my extended family allows me that privilege. I am thankful that they all have been willing and able to come year after year so we could share the day together. I don’t take it for granted. I know my parents won’t always be able to travel. I know my BIL and SIL can get stationed so far away that it just doesn’t make a trip to MD possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmastime in the Big Apple</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmastime-in-the-big-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmastime-in-the-big-apple/</guid>
      <description>About a month ago my youngest asked when we would see the Statue of Liberty again. We visited it a few years ago on our way to our Boston Vacation, and it has been a highlight memory of our youngest child ever since. He loves when we spot it on tv or in a picture somewhere. I replied, “Probably the next time we go to New York City.” To which he of course replied, “When can we go to New York City again?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cherishing These Days</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cherishing-these-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cherishing-these-days/</guid>
      <description>It’s hard to believe that my youngest will be school age next year. Seriously, how did that happen? Sometimes when we drop the big kids off at their tutorial on “school at the building days” he will pause outside the Kindergarten room and tell me, “That’s where I go next year Momma and then you will be all alone and so sad.” And my heart kinda breaks a little. Because he is right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Relaxing Christmas</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-relaxing-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-relaxing-christmas/</guid>
      <description>It has been a very relaxing Christmas vacation at the circus house. My sister in law and her family came in to town the evening of the 23rd. We had too much fun making cupcakes for the kids for baby Jesus’ bday party on Christmas night. She is an awesome trooper. She happily obliged my request to roll out 19 baby Jesus figurines out of marshmallow fondant at 10:00pm. Seriously, worlds best sister in law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking in the Garden</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/walking-in-the-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 06:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/walking-in-the-garden/</guid>
      <description>I know it isn’t very seasonal to have 66 degree weather the night of winter solstice. But I gotta confess I didn’t mind it one bit as that was the evening I’d been planning to take the kids to see the lights at Brookside Gardens. I had never been but heard someone talking about them once. Unlike other light displays, this one you park and get out and walk. Which could be a hard sell for 4 kids on a cold winter night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Letter to My Kids</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-letter-to-my-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 06:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-letter-to-my-kids/</guid>
      <description>Dear Children of Mine,
10 years from now when you are wondering what in the world to get Mom for Christmas, I have an idea for you. So write it down and stick it away and remember it when your 19, 17, 16, and 13. All I want for Christmas, is you. It’s true… nothing wrapped under the tree could possible come close to time spent with you. So, if you really want to make my day, ask me if we can make sugar cookies together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Christmas Mess</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-christmas-mess/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-christmas-mess/</guid>
      <description>A traditional Christmas card will not be arriving in your mailbox this year from the circus fam, instead I give to you this greeting from me to you. I’ve thought a lot about what I want to say in this card. What image I want to share with you from my family to yours. We’ve had a lot of great moments this year. Many of them I’ve shared on here so I can look back and remember them in the years to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Need a Little Art</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-need-a-little-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-need-a-little-art/</guid>
      <description>We are on break here at the circus. And I couldn’t be more excited about it. I have been looking forward to this week for ages. The week before Christmas. All I want to do is enjoy the kiddos and catch up on some house work. And bake. And do some shopping. And maybe see some friends. (ha, ha… can you tell I am an introvert? read over that list, when I proof read this and re read it, it made me laugh)…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Tradition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-favorite-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-favorite-tradition/</guid>
      <description>We got our tree today!!! 
We started decorating the house yesterday, but it wasn’t quite right without the tree. I don’t think our three year old remembers the Christmas tree b/c after we cut it down and tied it to our van he asked, “Can we keep it in our yard as our Christmas tree?” He had no idea it would go in the house. And then when we added lights, he was beyond excited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cookie-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cookie-fun/</guid>
      <description>The most favorite Christmas cookie for the circus fam to make is sugar cookies. Messiness + sugar = pure bliss for the circus crew!!


  This year we enjoyed rolling and cutting the cookies with our cousin Eli. 

 It was also the first year that the youngest circus crew member got to participate in the cooking making fun. And by participate, I of course mean, eating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watching the Christmas Story Unfold</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/watching-the-christmas-story-unfold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/watching-the-christmas-story-unfold/</guid>
      <description>When I saw the sign on the side of highway advertising a Live Nativity, I was instantly interested. I’ve never seen one and thought it would be a great experience for the kids. When talking to a friend I found out more details and made plans to bring them. It was a simple production, put on by a small community church on a cold winter’s night on the side of a busy highway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Tuba Christmas</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/merry-tuba-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/merry-tuba-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is without a doubt my favorite time of year. I’ve already shared in my last post how I love all the things about Christmas. And I do, even the shopping, baking, prepping for company… I love it all. In fact when Christmas actually gets here I am always a little sad, because truth be told I love the season, the anticipation, the preparation so much that I am sad to see it end when the actual day of Christmas arrives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love Christmastime</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-love-christmastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-love-christmastime/</guid>
      <description>Love choosing and cutting down our tree…

Love decorating it and passing on the memories to my children of the precious ornaments hung on our tree…

Love the wonder of the lights…

Love watching them play with toys that only come out once a year…

Love seeing them act out the story of Christ’s birth as they play with their nativity sets

And this year I love listening to the sounds of Christmas carols fill the house as my son plays them on the piano</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wasted Cookies?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wasted-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wasted-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Nothing like the holidays, to bring on some humor from the lil ones. Here’s a few I want to record for posterity.
When Scott was talking to my 4 yr old about what she wanted to get me for Christmas, she told him she wanted to get Mommy flowers and she was going to be nice. To clarify Scott asked, “So your going to be nice as a Christmas gift for Mommy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Momma’s Christmas Wish</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mommas-christmas-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mommas-christmas-wish/</guid>
      <description>Ever year it is the same… I beg and plead for just one small Christmas Eve miracle, a picture of my kids in front of the tree. The last few years as they’ve gotten older, it has actually gotten easier, thanks to a slight guilt trip from Daddy (do this for Mommy please, as your Christmas gift to her). I thought it might be fun after sharing this years picture to look back on Christmas’s Past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Presents Can’t Be Wrapped</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-presents-cant-be-wrapped/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-presents-cant-be-wrapped/</guid>
      <description>A few moments from this weekend which I wish to savor…
1. My son presenting his gift to his extended family. (One nap time he came up excited to share that he had drawn a picture from each scene in Luke 2. On Christmas he gave one picture to each person. He then laid them all out on the floor and recited the story from memory.)


2. Prepping the Christmas Lasagnas with my daughter… it marked a milestone, in which she was truly helpful in the kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2010</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-2010/</guid>
      <description>Just a few of my favorite pictures of our fun on Christmas morning!
Someone got a lil sleepy waiting up for Santa

The grandparents eagerly waiting for the kids to wake up on Christmas morning.

Does this capture the excitement of Christmas morning, or what? (I wish knew what had just been opened)
 
This tender moment was brought to you by “Lego Star Wars for Wii”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hard Way</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-hard-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-hard-way/</guid>
      <description>When cutting down a tree, much like when shopping for a dress, there seems to be an unwritten rule of conduct.
No matter how fabulous it looks, you simply can’t go with the first one you see.
One simply can’t drive to the farm, march down the aisle, and stop at the first decent looking spruce you see.
That would be far too easy. Where would the fun be in that?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
