<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Labor Day on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/labor-day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Labor Day on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 10:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/labor-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Blessed Tradition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-blessed-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-blessed-tradition/</guid>
      <description>Labor Day. What does it really mean anyway? I’m not fully sure of it’s tradition or reason for existing, but I do know it means a 3 day weekend at the end of the summer and so I’ve never really questioned it.
It wasn’t until the summer of 2002, that it took on a whole new meaning for me and my family. That was the year we went to my friends family cabin with 5 other couples and just hung out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Glad That Some Things Never Change</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-glad-that-some-things-never-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-glad-that-some-things-never-change/</guid>
      <description>Our conversations used to be about teachers and homework, now they are about how we’re going to school our own kids. We used to discuss boys and dream about our future, now many of us are married to those boys and discuss how many children we plan to have. They were the ones I called when Scott first told me he liked me, and when he first kissed me, and when he asked me to be his wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s so much more friendly with two (or 26)</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-so-much-more-friendly-with-two-or-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-so-much-more-friendly-with-two-or-26/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;It takes a long time to grow an old friend.&amp;quot; - by John Leonard

Nothing says labor day weekend to me, then a house bursting at the seams with friends. For the past 8 years, we’ve spent labor day with my group of 6 best friends from high school and our growing families. While we’ve changed locations over the years from rustic accommodations, rental homes, and friends houses, some things have remained constant.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
