<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>grand adventure of 2013 on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/grand-adventure-of-2013/</link>
    <description>Recent content in grand adventure of 2013 on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2013 11:47:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/grand-adventure-of-2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Almost Home</title>
      <link>/posts/almost-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2013 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/almost-home/</guid>
      <description>The last stop on our grand adventure of 2013 was Grandma and Papa’s house. We arrived in the afternoon on the 4th of July… just in time for a cookout. The kids greatly enjoyed tractor rides with Papa, playing board games with Grandma and running the trains in the basement.

Then they requested a visit to “The Coolest Playground Ever.” As we trekked around the US over the past 3 weeks, Scott and I learned from the kids that the playground by which all playgrounds are judged against is the wooden one by Grandma and Papa’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stopping to Play in Illinois</title>
      <link>/posts/stopping-to-play-in-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/stopping-to-play-in-illinois/</guid>
      <description>We set out from our friends in Iowa and headed north east. Our destination was the suburbs of Chicago. Scott and I visited Chicago last year for our anniversary and while I loved the city and would love to visit it again, we didn’t feel this was the trip to take the family into the city. Instead we planned a stop at Lego Discovery Center outside of the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heading East!</title>
      <link>/posts/heading-east/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/heading-east/</guid>
      <description>After leaving the Badlands, we were Eastward bound and on the homeward stretch. We planned lots of fun stops for this part of the journey, knowing it was the final stretch and wanting to change it up a bit and keep things fun and exciting.
Our first such stop was in Sioux Falls, SD. I found a hotel there that had a water slide and a splash pool. There was also a put put course in town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Park (for a long while)</title>
      <link>/posts/last-park-for-a-long-while/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2013 06:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/last-park-for-a-long-while/</guid>
      <description>Well, I am really sad to say our trip is winding down. We visited the last National Park of our vacation and we can count the number of days left on our trip on one hand. The last park on this grand vacation was Badlands National Park in South Dakota. 
We hit the Badlands on a great day and a great time of day. The sun was low in the sky making the colors pop out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animals, Animals, Everywhere!</title>
      <link>/posts/animals-animals-everywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/animals-animals-everywhere/</guid>
      <description>Saturday we left Mt Rushmore and drove 4.5 hours north to Theodore Roosevelt National Park in Medora, ND. A visit to this park meant an approximately 9 hour driving detour from what could have otherwise been a short hop from Mt. Rushmore to the SD Badlands. Sometimes a quest such as our forces your hand to take some pretty circuitous routes… we set off not exactly sure what the ND badlands had to offer that the SD badlands did not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wind Cave Take 2</title>
      <link>/posts/wind-cave-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wind-cave-take-2/</guid>
      <description>11 years ago when Scott and I did our first National Park/Cross Country trip, we drove through Wind Caves National Park. We hadn’t yet begun our quest to see every National Park, so we actually just drove through the park and enjoyed the prairie dogs and buffalo. It was literally a stop on our way, not a destination in itself. This time, Scott and I wanted to see the park the right way and go on a cave tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation Improv</title>
      <link>/posts/vacation-improv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2013 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/vacation-improv/</guid>
      <description>Between the long, late day at Black Falls of the Gunnison and the crazy hot and dirty hike at Great Sand Dunes, Scott and I found ourselves ready for a reprieve. So, we readjusted our schedule a bit and drove 3 hours to a hotel about an hour from Colorado Springs. There we chilled. I took the kids for a quick dip in the pool while Scott ran out to get us a pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Whole Lotta Sand</title>
      <link>/posts/a-whole-lotta-sand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2013 08:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-whole-lotta-sand/</guid>
      <description>We arrived at Great Sand Dunes National Park in the middle of the night so our first view of the dunes was when we opened up our tent the next morning. We thought for sure we wouldn’t be able to get a site since they were first come first serve and we were so very late. But once again we were blessed with a camp site in the park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Jam Packed 24 hours</title>
      <link>/posts/a-jam-packed-24-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-jam-packed-24-hours/</guid>
      <description>We left Canyonlands mid day on Monday and got a hotel in Montrose, Co. We were greeted with a fabulous view of the snow topped Rocky Mts. Scott took the kids swimming while I did laundry. Then we splurged and went out for dinner at Applebees. It was a welcome change from fast food/Subway. The next day we hit Black Canyon of the Gunnison!

This was a hard park to fully comprehend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking in their Footsteps</title>
      <link>/posts/walking-in-their-footsteps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 21:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/walking-in-their-footsteps/</guid>
      <description>We arrived in Mesa Verde National Park a few hours before sunset. We had been hoping to catch the Twilight Tour of Cliff Palace but tickets are sold on a first come basis and, much like we expected, we weren&amp;rsquo;t the first to come. We opted for a sunset drive along the loop with some pretty overlooks and booked tours for the following morning. 
The sunset drive was really fascinating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Mom’s Dream</title>
      <link>/posts/every-moms-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/every-moms-dream/</guid>
      <description>How many times have you wished you could be in more than one place at a time? I know there’s been many a time that I’ve had that thought….
And Saturday, I had my wish. We were in four places at once.
The circus family stood in Arizona, Utah, New Mexico, and Colorado at the same time.

We goofed around a bit and then the big kids got to strike their favorite pose in 4 states at once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It really is that GRAND</title>
      <link>/posts/it-really-is-that-grand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/it-really-is-that-grand/</guid>
      <description>11 years ago this month Scott and I visited The Grand Canyon. It was my first time seeing it and it took my breath away. Now, 31 parks later, it is still my favorite of all the National Parks. Many rank high on my list, but if you could only see one, I feel like this should be the one.

The day before we took the kids, I had a little fear, much like the fear I had before taking them to Disney World.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beneath the Rim</title>
      <link>/posts/beneath-the-rim/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 04:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/beneath-the-rim/</guid>
      <description>The highlight of our day at the Grand Canyon for most of the members of our circus crew was a short hike they took into the canyon. 
We all started on the hike, but it was more than this “fraid’ of heights Momma” could handle. The plan was to go to the first tunnel and back, but after about 2 treks on the switchback, I was biting back tears and hating EVERY second of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Step Back in Time</title>
      <link>/posts/a-step-back-in-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-step-back-in-time/</guid>
      <description>Thursday we spent the day at Petrified Forest National Park, located in the painted desert of Arizona.

Here the kids worked hard to earn their Junior Ranger badges. We spent quite a bit of time learning and researching in the visitors center. 
We also took a walk to look at the petrified wood. 
We then drove through the Painted Desert. It was beautiful to see all the layers of colored dirt deposited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Desert Experience</title>
      <link>/posts/the-desert-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-desert-experience/</guid>
      <description>The kids were so excited to finally get to go camping. Day 6 of our adventure and it was our first night setting up a tent. The kids LOVE the head flashlights I picked up before we left. 
Unfortunately, we discovered we neglected to pack the poles with our tent. So we had a family meeting round the picnic table. We had 3 options. 1. Go to Walmart, get a new tent and come back and set it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Saguaro</title>
      <link>/posts/the-great-saguaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-great-saguaro/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday we left New Mexico and headed south west for Saguaro National Park in Tuscon, AZ.

We got to Saguaro National Park in time to explore a bit and then take in the parks beauty after the oppressive heat of the day was past. It really was perfect timing. We walked around a path near the visitors center which allowed us to see the cacti up close. 
The cacti were much bigger than we expected and we were delighted to find some in bloom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cadillac Ranch</title>
      <link>/posts/cadillac-ranch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cadillac-ranch/</guid>
      <description>While planning our trip, I was searching for some sort of fun diversion for our long car ride day. I wanted something free, fun, and not out of the way.
Cadillac Ranch fit the bill perfectly. 
Cadillac Ranch is a wide open field on the side of route 40 with 10 old cadillacs stuck in the ground. People can come and spray paint on them. It’s a “changing art exhibit” as people are continually coming and adding to and changing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Road Again</title>
      <link>/posts/on-the-road-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 12:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/on-the-road-again/</guid>
      <description>Sunday was one of the few days of our trip that we spent entirely in the van. While we will be in the car for portions of almost every day of our trip, Sunday was a day when the event for the day was driving. For over 11 hours. We left Ft Smith, AR around 9:45AM5am CT, quickly entered into Oklahoma, drove the top portion of Texas, and arrived in Albuquerque, NM a little after 11:00pm MT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Like it Hot</title>
      <link>/posts/some-like-it-hot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/some-like-it-hot/</guid>
      <description>The first national park on this grand adventure was Hot Springs National Park in Hot Springs, AR.

It seems we are passing on the sign picture tradition… as everyone wanted a picture of the sign with their camera. The town of Hot Springs was built to capitalize on the hot springs of water coming out of the ground in that area. 
[
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/IMG_0284.jpg)
Numerous bath houses were built here in the early 1900s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trekking Across the USA</title>
      <link>/posts/trekking-across-the-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/trekking-across-the-usa/</guid>
      <description>Saturday we left Nashville and continued further west. Our goal for the day was to reach Ft Smith, AR (on the border of AR and OK) and to visit Hot Springs National Park in Hot Springs, AR. Mission Accomplished
We were in the car from about 9:45am to 11:30pm… with the exception of 3 hours in Hot Springs. No one seemed to mind though. They had video games, movies, books, coloring pages, and crafts to pass the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off to a Great Start</title>
      <link>/posts/off-to-a-great-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/off-to-a-great-start/</guid>
      <description>We started on our grand adventure yesterday morning. We set off a little later than we had hoped due to some storm preparations we had to make in case the forecasted impending storms took out our power while we were gone.
Our plan for day one was to drive from Annapolis, MD to Nashville, TN. Our route took us through DC which was a fun start.

We left our house around 10:15 in the morning and pulled into Scott’s cousins in TN around 10:30pm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
