<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>brothers on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/brothers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in brothers on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 12:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/brothers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Things about My Day at Cub Scout Camp</title>
      <link>/posts/top-10-things-about-my-day-at-cub-scout-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/top-10-things-about-my-day-at-cub-scout-camp/</guid>
      <description>Last week my oldest son went to a week of Cub Scout Day Camp. This year he was a Webelos 1. I remember vividly his first year when he was but a wee Tiger Scout.  He loves Cub Scout camp. And who wouldn’t? 8 and a half hours outside each day, fishing, archery, BB guns, wood shop, specials, crafts…
Each parent is required to volunteer one day. Two years Scott served in this role, last year I went, but it was the last day of camp and I didn’t get to see as much of the action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>While They Were Sleeping</title>
      <link>/posts/while-they-were-sleeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/while-they-were-sleeping/</guid>
      <description>It’s always fun to peek in on my kiddos when they are sleeping. Sometimes because it gives me a good chuckle, sometimes because it tugs at my heart strings, and sometimes just because it sets my mind at ease to see them sleeping snuggly in their rooms. Last night as I was crawling into bed, I realized I hadn’t peeked in on them. I don’t know if I’m the only Mom out there like this, but when I realize I forgot, I just can’t shake it off… I have to go b/c sometimes this little quirky fear will rise up “What if the one night I didn’t check on them something was wrong?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brothers…</title>
      <link>/posts/brothers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/brothers/</guid>
      <description>It’s been really neat to watch the bond between my oldest and youngest. Our baby was the answer to his older brothers prayers, as he longed to have a little brother. I’ll never forget the look of pure joy when he found out he finally had a baby brother. I know he can’t wait for the day when they can truly play together, but for now it is so neat to see the love between them blossom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melt this Momma’s Heart…</title>
      <link>/posts/melt-this-mommas-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/melt-this-mommas-heart/</guid>
      <description>As if the sight of one boy playing the piano, didn’t melt my heart enough…

2 boys just turns me to mush</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
