<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>snow on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/snow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in snow on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 09:34:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/snow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hearts and Snow</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hearts-and-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hearts-and-snow/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the snow fall cancelling our evening activities, we had time to bake and decorate some heart shaped cookies last night.

(it should be noted after my previous post on Red Lake 40… that these cookies were decorated with all natural food dye from Whole Foods)

The snow looked magical as we watched it fall outside our windows. I called the kids down from bed to watch it for a bit and then let them sleep with their blinds open so they could fall asleep watching it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Ice Baby</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ice-ice-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ice-ice-baby/</guid>
      <description>It has been C-O-L-D this past week here in MD. I heard rumors that parts of the bay and various rivers and inlets were freezing. So, this afternoon we took the kids out to see for ourselves. At one of the beaches we visited these ice balls had formed in the river. I had actually seen pictures of them floating earlier this week. Now the ice balls are frozen in to the ice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Beautiful Surprise</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-beautiful-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-beautiful-surprise/</guid>
      <description>I recall seeing something on Facebook before I went to bed about possible flash freezing or snow. But, I didn’t give it much thought.
When I woke up I peeked behind the curtain to see if anything came of it and I gasped. It was that big white puffy snow that sticks to the branches of trees. My most favorite kind of snowfall. And I laid in bed and watched it fall snuggling with my hubby and kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Doesn’t Take Much</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/it-doesnt-take-much/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/it-doesnt-take-much/</guid>
      <description>We were delightfully surprised with some big puffy flakes of snow on Monday afternoon which accumulated to a whopping 1/2 inch of fun for the big 3. 
This was the first “real snow” we’ve had here all winter. The pure, unadulterated glee which this brought to my children caused me to pause and give thanks that we live in MD.

Because it doesn’t snow here all the time (a fact that I am truly, truly grateful for) when it does it is cause for excitement and celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow Week Math</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/snow-week-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/snow-week-math/</guid>
      <description>Thought you might enjoy a little simple math to recap the week here at the circus. Add together the following totals….
 2 major snowstorms 33 inches of snow fallen 1 official blizzard  
 20 cups of hot chocolate drank 2 types of cookies baked  
 1 Daddy sized igloo built  
 1 sledding hill      0 power outages
 1 sleepover with our cousin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My REAL and honest thoughts on all this SNOW</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-real-and-honest-thoughts-on-all-this-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-real-and-honest-thoughts-on-all-this-snow/</guid>
      <description>If your from the midatlantic region (as most of my readers are, b/c I think most of my readers stalk me from facebook) then you have probably seen and read and heard all you want about snow this past week. Seriously, I have scrolled through and looked at gazillions of pictures of face book friends back decks overflowing with snow and seen kids waste high in it, which is kind of funny since I can look out my own windows and see the very same images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Winter Unlike Any I’ve Ever Seen</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-winter-unlike-any-ive-ever-seen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-winter-unlike-any-ive-ever-seen/</guid>
      <description>Most years when I put together our family scrapbooks, our “Fun in the Snow” spread looks something like this. Notice the grass poking through the snow and the pathetic little snowball snowman my son built?
But, this winter has been crazy! We had a record breaking snowfall in December. Then, last week we got a good 6 inches of snowfall (which in any normal MD winter, would have made us giddy with excitement).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Since There’s No Place to Go…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-since-theres-no-place-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-since-theres-no-place-to-go/</guid>
      <description>Let it Snow, Let it Snow, Let it Snow!!!
Growing up and living in the midAtlantic region means that snow is something we are familiar with, but we don’t encounter on a regular basis. It’s not like we’re living in Houston and a dusting of snow occurs once a decade. But, it also isn’t unreasonable that I don’t go out and purchase snow suits for my kids every winter either. We can typically anticipate seeing snowfall at least once a year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
