<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wendy on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/wendy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wendy on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 07:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/wendy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday to Wendy!</title>
      <link>/posts/happy-birthday-to-wendy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/happy-birthday-to-wendy/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday the family celebrated our beloved pup’s 1st birthday. We gave her a giant bone at lunch and after dinner we all enjoyed some Wendy’s Jr Frosties…. seemed fitting. We even presented her with a new squeak toy.
 I have never been a dog person, though I have appreciated the canine members of our house. There is something about watching a pup patiently accept the rough love of a toddler that warms a Momma’s heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Precious Moment</title>
      <link>/posts/a-precious-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-precious-moment/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures of our Life</title>
      <link>/posts/pictures-of-our-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pictures-of-our-life/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t had time to really update the blog lately. In fact, I have found my days to be quite full now that we are in full swing with our school and extra curricular activities. Bursting at the seams full. But, I have whipped the camera out a few times, so I decided today to download them and at least try to preserve some memories of everyday life around here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More on the Cat and the Dog</title>
      <link>/posts/more-on-the-cat-and-the-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/more-on-the-cat-and-the-dog/</guid>
      <description>Seems all of my posts recently are animal related, but truthfully, that is Life At The Circus these days… it’s all about the animals. Holding them, taking them potty, fighting over them…

Hands down the youngest two are my biggest animal lovers. My oldest son has taken way more to the cat than he thought though, he was surprised by how snuggly the kitten is and loves to hold her (though he has taken to either wearing layers of shirts or sweaters b/c he is not a fan of the scratching).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Eye Opening Experience</title>
      <link>/posts/an-eye-opening-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/an-eye-opening-experience/</guid>
      <description>I couldn’t believe how many old clichés took on a whole new meaning and relevancy to Scott and I last night when we welcomed our cat into our family. When I responded to the ad on Craigs List, I asked if there were any female kittens still available. She replied, that I was the first to respond to her ad, and so I could have the pick of the liter if I wanted to stop by that evening and take a look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Family is a Growing</title>
      <link>/posts/the-circus-family-is-a-growing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-circus-family-is-a-growing/</guid>
      <description>Since the passing of our beloved dog Maggie, there has been a void in our home. I missed her immensely more than I ever anticipated. And while no dog could ever replace her or what she meant to our family, we felt it time to once again hear the pitter patter of doggie feet in the circus home. But, we needed to wait until we were home from our grand adventure before welcoming a new pup to the family.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
