<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>national parks on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/national-parks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in national parks on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 18:29:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/national-parks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Another National Park – St. John USVI</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/another-national-park-st.-john-usvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/another-national-park-st.-john-usvi/</guid>
      <description>When we found out the itinerary for the family cruise, Scott and I were super excited to see that the ship would be stopping at St Thomas… this meant that we could take an excursion to St John and visit US Virgin Island National Park!!!
That’s right, another vacation with a sign pic for the circus crew!!

National parks rarely disappoint and St. John was no exception. St John was our family’s favorite day of the vacation (and there were a lot of good days)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our last National Park for this vacation!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-last-national-park-for-this-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 01:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-last-national-park-for-this-vacation/</guid>
      <description>We left Gana’s house around 11 on Saturday. Our destination was Great Basin National Park in eastern Nevada. Our route was ‘the loneliest highway in America’. It was by far our longest drive of the trip, 8 hours with no midpoint destinations. But, of course, we made a few stops. We were not expecting much. We had mentally interpreted “loneliest highway” as “boringest highway” and thought it was going to be 8 hours of unchanging desert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reuniting with Family at Pinnacles National Park</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/reuniting-with-family-at-pinnacles-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/reuniting-with-family-at-pinnacles-national-park/</guid>
      <description>During our trek across California, we wanted to also make time to see some of Scott’s family that live here. Scott’s aunt, uncle, and his cousin and her family live a few hours from Pinnacles National Park and graciously offered to meet us there and spend time with us at the park.

We met at a restaurant called Togo’s… we had never heard of it before, but Scott’s cousin described it as “like subway only better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiking to the Falls</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hiking-to-the-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hiking-to-the-falls/</guid>
      <description>Scott had been hoping for us to take a hike down from Glacier Point to Yosemite Valley. It would be our longest hike, but it would have been all down hill and we would pass both Nevada and Vernal Falls. Given our kids fascination with water falls, this seemed like a fun hike. Unfortunately, we learned too late that there was no shuttle from Yosemite Valley to Glacier Point, and the only way we could do this plan was if we had pre purchased tickets for a special shuttle that left early in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One of America’s Best</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-of-americas-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-of-americas-best/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I visited Yosemite 14 years ago during our trip which shaped all trips. Therefore, it wasn’t a must see for this vacation. And when Scott and I were first plotting out this trip, we kind of waivered as to whether we wanted to include it or not. But, we decided that since Yosemite is one of the quintessential parks and since we were were were going to be SO CLOSE, we owed it to the kids to show them Yosemite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Island Bound!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/island-bound/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/island-bound/</guid>
      <description>This trip seems to be all about extremes and remoteness. Channel Islands National Park is a group of islands located off the coast of Los Angeles. A visit here gives one a glimpse of what the California coast looked like before it was overpopulated with humanity. You can find vegetation and wild life here that doesn’t exist anywhere else. The signature element of the park however is the rocky cliffs along the waters edge and the marine life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Lady Liberty Up Close</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/seeing-lady-liberty-up-close/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/seeing-lady-liberty-up-close/</guid>
      <description>It was super fun to take the kids to see the “Statue of the Liberty” on the first day of our vacation.

It was a cloudy and overcast day so the picture of the Manhattan skyline don’t pop with color, but it was still really neat to see the skyline from this vantage point.

At first we couldn’t figure out why our youngest would lay down on the ground when we were at the base of the pedestal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Park (for a long while)</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/last-park-for-a-long-while/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2013 06:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/last-park-for-a-long-while/</guid>
      <description>Well, I am really sad to say our trip is winding down. We visited the last National Park of our vacation and we can count the number of days left on our trip on one hand. The last park on this grand vacation was Badlands National Park in South Dakota. 
We hit the Badlands on a great day and a great time of day. The sun was low in the sky making the colors pop out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animals, Animals, Everywhere!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/animals-animals-everywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/animals-animals-everywhere/</guid>
      <description>Saturday we left Mt Rushmore and drove 4.5 hours north to Theodore Roosevelt National Park in Medora, ND. A visit to this park meant an approximately 9 hour driving detour from what could have otherwise been a short hop from Mt. Rushmore to the SD Badlands. Sometimes a quest such as our forces your hand to take some pretty circuitous routes… we set off not exactly sure what the ND badlands had to offer that the SD badlands did not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wind Cave Take 2</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wind-cave-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wind-cave-take-2/</guid>
      <description>11 years ago when Scott and I did our first National Park/Cross Country trip, we drove through Wind Caves National Park. We hadn’t yet begun our quest to see every National Park, so we actually just drove through the park and enjoyed the prairie dogs and buffalo. It was literally a stop on our way, not a destination in itself. This time, Scott and I wanted to see the park the right way and go on a cave tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Whole Lotta Sand</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-whole-lotta-sand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2013 08:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-whole-lotta-sand/</guid>
      <description>We arrived at Great Sand Dunes National Park in the middle of the night so our first view of the dunes was when we opened up our tent the next morning. We thought for sure we wouldn’t be able to get a site since they were first come first serve and we were so very late. But once again we were blessed with a camp site in the park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Jam Packed 24 hours</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-jam-packed-24-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-jam-packed-24-hours/</guid>
      <description>We left Canyonlands mid day on Monday and got a hotel in Montrose, Co. We were greeted with a fabulous view of the snow topped Rocky Mts. Scott took the kids swimming while I did laundry. Then we splurged and went out for dinner at Applebees. It was a welcome change from fast food/Subway. The next day we hit Black Canyon of the Gunnison!

This was a hard park to fully comprehend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking in their Footsteps</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/walking-in-their-footsteps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 21:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/walking-in-their-footsteps/</guid>
      <description>We arrived in Mesa Verde National Park a few hours before sunset. We had been hoping to catch the Twilight Tour of Cliff Palace but tickets are sold on a first come basis and, much like we expected, we weren&amp;rsquo;t the first to come. We opted for a sunset drive along the loop with some pretty overlooks and booked tours for the following morning. 
The sunset drive was really fascinating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It really is that GRAND</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/it-really-is-that-grand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/it-really-is-that-grand/</guid>
      <description>11 years ago this month Scott and I visited The Grand Canyon. It was my first time seeing it and it took my breath away. Now, 31 parks later, it is still my favorite of all the National Parks. Many rank high on my list, but if you could only see one, I feel like this should be the one.

The day before we took the kids, I had a little fear, much like the fear I had before taking them to Disney World.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beneath the Rim</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/beneath-the-rim/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 04:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/beneath-the-rim/</guid>
      <description>The highlight of our day at the Grand Canyon for most of the members of our circus crew was a short hike they took into the canyon. 
We all started on the hike, but it was more than this “fraid’ of heights Momma” could handle. The plan was to go to the first tunnel and back, but after about 2 treks on the switchback, I was biting back tears and hating EVERY second of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Step Back in Time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-step-back-in-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-step-back-in-time/</guid>
      <description>Thursday we spent the day at Petrified Forest National Park, located in the painted desert of Arizona.

Here the kids worked hard to earn their Junior Ranger badges. We spent quite a bit of time learning and researching in the visitors center. 
We also took a walk to look at the petrified wood. 
We then drove through the Painted Desert. It was beautiful to see all the layers of colored dirt deposited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Desert Experience</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-desert-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-desert-experience/</guid>
      <description>The kids were so excited to finally get to go camping. Day 6 of our adventure and it was our first night setting up a tent. The kids LOVE the head flashlights I picked up before we left. 
Unfortunately, we discovered we neglected to pack the poles with our tent. So we had a family meeting round the picnic table. We had 3 options. 1. Go to Walmart, get a new tent and come back and set it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Saguaro</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-great-saguaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-great-saguaro/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday we left New Mexico and headed south west for Saguaro National Park in Tuscon, AZ.

We got to Saguaro National Park in time to explore a bit and then take in the parks beauty after the oppressive heat of the day was past. It really was perfect timing. We walked around a path near the visitors center which allowed us to see the cacti up close. 
The cacti were much bigger than we expected and we were delighted to find some in bloom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Like it Hot</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-like-it-hot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-like-it-hot/</guid>
      <description>The first national park on this grand adventure was Hot Springs National Park in Hot Springs, AR.

It seems we are passing on the sign picture tradition… as everyone wanted a picture of the sign with their camera. The town of Hot Springs was built to capitalize on the hot springs of water coming out of the ground in that area. 
[
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/IMG_0284.jpg)
Numerous bath houses were built here in the early 1900s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Infamous Sign Pictures</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-infamous-sign-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-infamous-sign-pictures/</guid>
      <description>I know I’ve posted some of them before, but as we prepare to add 11 new pictures to our collection, I thought I’d post the pictures we currently have in our flip book.
2002










2003



2005

2006



2007



2009



2010



2011

I had so much fun looking back over these pictures and recalling the stories behind them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Trip that Shaped Our Lives</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-trip-that-shaped-our-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-trip-that-shaped-our-lives/</guid>
      <description>You know how sometimes a movie or book will portray how one decision or one event changed the momentum and current of the character’s entire life?
Well for Scott and I, that momentum shifting/life altering event was our vacation in 2002. Somehow or other we got to talking about cross country trips. And somehow an idea blossomed for a large out west vacation. We had a huge map of the US in our laundry room and we began plotting our course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One Where I Question Our Sanity and Whine Like a Baby</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-one-where-i-question-our-sanity-and-whine-like-a-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-one-where-i-question-our-sanity-and-whine-like-a-baby/</guid>
      <description>When a tour company approaches you as you board their boat offering the chance to back out with a full refund, a normal person would heed the warning, take the money and run.
But we aren’t normal. Because we have a quest to visit every national park during our married life together. And this quest brought us all the way down to Key West. And we didn’t drive all the way down to Key West only to turn around and head 100 miles north without first taking a boat 70 nautical miles further west to Dry Tortugas National Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short but Sweet</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/short-but-sweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/short-but-sweet/</guid>
      <description>Our time at Biscayne National Park was fun, but way too short. We took a 3 hour tour (which thankfully turned out much better than the infamous 3 hr tour). I think the kids favorite part was the 45 minute ride out to Boca Chita Island. They described their ride out their as “the best rollar coaster ride ever!” The wind was really blowing. I thought it felt much like those super sonic hand dryers that look like they are ripping your skin off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everglades National Park</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everglades-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everglades-national-park/</guid>
      <description>When we arrived at Everglades NP it was shortly before midnight and raining quite hard. Scott got out of the van to attempt to put up the tent, but when he remembered the top of our tent is open screen (which we then put a cover over after set up) he realized it would be futile as the entire inside of the tent would be soaked before we even set it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because I’m Crazy Like That</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/because-im-crazy-like-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/because-im-crazy-like-that/</guid>
      <description>It’s been almost a year since our grand Texas vacation and already I’ve got the planning bug for another grand circus family trek. Remember how I thought we’d just swing by Houston since we’d be in El Paso? Well, I have similar aspirations for a trip to California in the fall. (I know originally I’d been thinking we’d do a Florida trip, but baby number 4 has changed that aspiration a bit)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures Can’t Do the Day Justice</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pictures-cant-do-the-day-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pictures-cant-do-the-day-justice/</guid>
      <description>During our recent visit to El Paso, we survived the desert trek to reach Carlsbad Caverns ( number 23 of the 47 U.S. National Parks we plan to visit in our life together). It was a perfect day alone with the man of my dreams exploring and enjoying God’s creation. We spent 5 hours exploring the caves 800 feet below the earth’s surface.
Pictures truly can’t do it justice, but I’ll try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prudent or Paranoid?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/prudent-or-paranoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/prudent-or-paranoid/</guid>
      <description>Our continual quest to visit each of the US National parks, prompted us to take a day trip to Carlsbad caverns while in El Paso this weekend.
Oddly enough we were quite familiar with the route has we were only about 11 miles from there this April when we visited Guadeloupe. To get to Carlsbad from El Paso you travel 138 miles on a rather barren and desolate road in the desert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Bend: From Sunup to Sundown</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/big-bend-from-sunup-to-sundown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/big-bend-from-sunup-to-sundown/</guid>
      <description>The sun’s rays cast a bright orange glow on the rocks when it rose in the morning.

As the day went on, the bees came out to pollinate the flora.

As the day progressed, we were able to pose for the very significant sign shot. Click here to learn of it’s high importance.

As the sun began to set the rocks began to change color yet again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
