<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sisters on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/sisters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sisters on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 08:52:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/sisters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finishing Strong</title>
      <link>/posts/finishing-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/finishing-strong/</guid>
      <description>This weekend marked the end of the gymnastics season for my girls. They both finished the season strong scoring personal bests on more than one event. After the meet I ran into the grocery store to buy some brownie mix to celebrate and I was literally beaming from ear to ear. I felt like I wanted to tell everyone I saw about my girls success. I restrained myself though.
However, I do want to record my emotions and thoughts on here to look back on later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“We are Scientists”</title>
      <link>/posts/we-are-scientists/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/we-are-scientists/</guid>
      <description>This week I took my girls on a field trip with their classmates from our tutorial. We visited a Science Center run by the local school system. The kids learned how to observe the world around them and record those observations. They studied bugs and wild life found in our area as well as learned about camouflage and even played a game to reinforce the concept.
They got to use almost all of their senses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Moment in Time</title>
      <link>/posts/a-moment-in-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-moment-in-time/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday afternoon the girls got their baby dolls and strollers and headed to the court to walk their babies. I don’t know what it was about that particular moment in time, but it struck a chord in this Momma’s heart and made me all sappy. 
As I watched them pushing their dolls and pretending they were walking to China… with a stop in Tennessee for some Chick-Fil-A, I found myself longing to take in the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Muffins and Memories for Breakfast</title>
      <link>/posts/making-muffins-and-memories-for-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/making-muffins-and-memories-for-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>Not sure which I like best about this snapshot, the smiles on the girls faces, my daughters hand in the peanut butter jar or my son sneaking yet another lick out of the bowl….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisters Sleeping Side by Side</title>
      <link>/posts/sisters-sleeping-side-by-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sisters-sleeping-side-by-side/</guid>
      <description>More times than not, when I peek in on my girls before heading to bed, I find them sleeping together. Sometimes this means they are both down on the bottom bunk.

Sometimes, it means they are side by side in their drawers (truthfully I find them like this almost as often as I find them in the bottom bunk). 

Sometimes they are both on the floor. (haven’t found them like that in the last 2 weeks)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Perfect 10!</title>
      <link>/posts/a-perfect-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-perfect-10/</guid>
      <description>One day my 4 year old came to me with about 8 pony tail holders and asked me to put them all in her hair. I was surprised with how cute it turned out and she was excited when she received compliments on it from her friend at church. After realizing how well it stayed in, I decided it might be worth trying this for gymnastics. (this is it after a night of sleep)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisterly Love</title>
      <link>/posts/sisterly-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sisterly-love/</guid>
      <description>Nothing like a surprise package of clothes in the mail to bring smiles to the girls faces and provide an impromptu photo opp. (the boys appreciated it too, but not to the same extent)



Thanks cousins Ben and Eli!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Birthday Buddy</title>
      <link>/posts/my-birthday-buddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-birthday-buddy/</guid>
      <description>Growing up, part of me wished for a sister… one to share a room with, share clothes and secrets with…. maybe if I’d have had one, I would know better how to braid my girls hair… I had a great brother, and I would never have traded him for a sister, yet part of me at times felt like I was missing out a little…
When I married Scott I instantly gained in my sister-in-law the sister I had always wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proud Momma</title>
      <link>/posts/proud-momma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/proud-momma/</guid>
      <description>My girls had their Mini Olympics Show yesterday afternoon and I gotta tell you, I was one proud Momma as I watched them perform. Their class did a floor routine (which was super cute to watch) and then each girl had a chance to perform on the bars, trampoline, and tumble track. 


The event concluded with a trip to the medal stand for each girl and then the opportunity to pose for pictures afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Busy…</title>
      <link>/posts/keeping-busy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/keeping-busy/</guid>
      <description>People often ask me what the girls do while I am doing homeschooling with my oldest child.

On Tuesday the answer was “take all the cushions off the couch and every single blanket and pillow they owned and build a fort”


 If I am distracted enough they even smoke a stogie or two in their fort. (just kidding those would be pretzel rods…I promise, but doesn’t this bottom picture look sketchy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sparkle of a True Princess</title>
      <link>/posts/the-sparkle-of-a-true-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-sparkle-of-a-true-princess/</guid>
      <description>“Momma, don’t we look beautiful?”
As I praised them for their lovely fashion choices and snapped picture upon picture of their dress up fun, it dawned on me that this was an opportunity to reinforce what true beauty is. Ya know, I said. To be truly beautiful, you have to be kind and loving to others. In fact, you can be wearing the prettiest dress ever, but if you act mean and unkind to others, you aren’t beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Priceless</title>
      <link>/posts/priceless/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/priceless/</guid>
      <description>Container of dish soap: $2.00

Chip in my favorite coffee mug: $10.00

Keeping 2 sisters happy and entertained for an hour: Priceless</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Visions of Super Bowl Victories Dance in Their Heads. . .</title>
      <link>/posts/and-visions-of-super-bowl-victories-dance-in-their-heads.-.-./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/and-visions-of-super-bowl-victories-dance-in-their-heads.-.-./</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even Princesses Have to Work</title>
      <link>/posts/even-princesses-have-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/even-princesses-have-to-work/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisters</title>
      <link>/posts/sisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sisters/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite things about parenting, is watching my children interact with each other (when they aren’t fighting that is). It’s fascinating to me to see the differences in their bonds and relationships. One relationship which I have observed recently growing is that between my two girls. 

With only 17 mths, and a few inches and pounds between them, they are in so many ways peers. They share much in common, and yet are so very different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Pretty, Pretty Princesses</title>
      <link>/posts/our-pretty-pretty-princesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-pretty-pretty-princesses/</guid>
      <description>Visit here or here for more fun with pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross Country Fashion Consult</title>
      <link>/posts/cross-country-fashion-consult/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cross-country-fashion-consult/</guid>
      <description>As I’ve already made well aware, I am not exactly a fashion guru. You won’t find me flipping through the pages of Cosmopolitan in my free time. My nails are rarely done and my idea of styling my hair involves taking the time to blow dry rather than air dry.
I wanted to look cute when Scott and I went on a date a few weeks ago. I was so excited because my friend had just lent me some adorable maternity clothes so I didn’t really give my thought to my wardrobe till about 30 min before we were going to leave when I began to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Role Reversal</title>
      <link>/posts/role-reversal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/role-reversal/</guid>
      <description>The other night at dinner my daughter was not so excited about eating her peas.

So, her little sister decided to step in and help her!

Sisters make everything better… even eating your greens!

Sometimes you just need a little encouragement!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe for a Good Time</title>
      <link>/posts/recipe-for-a-good-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2009 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/recipe-for-a-good-time/</guid>
      <description>Two cookies
 One mug of milk
 
And two sisters

Visit 5M4M  and Angie’s 7 Ring Circus for more Picture Fun!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
