<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>traditions on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/traditions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in traditions on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 18:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/traditions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Fun!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/halloween-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/halloween-fun/</guid>
      <description>What a Night!

We had a super fun Halloween evening this year and I am thankful we got to know several of our neighbors better. This year we had
Harry Potter 
Super Girl (yes she has been Supergirl for 1/3 of our Halloween’s but what can I say, the girl likes being super girl) This year she changed it up and went with pink super girl though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Preview</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pumpkin-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pumpkin-preview/</guid>
      <description>We carved our pumpkins tonight….


My second born has always been my tactile child. She loves getting her hands messy… she’s the one who loves the feel of dirt on her skin and apparently is also fond of pumpkin guts on her fingers. She happily squished and sorted seeds.

Her sister was less thrilled with the feel of pumpkin guts on her hands.

But,we were all happy with how the jack-o-lanterns turned out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fall Favorite</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-fall-favorite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-fall-favorite/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love apple picking with my kiddos. 
This year I found a great price on delicious locally grown honey crisp apples at the local grocery store and we enjoyed them all fall and I was so tempted to skip out on apple picking b/c we had already enjoyed such delicious apples this fall. But apple picking is about so much more than the apples for me.
It’s the memories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steelers Fans for Life</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/steelers-fans-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 05:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/steelers-fans-for-life/</guid>
      <description>It’s hard enough not living in the home town of your favorite sports team. Even harder than that, is living in the town of the ARCH RIVAL of your favorite sports team. One way that I think we as a family have connected and stayed connected with our Steelers roots, is by making the trek to training camp as often as possible. We missed the last two years, but we went often enough over the past 10 years that the big 3 all remember going and talk about going and consider it a tradition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blueberries!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/blueberries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/blueberries/</guid>
      <description>I love, LOVE picking fruit with the kiddos. Apple picking in the fall and strawberry picking in the spring are two of my favorite annual excursions with them. I was delighted when I found out that a family from our tutorial owns a pick your own blueberry patch. The younger three and I went Monday morning while my oldest was a day camp with the cub scouts. 
I hope to go back with all four of them and really stock up on some berries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Tradition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-favorite-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-favorite-tradition/</guid>
      <description>We got our tree today!!! 
We started decorating the house yesterday, but it wasn’t quite right without the tree. I don’t think our three year old remembers the Christmas tree b/c after we cut it down and tied it to our van he asked, “Can we keep it in our yard as our Christmas tree?” He had no idea it would go in the house. And then when we added lights, he was beyond excited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Infamous Sign Pictures</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-infamous-sign-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-infamous-sign-pictures/</guid>
      <description>I know I’ve posted some of them before, but as we prepare to add 11 new pictures to our collection, I thought I’d post the pictures we currently have in our flip book.
2002










2003



2005

2006



2007



2009



2010



2011

I had so much fun looking back over these pictures and recalling the stories behind them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Trip that Shaped Our Lives</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-trip-that-shaped-our-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-trip-that-shaped-our-lives/</guid>
      <description>You know how sometimes a movie or book will portray how one decision or one event changed the momentum and current of the character’s entire life?
Well for Scott and I, that momentum shifting/life altering event was our vacation in 2002. Somehow or other we got to talking about cross country trips. And somehow an idea blossomed for a large out west vacation. We had a huge map of the US in our laundry room and we began plotting our course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling for Fall</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/falling-for-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 06:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/falling-for-fall/</guid>
      <description>As much as I hate the cold, I really am a 4 seasons kind of girl. I love the beginning of a new season…. bringing out favorite clothes, decorations, foods, traditions only enjoyed for a season. It’s refreshing and exciting and makes me so grateful for the climate we live in. But, this year, more than most I have been crazy excited about fall. I can’t explain it. But, I’m more giddy than normal about pulling out my jeans and boots and sweaters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving Thanks</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/giving-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/giving-thanks/</guid>
      <description>The 4th of July kind of reminds me of Thanksgiving. I think the two go hand and hand really. Because as we celebrate the birth of our nation, our independence and our freedom, how can we not give thanks? We have so much that we’ve grown to believe we’re entitled to all of it and more. In the midst of a fun filled day of family and friends, of parades, and flags, burgers and hot dogs, fire works and red-white-and-blue, I want to pause a few minutes to reflect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hunt</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Countless “winter” afternoons were spent sporting flip flops, eating picnic lunches outside, soaking in the warmth of the sun’s rays. And I loved every minute of it, while also inwardly fearing a return of cold weather. I so hate that time of year when you have to keep both warm and cold weather clothes in your drawers because you never know what the weather will do. I love it when you can confidently box up last seasons clothes and fully embrace the new season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Best House Yet</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-best-house-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-best-house-yet/</guid>
      <description>We decorated our gingerbread house this weekend…before Christmas this year—astonishing, I know.
The big 3 had a fabulous time.


Unfortunately, our youngest found the experience quite confusing and a tad frustrating. “Why, oh why, aren’t they letting me eat that candy?”

I might have snuck the lil guy a few pieces of candy while they were busy working.


The kids were quite proud of their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hard Way</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-hard-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-hard-way/</guid>
      <description>When cutting down a tree, much like when shopping for a dress, there seems to be an unwritten rule of conduct.
No matter how fabulous it looks, you simply can’t go with the first one you see.
One simply can’t drive to the farm, march down the aisle, and stop at the first decent looking spruce you see.
That would be far too easy. Where would the fun be in that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Dad</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-date-with-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-date-with-dad/</guid>
      <description>I got my love of sports from my dad. I can remember watching Pirates games at 5 when he was out of town, just to make me feel closer to him. In high school, my dad would take me to Penn State Football games to watch my cousin play in the Blue Band. I think my dad made sure that we attended every kind of professional sporting event at least once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Hey, Hey, Goodbye!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hey-hey-hey-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hey-hey-hey-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>So long summer 2010….
We’ll forever hold you close in our heart for you were the summer that we welcomed dear sweet, squeezable number 4 to our fold.

We enjoyed your lazy hazy days as we spent time playing in our back yard and splashing in our pool…

We enjoyed time with family



We caught our first keeper… and enjoyed time on Nana and Pop’s boat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
