<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>thankful on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/thankful/</link>
    <description>Recent content in thankful on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 06:51:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/thankful/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our Half Life Anniversary Excursion</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-half-life-anniversary-excursion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 06:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-half-life-anniversary-excursion/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I started dating our senior year of high school, when we were both 17. A few years ago we were out for an anniversary date and realized that we were approaching the point in our life when we would have been together as much of our life as we weren’t together. We decided we wanted to celebrate such a momentous occasion and so we (and by we, I really mean Scott) calculated out when exactly that would be… our dates are different since we don’t share the same birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ringing in a New Year</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ringing-in-a-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ringing-in-a-new-year/</guid>
      <description>It’s funny how our New Years Eve festivities have changed through the years. Scott and I have never been big party animals, but we did go to downtown Pittsburgh on Dec 31, 1999 to ring in the new millennium with a kiss on the Roberto Clemente bridge. For several years we would watch the fireworks in Annapolis at midnight.
Then we had kids.
And New Years became a stay at home night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Year Later</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-year-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-year-later/</guid>
      <description>A year ago today Scott and I dropped the kids off at a friends house and went to sign on the dotted line about 20 gazillion times. We left with keys to our new home!
Scott and I headed to the new place to enjoy some take out Chinese on the back deck as we celebrated the immense blessing of this new home. Then as is the case quite often for us… our busy lives resumed… Scott back to work… me to grab some stuff from our old house to bring to our new house for our camp out that night… then we met up at the gym for our daughter’s Mini Olympics performance and I think we might have had a little league baseball game in there too… we got home much later that evening…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving Thanks</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/giving-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/giving-thanks/</guid>
      <description>The 4th of July kind of reminds me of Thanksgiving. I think the two go hand and hand really. Because as we celebrate the birth of our nation, our independence and our freedom, how can we not give thanks? We have so much that we’ve grown to believe we’re entitled to all of it and more. In the midst of a fun filled day of family and friends, of parades, and flags, burgers and hot dogs, fire works and red-white-and-blue, I want to pause a few minutes to reflect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humbled and Grateful</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/humbled-and-grateful/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/humbled-and-grateful/</guid>
      <description>These past few weeks have been some of the most exhausting in my life. It’s been 9 years and 4 kids since our last move and let’s just say we’ve acquired a whole lot more stuff since our last move. I purged and donated and purged some more and yet have found myself with enough miscellaneous boxes of random to sort through in the new house till Labor Day! Meanwhile we were listing our house for rent, showing it to perspective renters AND still trying to juggle the spring extra curriculars like year end home school evaluations, baseball games, gymnastics classes, play off games, mini Olympics, piano recitals, and birthdays and our anniversary.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
