<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>flashbacks on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/flashbacks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in flashbacks on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 12:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/flashbacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deja Vu</title>
      <link>/posts/deja-vu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/deja-vu/</guid>
      <description>My kids have gotten the Minecraft bug. Started first with my oldest son. He shared the obsession with my 6 year old daughter… and then even my child who doesn’t really like to play games, joined in the fight against zombies. Yesterday they finally figured out how to do multi player, which means they can all play at the same time on various different wireless devices in the same world. Giggles could be heard as they found each other walking around in their worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Dad</title>
      <link>/posts/my-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-dad/</guid>
      <description>With Fathers Day approaching this weekend and the kids and I brainstorming ways to make it ultra special for the circus dad, I feel it also appropriate to spend some time reflecting on my own father.
Because, when it comes to dad’s, I have been richly blessed. While in the throws of parenthood, I think many a parents wonders, “Is it making a difference? Do my kids even notice?” And the answer is a resounding “Yes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poor Dad, Get’s No Respect</title>
      <link>/posts/poor-dad-gets-no-respect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/poor-dad-gets-no-respect/</guid>
      <description>While capturing this “precious” Father/Son moment the other day…
 my mind instantly flashed back to a similar “bonding” moment between father and son which I captured 6 years ago…

Seems both my boys enjoy sticking their tongues out at dear old Dad!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Far We’ve Come</title>
      <link>/posts/how-far-weve-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-far-weve-come/</guid>
      <description>Today I’d like to give a shout out to my maternal grandmother, whom I have lovingly called, “Mema” for as long as I can remember. I have this vivid picture in my mind of me in high school showing her and my Pap how to work our computer. I recall her being completely baffled by it and saying something to the effect of, “You’ll never catch me on that thing!” I remembered there being a picture of the event and when my parents were visiting last week I asked my mom if she knew where it was.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
