<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>craft on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/craft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in craft on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 10:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/craft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>We Need a Little Art</title>
      <link>/posts/we-need-a-little-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/we-need-a-little-art/</guid>
      <description>We are on break here at the circus. And I couldn’t be more excited about it. I have been looking forward to this week for ages. The week before Christmas. All I want to do is enjoy the kiddos and catch up on some house work. And bake. And do some shopping. And maybe see some friends. (ha, ha… can you tell I am an introvert? read over that list, when I proof read this and re read it, it made me laugh)…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping the Peace</title>
      <link>/posts/keeping-the-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/keeping-the-peace/</guid>
      <description>My kids love to draw and color and cut and create. And they are always, always, always asking me for paper. When my 4 year old doodled all over my check book, I knew I had to come up with something better. One day I stared at our empty popcorn tin and an idea hit me. For some reason the tin seemed perfect for storing crayons. Wouldn’t it be great, I thought, if we could have a roll of paper on our table like at Macaroni Grill?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Finally Found My Niche in the Craft World</title>
      <link>/posts/i-finally-found-my-niche-in-the-craft-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/i-finally-found-my-niche-in-the-craft-world/</guid>
      <description>You all know that the really talented crafty genes somehow skipped over me in the family tree. My girls are not going to get their wedding dress sewn by their Momma like I did. In fact there is a lot of doubt as to whether or not they’ll ever get the pajama pants I set out to sew them a year ago. But, I think I may have stumbled across a medium which I can do, and do with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
