<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>recipes on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in recipes on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 17:38:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>St Patty’s Day Fun</title>
      <link>/posts/st-pattys-day-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/st-pattys-day-fun/</guid>
      <description>I typically enjoy donning some green (and forcing encouraging my family to do the same) and serving an Irish fare on the 17th of March. I thought I’d share some of our traditions with you today, as well as some new recipes I got from some friends on face book, in case you wanted to try some at your home on Wednesday. I’m always eager to try new traditions and activities at the circus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Cooking at the Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/whats-cooking-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/whats-cooking-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>I have found that by planning my meals for the month, I can drastically reduce our families grocery spending. It takes time and a whole lot of effort though. And to be honest the past several months I wasn’t so good about it. But, then Scott and I sat down and took a look at our spending. And we realized that we needed to be a whole lot better about sticking to our budget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Cookie Exchange: Saltine Brittle</title>
      <link>/posts/christmas-cookie-exchange-saltine-brittle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/christmas-cookie-exchange-saltine-brittle/</guid>
      <description>This year, I was looking for something simple and inexpensive that the kids could work together with me to make for their teachers. Too much to ask? I hoped not, but nothing was coming to me. And then I remembered this brittle that someone had brought to MOPS a few years ago. It uses saltine crackers. And you can pick up a box of Saltines at Aldi’s for 89 cents… which is perfect since I have to make gifts for SS and Bible Study teachers (times 3) plus neighbors and the tutorial teacher and “don’t forget my gymnastic teacher Mom!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving Recipes: Old and New</title>
      <link>/posts/thanksgiving-recipes-old-and-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2009 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/thanksgiving-recipes-old-and-new/</guid>
      <description>This year the Thanksgiving menu held some old favs and some new favs as well. Thought I’d share the recipes so you could stick em in your box for next year, or for later this holiday season.
My mom’s apple pie is by far my most favorite apple pie in the world. In fact, I am an apple pie snob and won’t eat any other pie but her recipe. Because, once you’ve had this one, no others compare in my opinion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gana’s French Toast</title>
      <link>/posts/ganas-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ganas-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>I love my husband’s Nana. She’s a remarkable lady. I loved her for years, just based on hearing about her from her grandson and reading her sweet letters. Then, I flew to California and met her. And I loved her as my own Nana!! When I walked in her side door, I instantly felt at home. I sat down at her table and never wanted to leave again.
Gana (as my kids call her b/c she is their Great Nana) is famous for her quince jam, her tacos, and her French toast (among many other things).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camp Fire Donuts</title>
      <link>/posts/camp-fire-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/camp-fire-donuts/</guid>
      <description>This recipe for warm and gooey deliciousness is courtesy of Scott’s college room mate. It’s not as easy as popping a mallow on a stick and roasting it, but it is oh so worth the effort! You must try camp fire donuts on your next over night camping trip&amp;hellip;
First you take a can of Pillsbury breadsticks (or a generic equivalent)

Pop it open

Then you begin to wrap the bread dough around a stick</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sweet Taste of Success</title>
      <link>/posts/the-sweet-taste-of-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2009 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-sweet-taste-of-success/</guid>
      <description>Those of you that have been part of the circus for awhile, know that I seriously lack a green thumb. I guess you could call me naive, but this spring I decided to try again. Much like peach picking, my goal in gardening is to teach my kids. So, I didn’t go for huge garden with hopes of providing a summer’s worth of produce. Instead, I opted for a few plants that we could watch grow and hopefully taste the fruits of our labor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Jam Circus Style</title>
      <link>/posts/making-jam-circus-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/making-jam-circus-style/</guid>
      <description>If you’re anything like me, you don’t really need one more reason to enjoy carbs. Yet, I can’t help but share my favorite. One of my mom’s most highly requested recipes growing up was for her strawberry jam. She always got a kick out it when people asked her if she would please share it.
So, here’s the family secret.
Yup, buy yourself a box of Sure Jell, add 4 cups of crushed berries, and 4 cups of sugar, and you are set!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pomp and Circumstance</title>
      <link>/posts/pomp-and-circumstance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pomp-and-circumstance/</guid>
      <description>I can’t believe the school year is over all ready. More than that I can’t believe my little guy is going to be a kindergartener next fall. Where did the time go? It truly seems like it wasn’t that long ago when he was taking his first steps. And now he’ll be stepping across the stage…ready to commence a new stage of life.
He is no longer a preschooler.
I’m so proud of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circus Menu</title>
      <link>/posts/circus-menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/circus-menu/</guid>
      <description>Between baseball practice, swim lessons, sailing races, and deacon meetings, our evenings can get quite busy. And one thing my family is passionate about is their food. Not so keen on skipping diner. So, to keep dinner on the table, I have found it is helpful to have a plan. I must confess I used to be much better about the plan. I’d write up my meal plan for the month and then make my grocery list based on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert for Breakfast</title>
      <link>/posts/dessert-for-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 05:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dessert-for-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>One of my hubby’s fav breakfast foods is my home made coffee cake. I often make it for him on special occasions like Valentine’s Day, our anniversary, or his birthday.
Because you can make it the night before, it is great to serve for overnight guests. Or for freakishly early breakfast guests like I had this weekend. My son had a 9:30 baseball game on Saturday and we had invited my husband’s extended family over for breakfast before the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The World’s Most Expensive Pint of Ice Cream</title>
      <link>/posts/the-worlds-most-expensive-pint-of-ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-worlds-most-expensive-pint-of-ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>Besides taking in the beautiful scenery (of which there was much) at Guadalupe and Big Bend National Parks, we really enjoyed being able to just be together (most of the time). Each day at Big Bend we took a very, long picnic lunch. One day we went to the western portion of the park and enjoyed a leisurely picnic. I thought it would be fun to make our own ice cream in coffee cans using a recipe I had found online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Need Some Chocolate??</title>
      <link>/posts/need-some-chocolate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/need-some-chocolate/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been battling some germs here at the circus. Everything from ear infections, stomach bugs, croup, asthma attacks… we seem to have had it all, and then had it again. After this week’s bout of croup went from kid to kid (with the baby waking up today with a fever) I am thinking Momma could use some chocolate. So, during nap time today I plan to whip up some of these (my favs) and enjoy a little chocolate fix while I try to catch up on some blog reading and commenting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Good Cookies Even Better</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-make-good-cookies-even-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-to-make-good-cookies-even-better/</guid>
      <description>Home made chocolate chip cookies are my favorite! I am partial to the recipe my mom got years ago. Perhaps you’ve seen the recipe as well. The story goes someone asked for Mrs. Fields cookie recipe and was told it cost two fifty. Upon receiving the recipe, she learned it cost two hundred and fifty dollars rather than two dollars and fifty cents. Outraged, she went on to share this recipe with the world to get back at them for charging so much.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
