<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>apple picking on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/apple-picking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in apple picking on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 12:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/apple-picking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>His Little Friend the Bee</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/his-little-friend-the-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/his-little-friend-the-bee/</guid>
      <description>While picnicking at the orchard last weekend, a bee made his way to our 4 year olds apple. As it buzzed around and lingered around his hands, Scott thought that it might freak him out so he started to swat it away.
“No Daddy!” our 4 year old protested, “he’s trying to become my friend!”

That’s one we hadn’t heard before…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fall Favorite</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-fall-favorite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-fall-favorite/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love apple picking with my kiddos. 
This year I found a great price on delicious locally grown honey crisp apples at the local grocery store and we enjoyed them all fall and I was so tempted to skip out on apple picking b/c we had already enjoyed such delicious apples this fall. But apple picking is about so much more than the apples for me.
It’s the memories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling for Fall</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/falling-for-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 06:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/falling-for-fall/</guid>
      <description>As much as I hate the cold, I really am a 4 seasons kind of girl. I love the beginning of a new season…. bringing out favorite clothes, decorations, foods, traditions only enjoyed for a season. It’s refreshing and exciting and makes me so grateful for the climate we live in. But, this year, more than most I have been crazy excited about fall. I can’t explain it. But, I’m more giddy than normal about pulling out my jeans and boots and sweaters.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
