<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reading on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reading on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 03:47:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I keep Going Back</title>
      <link>/posts/why-i-keep-going-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 03:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/why-i-keep-going-back/</guid>
      <description>I’ve written time and time again of my hot/cold, love/hate, on again/off again relationship with the library. Despite the fines (and my husband can attest to the fact that we have paid MANY), I keep going back again and again….and the reasons are…

 1. the hush that falls over the circus van on the ride home as everyone is absorbed in their books (I’ve even been known to sit in the van in the parking lot soaking in that silence)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Reluctantly Photographed</title>
      <link>/posts/the-reluctantly-photographed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-reluctantly-photographed/</guid>
      <description>My youngest was sitting on the floor “reading” his choo-choo book to our dog Maggie when I had to grab my camera and snap a picture. He then looks over at me and says, “Aww man, No SMILE!”
I said, “Ok, no smile.” and he happily went back to his reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Reading</title>
      <link>/posts/summer-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/summer-reading/</guid>
      <description>I love to read. I love when you get to that point in the novel, where you literally can not put it down and find yourself speed reading/skipping words just to quickly make it to the next part and find out what happens. One of our goals in educating our children was to make readers out of them. This was hard at first with our son as reading didn’t come naturally to him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melts this Momma’s Heart</title>
      <link>/posts/melts-this-mommas-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/melts-this-mommas-heart/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Date with my Son</title>
      <link>/posts/a-date-with-my-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-date-with-my-son/</guid>
      <description>6 Flags Amusement park offered a free ticket to any K-6 grade student that registered for their Read to Succeed program and completed 6 hrs of non school required reading. As a bonus, the teacher who enrolled the student also got a free ticket. So, that meant this home schooling momma got a ticket for herself and her son to 6 Flags.
I kept track of his reading in the spring and when he completed 6 hrs of recreational reading, unannounced to him, I registered him for the free ticket.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
