<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steelers on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/steelers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steelers on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 05:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/steelers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Steelers Fans for Life</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/steelers-fans-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 05:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/steelers-fans-for-life/</guid>
      <description>It’s hard enough not living in the home town of your favorite sports team. Even harder than that, is living in the town of the ARCH RIVAL of your favorite sports team. One way that I think we as a family have connected and stayed connected with our Steelers roots, is by making the trek to training camp as often as possible. We missed the last two years, but we went often enough over the past 10 years that the big 3 all remember going and talk about going and consider it a tradition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One For the Books</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-for-the-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-for-the-books/</guid>
      <description>My dad called me last week and said he had 3 tickets to the Steelers/Ravens game if we wanted to come join him. His boss had generously given his tickets to my Dad and my parents generously offered to share them with us. I quickly called Scott who said, “Yes, we’ll make it work.” And make it work we did.
Our weekend was already jam packed with commitments so the only way to make it back was to drive from Annapolis to Pittsburgh and back in one day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Long #86</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-long-86/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-long-86/</guid>
      <description>While he wore the jersey for 14 years, she proudly wore hers for 3. (more than half of her life). It was her first jersey and I always thought it suited her personality well.  As we listened live to Hines bid his tearful goodbye to football this afternoon, we were sad to see him go but as my 7 year old pointed out, “thankful he’s not going to play for the Ravens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An End of Summer Tradition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-end-of-summer-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-end-of-summer-tradition/</guid>
      <description>Of the 32 years I’ve been a Steelers fan, I only had the joy of being a hometown fan for only 8 of those years (5 of which I was 5 and under so it doesn’t really count in my book). My sophomore year of college, I moved to PA for 3 years. I was thrilled to get to watch the Steelers on a weekly basis. Unfortunately, this was during the Kordell Stewart, Tommy Maddox era, which wasn’t exactly the Steelers golden era of football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks for a Great Ride</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thanks-for-a-great-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thanks-for-a-great-ride/</guid>
      <description>Well, it’s over… another great football season has has come to an end. While the ending wasn’t quite as sweet as I wanted, it was to be honest, a WHOLE lot better than I thought it would be when the season started. I never dreamed in August that we’d be having a Steelers party in February.
Looking back, it was a great season. We had a ton of fun cheering for our boys in black and gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We ARE ready for some Steelers Football!!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-are-ready-for-some-steelers-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-are-ready-for-some-steelers-football/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been playing the song on repeat for weeks and now the day is here. Pittsburgh isn’t going to the Super Bowl anymore they are AT the Superbowl! And we are ready to cheer them on for their 7th Superbowl victory!

Even our dog Maggie is sporting the black and gold today!

GO STEELERS!!!!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Visions of Super Bowl Victories Dance in Their Heads. . .</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-visions-of-super-bowl-victories-dance-in-their-heads.-.-./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-visions-of-super-bowl-victories-dance-in-their-heads.-.-./</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muted Celebration</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/muted-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/muted-celebration/</guid>
      <description>I’ve never known what it was like to be part of the home town team. Though I was born in Pa, I’ve lived in rival MD since the age of 5, not counting 3 of my 4 years of college. I got my love of football from my dad and my dad brought me up a Steelers girl. I now pass this legacy onto my four children. I just love this pic of our newest Steelers fan, I had to find a reason to sneak this in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Saw the Sign</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-saw-the-sign/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-saw-the-sign/</guid>
      <description>At dinner last night I was telling Scott how cute it is to watch our 3 yr old in gymnastics. Every now and then she’ll look at the observation window, get a big grin and wave to me. Sometimes she’ll even give me a thumbs up sign. At which point she chimed in and said,
“Yea, this means good.”

“And this means Ravens”

What can I say? That’s my girl!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Exactly Something You See Everyday</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-exactly-something-you-see-everyday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 07:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-exactly-something-you-see-everyday/</guid>
      <description>Not everyday you see an Oriole wrapped in a Steelers Terrible Towel. Click here or here for more picture fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Than Just a Game</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/more-than-just-a-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/more-than-just-a-game/</guid>
      <description>Last night I came home from Kids Quest (our church’s evening class for kids in which we teach them the questions from the Shorter Catechism), pizza in hand and Scott and I quickly tag teamed to get the kids in bed so we could hit play and watch the recorded Steelers game. (I seriously think the invention of the DVR has got to go on my top 5 list of inventions that changed my life… I LOVE it)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Football</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/extreme-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 20:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/extreme-football/</guid>
      <description>This weekend in addition to enjoying some fishing and campfire doughnuts, we also got to par take in some Pittsburgh Steelers revelry. While camping is always a good time, the reason for our camping trip was so we could spend the afternoon checking up on our boys in the burgh!
This was Scott and my third trip to Latrobe, PA to watch the Steelers practice at training camp. It’s always fun to see the players you watch and cheer on T.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Savoring our Victory</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/savoring-our-victory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/savoring-our-victory/</guid>
      <description>Since you’ve seen the decor at the circus for the big game, I thought I’d give you a glimpse of the cast members as well.
We had some fun last night, that is FOR SURE!!!
My daughter and her Papa wore their Steelers jackets to church Sunday morning. 
The kids had their faces painted for the game to show some Steelers pride!

Great Grandpa snapped a picture of the hang celebrating during half time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Got Our 6 Pack!!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-got-our-6-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-got-our-6-pack/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superbowl Time!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/superbowl-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/superbowl-time/</guid>
      <description>Since many people have asked how we we are celebrating the Superbowl, I thought I’d give you all a glimpse of the circus on Superbowl Sunday.
We didn’t invite a ton of friends over b/c to be honest, we want to be watching the game and not playing host and hostess. We invited my parents, Scott’s parents, and Scott’s grandfather over to watch the game with us. The rule is you gotta route for Pittsburgh to be welcome here and during the game, there is no talking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’ve Had the Time of My Life…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ive-had-the-time-of-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 07:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ive-had-the-time-of-my-life/</guid>
      <description>Game time 6:30pm on Sunday, January 18, 2009
Scott and I were in our seats by 4:45. We were too excited to stay away any longer. When we looked out into the stadium, it was obvious who the non season ticket holders were. There was a sprinkling of us around the stadium. Rookies eager to enjoy every precious minute of the event. As we sat down in our seat (only three rows back in the upper level) we could see everything!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re Going…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-going/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-going/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I was talking with a friend of mine about the Steelers game. She had offered her condolences on our loss against Tennessee. I told her I wasn’t too worried about it because we were going to the play offs. She looked at my kind of incredulously and asked, “Really?”
“Yea,” I said.
“Your going to the playoffs? That’s crazy.”
I was kinda confused, we were after all the leader of our division, and then it hit me…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here We Go Steelers, Here We Go!!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/here-we-go-steelers-here-we-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 19:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/here-we-go-steelers-here-we-go/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5M4M for more WW</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Those Who Care...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/for-those-who-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/for-those-who-care/</guid>
      <description>I am one happy girl tonight.
Why, you ask?
** The Steelers beat the Ravens **&amp;hellip; and if that wasn&amp;rsquo;t reason enough to rejoice, doing so clinched them a spot in the play offs AND a first round bye.
I had a realization about myself while watching the game though. I don&amp;rsquo;t really enjoy watching the game unless we are winning. Really. I was literally sick to my stomach with worry for much of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Going Head to Head</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-going-head-to-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-going-head-to-head/</guid>
      <description>Update: This round of playoffs takes two weeks. So the winner is decided by totaling the points scored both weeks, and whoever scored the most points goes on to the championship round. Looks like a close one&amp;hellip;Scott scored 80 and I had 76. There is def still time for me to pull out a victory!!
There are 10 teams on our fantasy football league this year. Four teams make it to play offs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Like That!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/crazy-like-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 04:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/crazy-like-that/</guid>
      <description>Sunday my husband and I had plans during the Steelers games. Thankfully we have a DVR, so we just recorded the game to watch when we got home. This has happened before, and we have devised a sort of routine for situations like this, because it would be AWFUL to accidentally find out the results of the game before we watched it. So, we typically race into the house (because what if we see a neighbor and they casually mention the game) we then unplug the phone (because what if a friend or family member calls to talk about it) and we don&amp;rsquo;t turn on the computer (because what if someone e-mailed about it or we saw something on our &amp;ldquo;igoogle headline&amp;rdquo; (since we have Steelers websites in our favorites on our home page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are READY for some FOOTBALL</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-are-ready-for-some-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-are-ready-for-some-football/</guid>
      <description>The Steelers play the Ravens on Monday Night Football tonight on ESPN.
We are so psyched! It is probably my favorite game of the year. If there&amp;rsquo;s anything I enjoy watching more than the Steelers win, it&amp;rsquo;s watching them win against the Ravens. Here&amp;rsquo;s hoping for a good game!! Go STEELERS!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How We Enjoy the Game</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-we-enjoy-the-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-we-enjoy-the-game/</guid>
      <description>Many of you know, that my hubby and I are big Pittsburgh Steelers fans. Sadly, many of the games are not televised here. We didn&amp;rsquo;t want to miss the big opening game on Sunday, so we took the kids to Glory Days restaurant to watch the game.
My hubby and I were a little nervous about how well this would go down. How would we keep 3 kids entertained sitting at a restaurant table for 3 hours?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two of My Favorite Things</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/two-of-my-favorite-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/two-of-my-favorite-things/</guid>
      <description>Updated with new picture from today below
Today I get to celebrate two of my favorite things&amp;hellip;
Chick-Fil-A and Football. :-)
Today, Chick-Fil-A is giving away their new chicken strips (which, by the way, are delicious, and my hubby and my new fav menu item) to anyone who visits their store wearing a football logo. Check it out here for more details.
You better believe that all 5 of us will be sporting our Steelers pride at Chick-Fil-A today when we stop for lunch on our way back from our annual Labor Day get together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Struck</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/star-struck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/star-struck/</guid>
      <description>My hubby and I are huge Pittsburgh Steelers fans. I was born a Steelers fan. My husband&amp;rsquo;s allegiance was born in college when he began faithfully watching the home team in Western, PA. There&amp;rsquo;s no way to distinguish who is more devoted now, we are both hard core. Living in Ravens territory is tough. We watch every game televised here, head to Glory Days for big games that aren&amp;rsquo;t televised, make a few treks to my parents house in PA, read the play by plays online, listen on the radio&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
