<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cartwheel on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/cartwheel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cartwheel on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 14:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/cartwheel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Precious Moment</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-precious-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-precious-moment/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures of our Life</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pictures-of-our-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pictures-of-our-life/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t had time to really update the blog lately. In fact, I have found my days to be quite full now that we are in full swing with our school and extra curricular activities. Bursting at the seams full. But, I have whipped the camera out a few times, so I decided today to download them and at least try to preserve some memories of everyday life around here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More on the Cat and the Dog</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/more-on-the-cat-and-the-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/more-on-the-cat-and-the-dog/</guid>
      <description>Seems all of my posts recently are animal related, but truthfully, that is Life At The Circus these days… it’s all about the animals. Holding them, taking them potty, fighting over them…

Hands down the youngest two are my biggest animal lovers. My oldest son has taken way more to the cat than he thought though, he was surprised by how snuggly the kitten is and loves to hold her (though he has taken to either wearing layers of shirts or sweaters b/c he is not a fan of the scratching).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Eye Opening Experience</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-eye-opening-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-eye-opening-experience/</guid>
      <description>I couldn’t believe how many old clichés took on a whole new meaning and relevancy to Scott and I last night when we welcomed our cat into our family. When I responded to the ad on Craigs List, I asked if there were any female kittens still available. She replied, that I was the first to respond to her ad, and so I could have the pick of the liter if I wanted to stop by that evening and take a look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She got her wish!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/she-got-her-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/she-got-her-wish/</guid>
      <description>Since late last fall, our youngest daughter has been lobbying hard for a cat. She did a school project on one, she drew endless pictures of them, she wrote stories about them, she slept with her stuffed animal cat every night and my favorite was the note she wrote Scott listing all their fine attributes.
 
We waited it out awhile, trying to see if it was merely a passing phase or if it would stick.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
