<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>camping on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/camping/</link>
    <description>Recent content in camping on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 11:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/camping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Ending</title>
      <link>/posts/perfect-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/perfect-ending/</guid>
      <description>The last true day of our vacation (the day before we headed home) was in my opinion the most relaxing day of the week.
We slept in, ate breakfast, (the kids did the dishes), and then we headed out for a morning hike along the beach.
 
The tide was out and we discovered many living creatures in tide pools on the rocky beach
.


We made our way to the other side of the island and even caught a glimpse of the Boston skyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peddocks Island Day 1</title>
      <link>/posts/peddocks-island-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 03:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/peddocks-island-day-1/</guid>
      <description>After our rain delay/rain out, we finally made it to Peddocks Island… one day late. After hiking the LONG hike uphill to our site, I am so glad we didn’t attempt it during the torrential rainstorm.
It was a big enough hassle getting our stuff from the van to the ferry, off the ferry, on to the other ferry, off that ferry, and then up the long hike up hill to our site… but the weather was gorgeous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wind Cave Take 2</title>
      <link>/posts/wind-cave-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wind-cave-take-2/</guid>
      <description>11 years ago when Scott and I did our first National Park/Cross Country trip, we drove through Wind Caves National Park. We hadn’t yet begun our quest to see every National Park, so we actually just drove through the park and enjoyed the prairie dogs and buffalo. It was literally a stop on our way, not a destination in itself. This time, Scott and I wanted to see the park the right way and go on a cave tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He Spoils Us</title>
      <link>/posts/he-spoils-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/he-spoils-us/</guid>
      <description>Time and time again our fourth child has blown us away with his easy going, flexible, happy-go-lucky approach to life. It has made the transition to a family of 6, for this family on-the-go, SO MUCH easier—a fact I am truly, truly grateful for.
This weekend, he really went above and beyond our expectations though.
Not only did he fall asleep in the tent both nights, while the rest of us were out at the camp fire, but he even napped in the tent Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping with the Cub Scouts</title>
      <link>/posts/camping-with-the-cub-scouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/camping-with-the-cub-scouts/</guid>
      <description>This weekend the family went on a Cub Scout camp out from Friday- Saturday evening. The kids have been begging to go camping again, and this over nighter was the perfect little get away for us. As an added convenience it was at a State Park not far from our house, so it was quite easy to pop home if you needed something and made it no big deal when we got a late start on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everglades National Park</title>
      <link>/posts/everglades-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/everglades-national-park/</guid>
      <description>When we arrived at Everglades NP it was shortly before midnight and raining quite hard. Scott got out of the van to attempt to put up the tent, but when he remembered the top of our tent is open screen (which we then put a cover over after set up) he realized it would be futile as the entire inside of the tent would be soaked before we even set it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Plans Change</title>
      <link>/posts/when-plans-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/when-plans-change/</guid>
      <description>When things didn’t work out for us to go camping this weekend as planned, we promised the kids a night of “camping-like” fun at home. Scott came home from work a little early and we cooked up hot dogs and baked beans (a fav here at the circus).
Then we spent the evening fishing on the river.

(more details on the fishing to come later this week)
Camping wouldn’t be complete without Smore’s so we roasted some mallows over the gas stove.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping with Kids</title>
      <link>/posts/camping-with-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 10:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/camping-with-kids/</guid>
      <description>My daughter keeps asking me almost every day, “When are we going camping again?” Our family loves to camp. We enjoy it for many reasons… the dirt, the food, the family time away from home, and a cheap place to sleep while visiting our beloved National Parks…
Scott and I have gone camping every year since we’ve been married, with the exception of one… the year 2004…when our first child was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camp Fire Donuts</title>
      <link>/posts/camp-fire-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/camp-fire-donuts/</guid>
      <description>This recipe for warm and gooey deliciousness is courtesy of Scott’s college room mate. It’s not as easy as popping a mallow on a stick and roasting it, but it is oh so worth the effort! You must try camp fire donuts on your next over night camping trip&amp;hellip;
First you take a can of Pillsbury breadsticks (or a generic equivalent)

Pop it open

Then you begin to wrap the bread dough around a stick</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number One Rule of Camping</title>
      <link>/posts/number-one-rule-of-camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/number-one-rule-of-camping/</guid>
      <description>**Updated Below!
Once we finally departed, the kids were ecstatic about our camping trip this weekend. As we were preparing to leave, my son already started talking about the very, important rules of camping, as he’s discovered them over the years.
And the number one, most exciting rule is that **
camping is messy!
**
This one cracked me up, because while it is true, to hear him talk you would think he grew up in a house where he was never allowed to get dirty.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
