<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aunt Karen on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/aunt-karen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aunt Karen on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 11:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/aunt-karen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mr Sneaky</title>
      <link>/posts/mr-sneaky/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mr-sneaky/</guid>
      <description>So, it turns out we have a sneak here at the circus.
Yes, behind this adorable smile is actually a rather devious little chocolate hoarder. Earlier this week the kids received a package of chocolate from their cousins for Valentines day. I let them all have one after lunch and then we put the box up on the counter for later. Later that evening when the kids wanted another piece after dinner the box was no where to be found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life is Good</title>
      <link>/posts/life-is-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/life-is-good/</guid>
      <description>Years ago Aunt Karen gave our oldest child a Life is Good soccer shirt. Because the color and theme were gender neutral, I ended up passing it down to my daughter a few years later. It actually became that perfect shirt for younger siblings to wear to soccer games so she could feel like she was a part of the team too. By the time my third child wore it, it was worn with shin guards and sometimes even cleats TO WATCH the older 2 practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DATE DAY</title>
      <link>/posts/date-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/date-day/</guid>
      <description>While we didn’t plan it like this at first, Sunday ended up being date day for each of our 4 kids. Each child ended up with some one on one time with either mom, dad, or Aunt Karen. Good times had by all!
One of the duties of our church deacons is to unlock the church on Sunday mornings. When Scott became a deacon 3 years ago, he started taking one child with him on his deacon duty mornings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
