<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>spring on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/spring/</link>
    <description>Recent content in spring on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 12:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/spring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spring is Here!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-is-here/</guid>
      <description>When I walked outside today and felt warmth, my heart was instantly happy. It’s a balmy 75 degrees today and I.LOVE.IT!! This is my ideal temp. I love being able to walk around in flip flops and head out the door without thought of a jacket. I love not being at all chilly. So of course when I picked the kids up from tutorial today, I brought my trusty ball cap because I knew we’d be staying after for football, and flower picking, chatting with friends, and the latest development in after school play time….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sweet Spring Tradition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-sweet-spring-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-sweet-spring-tradition/</guid>
      <description>When my son was 3, I took him strawberry picking for the first time. It was a special Mommy/Son date prior to the birth of our third child. [
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/IMG_1690.jpg)
 The next year, we returned, but this time it was a family affair.
2009 brought us back to the same farm, this time with friends.

And 2010 found me once again at the fields pregnant, with many small children in tow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our February Stay-cation</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-february-stay-cation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-february-stay-cation/</guid>
      <description>Without having to pay thousands of dollars to fly to the Caribbean for a few days, we in the Maryland area were blessed with a week of spring weather in February. And the Circus kids and I soaked up every precious minute of it. I had my kids outside as much as possible this week. Biking, Swinging, Picnicking, digging, and wading…




Rumor has it snow could fall here next week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
