<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>things that make me laugh on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/things-that-make-me-laugh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in things that make me laugh on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 03:46:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/things-that-make-me-laugh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>T-R-O-U-B-L-E</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t-r-o-u-b-l-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 03:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t-r-o-u-b-l-e/</guid>
      <description>This afternoon my smiley, mild mannered, easy going baby suddenly channeled his inner Dennis the Menace and went all toddler boy on me for 30 minutes. First I looked over and found him standing on his tool bench (oops look who forgot to put away the advent calendar with her Christmas decorations)

I got him down and shortly after realized things had been mighty quiet for awhile and went searching for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ever Wonder Why it’s Called Butcher Paper?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ever-wonder-why-its-called-butcher-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ever-wonder-why-its-called-butcher-paper/</guid>
      <description>I was an elementary school teacher for 3 years. We used butcher paper all the time for bulletin boards. I’ve also seen it cleverly used at restaurants in place of a tablecloth to give a space for the kids to doodle while waiting. Never… in all my years did I really stop to think why it was called butcher paper.. or what the actual intent of the paper was for. Scott and I got the idea to get the kids a roll of butcher paper to keep on our dining room table.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
