<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yosemite National Park on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/yosemite-national-park/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yosemite National Park on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 19:31:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/yosemite-national-park/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hiking to the Falls</title>
      <link>/posts/hiking-to-the-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hiking-to-the-falls/</guid>
      <description>Scott had been hoping for us to take a hike down from Glacier Point to Yosemite Valley. It would be our longest hike, but it would have been all down hill and we would pass both Nevada and Vernal Falls. Given our kids fascination with water falls, this seemed like a fun hike. Unfortunately, we learned too late that there was no shuttle from Yosemite Valley to Glacier Point, and the only way we could do this plan was if we had pre purchased tickets for a special shuttle that left early in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One of America’s Best</title>
      <link>/posts/one-of-americas-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-of-americas-best/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I visited Yosemite 14 years ago during our trip which shaped all trips. Therefore, it wasn’t a must see for this vacation. And when Scott and I were first plotting out this trip, we kind of waivered as to whether we wanted to include it or not. But, we decided that since Yosemite is one of the quintessential parks and since we were were were going to be SO CLOSE, we owed it to the kids to show them Yosemite.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
