<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>baseball on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/baseball/</link>
    <description>Recent content in baseball on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 15:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/baseball/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finally a GOOD season for baseball</title>
      <link>/posts/finally-a-good-season-for-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/finally-a-good-season-for-baseball/</guid>
      <description>My son has loved baseball since he was 2. A fan of his own right. Loves it inside and out. But, I thought last year the flame might die. Or be killed a slow and painful death.
It was a painful combination of not yet seeing a winning baseball game in his life and playing on a team which didn’t win a single game all season, topped off with having a coach that didn’t coach, just yelled in frustration at the discouraged players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Call it Crazy…</title>
      <link>/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</guid>
      <description>This spring I have 3 kids in sports. On 3 different teams. This in addition to the girls both taking gymnastics twice a week and Cub Scouts.
We are busy, busy, busy with games and practices most every night… some nights we’re even double booked.
Many people look at my schedule and call me crazy. Why do you do this to yourself?
The answer is, honestly, two fold. 1. We love it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let the Record Show…</title>
      <link>/posts/let-the-record-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/let-the-record-show/</guid>
      <description>There is a whole lot of hype round these parts about the Orioles… with a 4-1 record to start the season, some new acquisitions over the off season and a new manager last season, for the first time in a LONG time, things are looking up for the Baltimore Orioles. And I feel the need to 1. explain the weird circus family sports allegiance when it comes to Baltimore and Pittsburgh and 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America’s Pastime</title>
      <link>/posts/americas-pastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/americas-pastime/</guid>
      <description>I clearly remember the first baseball game I attended with Scott. A coworker had given him the tickets and since we had no plans, we thought, “Sure, why not?” As we drove into Baltimore and hit traffic, Scott was in disbelief, “Could this be game traffic?” He asked. “I had no idea this many people liked baseball.”
Yea… clearly, we aren’t big baseball enthusiasts.
But, thanks to my oldest son, my children are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our All American Boy</title>
      <link>/posts/our-all-american-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-all-american-boy/</guid>
      <description>We took a lot of pictures of my son’s first baseball game of the season,

but without a doubt, this one is my favorite.

His look truly says it all. Is that the face of a happy ball player or what?
This is what little league is all about…the pure love of the game. May he never outgrow it.
Visit here or here for more picture fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Exactly Something You See Everyday</title>
      <link>/posts/not-exactly-something-you-see-everyday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 07:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/not-exactly-something-you-see-everyday/</guid>
      <description>Not everyday you see an Oriole wrapped in a Steelers Terrible Towel. Click here or here for more picture fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Very Realistic Fan</title>
      <link>/posts/a-very-realistic-fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-very-realistic-fan/</guid>
      <description>Our son is a huge baseball fan. His team of choice is the Baltimore Orioles. As much as he likes the Orioles, he also recognizes that they don’t exactly have a winning record…
Last week we were getting ready for soccer practice when he informed me that he didn’t feel like going to practice. Me:&amp;amp;#160; “Well you need to practice, it helps you to get better.”Son: “ But Mom, I’m already really good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Just Like That He Turned Me Into a Baseball Fan</title>
      <link>/posts/and-just-like-that-he-turned-me-into-a-baseball-fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/and-just-like-that-he-turned-me-into-a-baseball-fan/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5M4M for more WW</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
