<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gardening on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/gardening/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gardening on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/gardening/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Worst Garden Ever</title>
      <link>/posts/worst-garden-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/worst-garden-ever/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to stop pretending. The act is over. Who am I kidding?
I am not a gardener.
Each spring, I get bitten by a gardening bug and I think that I will turn over a new leaf and suddenly spawn a green thumb. So, I buy some plants and seeds and the kids and I set off to garden. Each spring Scott asks why am I doing this when I know what will happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sweet Taste of Success</title>
      <link>/posts/the-sweet-taste-of-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2009 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-sweet-taste-of-success/</guid>
      <description>Those of you that have been part of the circus for awhile, know that I seriously lack a green thumb. I guess you could call me naive, but this spring I decided to try again. Much like peach picking, my goal in gardening is to teach my kids. So, I didn’t go for huge garden with hopes of providing a summer’s worth of produce. Instead, I opted for a few plants that we could watch grow and hopefully taste the fruits of our labor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WOW! I did it!!</title>
      <link>/posts/wow-i-did-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wow-i-did-it/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Becky and her super fun WOW (within one week) carnival, I managed to tackle my overgrown flower beds and get them spruced up in time for summer. I realize many of you did your spring planting early this spring, but I already told you yesterday, I am not always timely.
Check out the before and after.
Flower Bed #1:

I’d still like to cut my rose bushes down some, but I think you will agree it looks MUCH better than it did last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WOW Have I Gotta Lot to Do!!</title>
      <link>/posts/wow-have-i-gotta-lot-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2009 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wow-have-i-gotta-lot-to-do/</guid>
      <description>If you’re anything like me then perhaps you’ve got a project or two that’s been sitting on the back burner for awhile… in the daily struggle to get dinner on the table and clean underwear out of the dryer, some how those bigger projects get pushed off until “later.”
Well, Becky’s got a carnival going on this week to inspire us to tackle those projects we’ve been meaning to get to, but haven’t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvest Time</title>
      <link>/posts/harvest-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 01:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/harvest-time/</guid>
      <description>Despite the fact that I lack a green thumb and raise suicidal plants, I still attempted a garden this summer with my kids. Some may call me a hopeless optimist, to others I am just naive. But, my oldest two children were particularly excited about this new venture and I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to let them down.
This April we planted a row of peas, a row of green beans, a row of pumpkins, two tomato plants, and two pepper plants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversations in the Garden</title>
      <link>/posts/conversations-in-the-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/conversations-in-the-garden/</guid>
      <description>I weeded our flower beds this week with my 4y, 2y and 9m old. This is not an equation for efficiency, but we had fun&amp;hellip;.
We found an earthworm and I was really proud of myself for not going &amp;ldquo;eek&amp;rdquo; when I uncovered it in the dirt. Not only did I not shriek, but I feigned excitement and got my kids to be excited about it. My 2 year old tried to eat it (you have to watch her)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Answer My Friend is Blowing in the Wind</title>
      <link>/posts/the-answer-my-friend-is-blowing-in-the-wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-answer-my-friend-is-blowing-in-the-wind/</guid>
      <description>This morning when my kids were eating breakfast my son asked,
&amp;ldquo;Mom, what happened to your flower?&amp;rdquo; I looked on the deck and it was gone. I asked my hubby if he moved it and he said,&amp;quot; No, but last night when I was sitting out at the dining room table, I did hear a  crash outside when the wind blew.&amp;quot;
My kids went out to investigate this morning and it seems my poor flower decided to take her life with a fateful jump off of our deck, rather than to continue to suffer under my care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Not So Green Thumb</title>
      <link>/posts/my-not-so-green-thumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 22:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-not-so-green-thumb/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t have a green thumb. I want to, but truth be told, I lack the follow through. On Wednesday my husband and I went to a dinner for his work and they had potted flowers on all of the tables. Afterwards we each got to take one home. As we drove home with it in the car, my husband said to me, &amp;ldquo;So, how long before you kill it?&amp;rdquo; I replied with a &amp;ldquo;ugh&amp;rdquo; and a look that said how dare you say that&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
