<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wife on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/wife/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wife on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 06:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/wife/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Anniversary Date in DC</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/anniversary-date-in-dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 06:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/anniversary-date-in-dc/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we snuck away for to celebrate our anniversary. We spent the night in the nations capital. And we had a blast. No agenda. No plan. Just hanging out in DC just the two of us. Confession: I love the monuments in DC. Living in MD, I have seen them a lot. Growing up summer visits from cousins ALWAYS meant trips into DC. And I know they are very touristy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tee Shirt Love</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tee-shirt-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tee-shirt-love/</guid>
      <description>Scott has been a huge help and support to me this week… taking time off of work so I can rest up (apparently surgery takes more out of you, then you anticipate)… driving the kids to their activities, helping with school, and meals and cleaning up… So, today, I thought I’d show my appreciation and wear my “My Husband Rocks” tee shirt. My 7 year old looked at my shirt, read it aloud and said, “So, why did you wear that today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sparkle</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sparkle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sparkle/</guid>
      <description>One of the things I came across while packing for our move was a bottle of jewelry cleaner. As soon as I found it, I scrubbed my wedding rings. As I did, I realized it had been quite awhile since I had cleaned my rings. As I scrubbed, the grime became more and more apparent. I couldn’t believe how brilliantly they sparkled after I cleaned them. When Scott first came me my engagement ring, I couldn’t take my eyes off of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Things I Love About You</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/11-things-i-love-about-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2012 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/11-things-i-love-about-you/</guid>
      <description>Scott, in honor of our anniversary this weekend, I compiled a list of 11 things I love about you.
1. You’re a dreamer.
2. Your not afraid to go for the crazy (take 4 kids on a 22 hour car ride to see a 2 minute rocket launch… sure thing…stop by Times Square for hot dogs on the way to CT for a wedding with 2 toddlers and a very pregnant wife, “I’m in!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Wants Mom’s Dead Flowers?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-wants-moms-dead-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-wants-moms-dead-flowers/</guid>
      <description>On the wall in my bedroom, tucked away in the corner on my side of the bed is a shadow box in which I pressed some dried flowers from my wedding bouquet. I’ll confess I don’t look at it often, but when I do I smile and remember that special day.
My children, however, don’t share my sentimentality.
The other day my 5 yr old and I were sitting on my bed and she said, “Mom, why do you have those old dead flowers hanging on your wall?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just the 2 of us in Chicago</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-the-2-of-us-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-the-2-of-us-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I got away last week, just the 2 of us, for 3 nights in the Windy City. It was a belated 10 year anniversary gift to ourselves.
And it was WON-DER-FUL!!
The city of Chicago is beautiful. The buildings are unique and interesting… truly works of art in and of themselves. We had so much fun walking around the city and taking in its beauty. The weather was overcast and it rained off and on while we were there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Still the One…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/your-still-the-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/your-still-the-one/</guid>
      <description>It was one of the best days of my life. Even though it seemed like the time would never arrive, finally it was time. The doors opened, and Scott’s best friend began playing Trumpet Voluntary on his trumpet. And dad and I began our walk down the aisle. I will never forget the look of love in Scott’s eyes as I walked toward him down that aisle. I have a picture of his face on my dresser so I can remember it always.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating the Beginning of the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/celebrating-the-beginning-of-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/celebrating-the-beginning-of-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>10 years ago we came…spread a blanket out on the sandy shore to watch the sunset. Today we came, with sandwiches and Doritos. This time there was a picnic table where we had spread our blanket. And we watched the sunset mirrored in the faces of our three children.
 
10 years ago it was quiet… we held hands and sat close on the blanket.
Tonight there was sand in our shoes and children squirming….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross Country Fashion Consult</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cross-country-fashion-consult/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cross-country-fashion-consult/</guid>
      <description>As I’ve already made well aware, I am not exactly a fashion guru. You won’t find me flipping through the pages of Cosmopolitan in my free time. My nails are rarely done and my idea of styling my hair involves taking the time to blow dry rather than air dry.
I wanted to look cute when Scott and I went on a date a few weeks ago. I was so excited because my friend had just lent me some adorable maternity clothes so I didn’t really give my thought to my wardrobe till about 30 min before we were going to leave when I began to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe in Daddy’s Arms</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/safe-in-daddys-arms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 04:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/safe-in-daddys-arms/</guid>
      <description>Tonight is one of those nights when I am extra thankful that God has given me a helpmate in life. And not just any helpmate, but one of the best.
My three year old was getting on the couch this evening, and if you know my girls, you know that they do this with much exuberance, so somewhere during the twirl she slipped and fell back, hitting her head on our toy box/coffee table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He’s Baaaack!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hes-baaaack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hes-baaaack/</guid>
      <description>The first time Scott went away on business travel, we were newly married and when he told me he was going to CA for a week, I really thought the world was ending. Looking back it was one of those classic examples of a couple looking at the same event in two different ways. For Scott the trip was an exciting opportunity. A chance to do something new and definitely a plus for his career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shh, don’t tell…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shh-dont-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 21:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shh-dont-tell/</guid>
      <description>While most of America celebrated Father’s Day yesterday, the circus family did not. Shh…Please don’t tell the circus children. They think Father’s Day is next week, because that’s when we are celebrating it. We paint pumpkins in Nov and build gingerbread houses in Jan, so why can’t we celebrate dear old dad one week late? Yes, we are shamelessly pulling the wool over our innocent children’s eyes.
Scott and I wanted to get away for a weekend alone, just the two of us, as our gift to each other for our 30th birthdays this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save Your Thoughts</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/save-your-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 08:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/save-your-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Just a heads up that we’ll be saving those weekend thoughts for next weekend. My husband and I are heading out the door for a weekend away and I’ve got no deep thoughts for you….other than thoughts of me and my hubby being whisked away for a weekend alone. But,I’ll be keeping those thoughts to myself, thankyouverymuch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Great Years and Counting</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/8-great-years-and-counting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/8-great-years-and-counting/</guid>
      <description>I put together a short video for our anniversary (I promise it’s only 2 min 10 secs) of my hubby and me over the past 8 years. Those of you who have read our story, see if you can tell why I picked the song I did. Also, for fun see if you can pick out the 3 shots taken by my son in this 2 minute video montage. As I look back over the past 8 years I see lots of national parks and newborn babies…what a great time we’ve had!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Its PARTY time!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-party-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-party-time/</guid>
      <description>[5 Minutes for Mom] (http://www.5minutesformom.com)is hosting their annual blog party and this year I am joining in the fun! So kick your shoes off, change in to some comfy pants and make yourself at home, because the best thing about a blog party is you can join in the fun from the comfort of your couch!
I’ve been blogging for almost a year now. What started as a fulfillment of my new years resolution, has grown into a means of making new friends and reconnecting with old ones as I share my circus life as a wife and stay at home mom of three active preschoolers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Forever Kind of Love</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-forever-kind-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2009 06:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-forever-kind-of-love/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for sticking around this week for the last installment in my week long saga of how the circus began.
It was spring break of our junior year. The plan (or so I thought) was to spend the first part of break at my parents house and the last part in MD at his parents house.
Wednesday we drove to MD and Thursday we had plans for a fun date in DC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The College Years</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-college-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2009 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-college-years/</guid>
      <description>I have been having a ton of fun on my walk down memory lane this week. (click here to read the beginning of the story).The other day I opened up a hat box which I have filled with Every.Single.Card and note Scott wrote me from our pre-marriage days and our first 2 years of married life. I told you my love language was words of affirmation and if you needed the proof, it is in the box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cupid’s Big Day</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cupids-big-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cupids-big-day/</guid>
      <description>I am sucker for holidays and tend to go all out for them. Valentine’s is no exception. We’ve got the heart shaped clings on the windows, our wedding picture on our entry table and big plans for strawberry milk and heart shaped pancakes for breakfast on Saturday morning.
This isn’t anything new. Back in high school I looked forward to the day even when I didn’t have a boyfriend to celebrate with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He Likes Me!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/he-likes-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/he-likes-me/</guid>
      <description>I left off on my love story yesterday with the note my husband wrote me on the back of his senior picture. A few weeks later we did in fact “spend time together after school.” It was the day before Thanksgiving and we had a half day of school. The plan was for him to come to my house that afternoon to watch Toy Story.
I was both nervous and excited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How The Circus Began</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-the-circus-began/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 03:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-the-circus-began/</guid>
      <description>In honor of Valentine’s Day I thought I’d share my love story with you all this week.
I mentioned before that prior to being voted “Most Congenial” Scott and I had only had 2 conversations with each other throughout high school. After the 4th photo shoot, we got one acceptable enough to put in the yearbook, and I started to notice what a genuinely nice guy he was. Sadly though, we had no classes together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Are The Moments</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/these-are-the-moments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/these-are-the-moments/</guid>
      <description>As we finished up dinner tonight a song came on the ipod that made Scott want to dance and he invited me to join him. So we did a little swing dancing in the living room with the kids watching from the table.
Then my son got up and grabbed the “point and shoot” we sometimes let him use to take pictures with and took some pictures of us “to put on my wall” he said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My how 12 years Has Changed Things a Bit</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-how-12-years-has-changed-things-a-bit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-how-12-years-has-changed-things-a-bit/</guid>
      <description>12 years ago Scott and I went on our first date. We went to dinner and then strolled around the shops in downtown Annapolis for midnight Madness.
I was so excited and nervous.
This was my first REAL date.
And what could be more romantic than strolling through historic Annapolis listening to Christmas carols?
Even though we didn&amp;rsquo;t hold hands, (That didn&amp;rsquo;t come until February). I was still on cloud nine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Him</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tell-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tell-him/</guid>
      <description>Ladies, I have truly enjoyed reading your comments about how your husbands rock. It was probably my most exciting blog week to date. I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you how much it brightened my day to read such uplifting words about your hubbies. I want to encourage all of you to tell your husbands why they rock. Today. Don&amp;rsquo;t assume they know. Don&amp;rsquo;t figure they don&amp;rsquo;t need to hear it. Don&amp;rsquo;t wait for them to tell you why you rock first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give Away: My Husband Rocks</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/give-away-my-husband-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/give-away-my-husband-rocks/</guid>
      <description>How often do you plan something special just for your hubbie? No, not your anniversary or his birthday, but just because you love him?
While I was at the MOPS convention last month, there was a woman there promoting The Husband Project. Curious, I stopped by her booth. The husband project is basically a guideline for helping wives to focus on their husbands needs. The project is designed to last for 3 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Got A Hot Date Tonight!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ive-got-a-hot-date-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2008 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ive-got-a-hot-date-tonight/</guid>
      <description>Updated&amp;hellip;for those those that asked Movie Review Below
I&amp;rsquo;m going on a hot date tonight with my hubby and I am SO excited!! My legs are shaved, eye brows plucked, and I&amp;rsquo;m even going to wear a skirt and put on make up!! Perhaps I&amp;rsquo;ll even add a little jewelry for sparkle!!
This time we aren&amp;rsquo;t going to Toys R Us! I got free movie tickets at the grocery store earlier this summer so thanks to Sarah&amp;rsquo;s raving review, we&amp;rsquo;re going to see the new Batman Movie and eating dinner too (one where we don&amp;rsquo;t have to cut food into tiny pieces, sop up spilled milk, AND we can even have a complete conversation)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isn&#39;t he just awesome?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/isnt-he-just-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/isnt-he-just-awesome/</guid>
      <description>I think everyone should be so lucky as to be married to an engineer. While it is true that purchasing large or technical products such as televisions, cameras, or computers will take longer as we&amp;rsquo;ll he&amp;rsquo;ll have to research the various brands, settings, options and figure out which one is the best price and has the best features for us, when any of those things breaks he is not afraid to open them up and fix them (and since he spend a larger portion of his childhood taking a part such items he actually knows what he is looking at and how to fix it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Running</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-running/</guid>
      <description>Last week I registered for a 10 mile run at the end of August. For over a year now I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to do this. I ran a 5K for the first time when my son was a year old. I ran two more when my 2 year old was 6 mths old. Until last Tuesday, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t run since.
I waited through one of the mildest winter and spring seasons I&amp;rsquo;ve seen here and decided to start running during the week of record breaking heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Higher and Lower Then Ever Before</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/going-higher-and-lower-then-ever-before/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 03:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/going-higher-and-lower-then-ever-before/</guid>
      <description>I thought I’d post a picture from my honeymoon since 7 years ago today I was in St Lucia with my hubby. Being married to Scott has been a grand adventure. He’s taken me lower and higher than I thought I’d ever go. Whether it’s exploring the world below sea level, or hiking along a glacier, he’s pushed me to do things I’d never have thought of doing on my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Home Date Nights</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/in-home-date-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/in-home-date-nights/</guid>
      <description>With three children under 4, it isn&amp;rsquo;t always easy to get out for a date night. Sometimes we do date nights at home. We feed the kids a simple dinner&amp;hellip; chicken nuggets or hot dogs. While I am getting the kids ready for bed, my husband grills us steak for dinner. We light a candle and enjoy a leisurely dinner together. We get to talk, uninterrupted and enjoy our food while it is still warm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: What a Man!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/weekend-thoughts-what-a-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/weekend-thoughts-what-a-man/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we are celebrating my husband&amp;rsquo;s 29th birthday. As I look back at some of his baby pictures, (isn&amp;rsquo;t he such a cutie) I am so thankful for the man he is today and feel incredibly blessed to call him my husband.
There are many things I respect about him, but at the top of the list would be his integrity, his perseverance, and his wisdom. We&amp;rsquo;ve been married almost 7 years now and since I get to live with him day in and day out, I truly get to see all sides of him and I can honestly say that he is consistent and that he genuinely strives each day to glorify God in all he does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Congenial??????</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/most-congenial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/most-congenial/</guid>
      <description>We are THAT family is hosting a blog carnival which lets us share some flashback pictures and anecdotes. I thought I would use this as an excuse to pull one of my countless unphotogenic pictures from the archives. Maybe they can finally be put to good use.
My husband and I are high school sweethearts. We went to a small Christian school with only 44 students in our graduating class. Because our last names were on opposite ends of the alphabet we never had home room together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Mr. Incredible</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-mr.-incredible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 20:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-mr.-incredible/</guid>
      <description>Tonight I was out all evening. I met a friend for dinner and then went to a steering meeting for my MOPS group. My wonderful husband stayed home with the kids. He made them waffles for dinner and they had a super hero night. My son received a Super Hero Starter Kit for his birthday which included an instruction book, real cape, eye masks and shield stickers. My son has been wearing his cape for days and my hubby has been teaching him how to be a super hero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Need to Get Out More</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-need-to-get-out-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 00:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-need-to-get-out-more/</guid>
      <description>Tonight I had a hot date with my hubby. My son&amp;rsquo;s birthday is coming up and we needed to go shopping for his present. Since we had to get a babysitter to watch the kids, we decided to take full advantage of that fact and we went out for dinner as well. I really enjoyed having an uninterrupted conversation with him while getting to hold his hand as we walked into the store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do you say I Love You?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-do-you-say-i-love-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 20:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-do-you-say-i-love-you/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago my hubby told me he had left me a surprise love note in the kitchen for me to find later. I thought perhaps he had done the dishes or something. When I went to the kitchen I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find it. Every now and then when I thought about it, I would look around trying to figure out what it was.
The other night I was talking on the phone and doing some dishes when I looked at our window and saw a U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
