<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>running on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/running/</link>
    <description>Recent content in running on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 11:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/running/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Banner Week</title>
      <link>/posts/banner-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/banner-week/</guid>
      <description>Exciting things are happening round the circus parts this week and it’s only Tuesday!!
Sunday, I ran a half marathon with my FIL. My friend, who had to run a half marathon in order to see me in real life, also ran but she was so stinking fast that I am glad I caught her in line for the potty before the race, b/c there was no seeing her after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back on the Wagon</title>
      <link>/posts/back-on-the-wagon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/back-on-the-wagon/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago my FIL approached me about running in a local half marathon with him at the beginning of March. Because I seem to require a race to motivate me to run, I was eager to accept. However, it only left me about 7 weeks to prepare and I was not in running shape, having only run a handful of times since my son’s birth last June. I found some training guides online (both of which suggested 12 weeks to prepare) and spent a good amount of time face booking and e-mailing with a friend about my strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: I’m a Survivor</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-im-a-survivor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-im-a-survivor/</guid>
      <description>Last week I survived the Annapolis 10 Mile Run. I’d like to say that I raced it or ran it, but in actuality I just survived it.
While one might wonder why I am not more excited and proud of such an accomplishment, it is because the year prior, I ran it well. I trained for it all summer and come race day I did my best. Now my best is only about 15 min faster than my survival pace, but the feeling I had when crossing the finish line was worlds different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Sounded Like A Good Idea 3 Months Ago</title>
      <link>/posts/this-sounded-like-a-good-idea-3-months-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/this-sounded-like-a-good-idea-3-months-ago/</guid>
      <description>I saw this line on a tee shirt this weekend at the Annapolis 10 Mile and loved it. But, it cost $27 so I decided instead of buying the tee shirt, I’d make it my blog title. Yea, I was so excited when I signed up back in June to run this race with my high school friends. And somehow 3 months came and went and I ummm didn’t really train adequately for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Non Athletic Team</title>
      <link>/posts/my-non-athletic-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2009 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-non-athletic-team/</guid>
      <description>I am not an athlete. Those of you blog readers who knew me in high school can vouch for me on this. My position on the HS sport team was bench warmer, my role, “team encourager.” When my recent blog friend turned IRL friend accompanied me this weekend to pick up my runners pack for the Pittsburgh Half Marathon and called me athletic, I almost laughed in her face.
Me athletic?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day One of Training</title>
      <link>/posts/day-one-of-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/day-one-of-training/</guid>
      <description>Well, January came and went and I exercised one day in 2009. This is why I have to set goals for myself. Without a race in my future, I lack the discipline to get off my butt.
So, I’ve set my sights on a Half Marathon in May in one of my favorite cities…Pittsburgh. I am really excited. I checked out the route online and it looks great…we cross two bridges, run downtown a bit, run along the river overlooking the city and my highlight, we run by Heinz Field (home of the Superbowl Champs)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Run Like a Mommy</title>
      <link>/posts/i-run-like-a-mommy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 05:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/i-run-like-a-mommy/</guid>
      <description>My son told me he knew what I should wear on a tee shirt. He came up with this slogan out of the blue the other day.
&amp;ldquo;I run like a mommy and my kids cheer all the time when I run
and my husband works so good like a dad, he&amp;rsquo;s awesome!&amp;quot;
I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly sure what it means to run like a Mommy.
But after recently receiving the photos from the race photographers, I realized that I learned a valuable lesson at my A10 race which I applied when running my half marathon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
