<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Circus Shots on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/circus-shots/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Circus Shots on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 04:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/circus-shots/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Oh This Boy!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/oh-this-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 04:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/oh-this-boy/</guid>
      <description>It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t shock me, but yet it does. How completely DIFFERENT each of my children are. Their personalities are so unique, it truly amazes me.
Take my youngest.
Oh my goodness&amp;hellip; he is such a goof ball, and a FLIRT, but I&amp;rsquo;ll save that for another post&amp;hellip;
Here the kids are in Boston.
&amp;ldquo;Kids, get together so mom can get a picture of the four of you by the fountains.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Class Clown</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-class-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 05:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-class-clown/</guid>
      <description>It seems to be that when you have more than one child… their differences sometimes seem to shine out, and they can kind of fall into different roles. The peacemaker, the organizer…. not that I am advocating type casting your children or anything. I know they can all play different roles at different times.
However, when I asked the kids to pose for a picture at the strawberry patch the other day, my youngest displayed his true colors…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Clean Once Again Proves Himself to be a Worthy tool in the Arsenal of Motherhood</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mr.-clean-once-again-proves-himself-to-be-a-worthy-tool-in-the-arsenalof-motherhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mr.-clean-once-again-proves-himself-to-be-a-worthy-tool-in-the-arsenalof-motherhood/</guid>
      <description>I don’t really know what it is that possesses a child to just randomly on a whim pick up that crayon and suddenly decide to make the world (or in this case the bathroom) his canvas. We have crayons out every single day in our house. I do my best when I see a stray one on the floor to nab it lest it suddenly look inviting to my toddler. But, truly they are laying on the school table, in reach, every single day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Sneaky</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mr-sneaky/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mr-sneaky/</guid>
      <description>So, it turns out we have a sneak here at the circus.
Yes, behind this adorable smile is actually a rather devious little chocolate hoarder. Earlier this week the kids received a package of chocolate from their cousins for Valentines day. I let them all have one after lunch and then we put the box up on the counter for later. Later that evening when the kids wanted another piece after dinner the box was no where to be found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapshots</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/snapshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/snapshots/</guid>
      <description>I am trying to get my blogging groove back on… not sure how exactly to do that, but it seems one way is to simply post… I am short on words right now, so I’ll just post a few of my favorite recent snapshots.
He loves to help me in the kitchen, in large part b/c he loves to sample the ingredients EVERY CHANCE HE gets.

Kit joined us for school at home</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Beautiful Surprise</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-beautiful-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-beautiful-surprise/</guid>
      <description>I recall seeing something on Facebook before I went to bed about possible flash freezing or snow. But, I didn’t give it much thought.
When I woke up I peeked behind the curtain to see if anything came of it and I gasped. It was that big white puffy snow that sticks to the branches of trees. My most favorite kind of snowfall. And I laid in bed and watched it fall snuggling with my hubby and kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even Super Man Sleeps</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/even-super-man-sleeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/even-super-man-sleeps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Each Their Own</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/to-each-their-own/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/to-each-their-own/</guid>
      <description>Some people like the feeling of sand beneath their toes. I must say I do enjoy the squish of wet sand beneath my feet as the waves lap at my ankles. My children, however, have a whole different kind of love of sand.

One which truly baffles my mind.

EVERY SINGLE TIME we visit our community beach, it’s the same routine. We drop our stuff in the sand and they make a mad dash for the water, they splash and play and swim and then, inevitably, they decide it’s time to hit the sand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Their Current Favorite</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/their-current-favorite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/their-current-favorite/</guid>
      <description>Round these parts the_ current _ show which they all can agree on when they are given the chance to pick something is Woody Woodpecker. What’s at the top of your queue these days?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 05:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/memory/</guid>
      <description>She pretty much whips me at this every Monday and Wednesday… and I wouldn’t trade the sweet memories we’re making for anything in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spontaneous Family Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spontaneous-family-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spontaneous-family-fun/</guid>
      <description>I really wanted to take the kids in to DC this spring to see the Cherry Blossoms. It’s not something we do every year, in fact, I think I’ve been only a handful of times in the 27 years I’ve lived in Maryland. But, this year, I thought it’d be fun to go and was thinking we might even have a free weekend during their peak blooms. But, thanks to the warm winter we had, they peaked early and there was NO chance of going during their peak week as it just didn’t fit with our schedules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There She Goes</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/there-she-goes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/there-she-goes/</guid>
      <description>Truthfully, the circus family doesn’t spend much time on bikes. We do a lot of fun things here, don’t get me wrong, but there are only so many hours in a day, and teaching our kids to ride bikes has not been where we’ve spent ours.
But, today the sun was shining, the weather was unseasonably warm here in MD again, and as the kids played in the backyard while Scott did yard work, our oldest daughter decided that today she wanted to ride her bike without training wheels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisterly Love</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sisterly-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sisterly-love/</guid>
      <description>Nothing like a surprise package of clothes in the mail to bring smiles to the girls faces and provide an impromptu photo opp. (the boys appreciated it too, but not to the same extent)



Thanks cousins Ben and Eli!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What? Do I have something on my face?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-do-i-have-something-on-my-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 06:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-do-i-have-something-on-my-face/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-R-O-U-B-L-E</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t-r-o-u-b-l-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 03:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t-r-o-u-b-l-e/</guid>
      <description>This afternoon my smiley, mild mannered, easy going baby suddenly channeled his inner Dennis the Menace and went all toddler boy on me for 30 minutes. First I looked over and found him standing on his tool bench (oops look who forgot to put away the advent calendar with her Christmas decorations)

I got him down and shortly after realized things had been mighty quiet for awhile and went searching for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Our Money’s Worth</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/getting-our-moneys-worth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/getting-our-moneys-worth/</guid>
      <description>We had some trees and branches cut down in our yard yesterday. Thus far I think it was worth every penny as I love the new look of our yard, the feeling of safety knowing those dead branches aren’t going to come down in the next storm, AND the free babysitting it provided yesterday afternoon.

The tree in front of our living room window provided the most excitement. Even my 18 mth old was so intrigued, he kept looking out the window and then he’d yell, “Hey Mama” and a whole bunch of gibberish followed by “Hey Mama”… I swear with that gibberish, he was telling me “there’s a man flying outside our window!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cookie-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cookie-fun/</guid>
      <description>The most favorite Christmas cookie for the circus fam to make is sugar cookies. Messiness + sugar = pure bliss for the circus crew!!


  This year we enjoyed rolling and cutting the cookies with our cousin Eli. 

 It was also the first year that the youngest circus crew member got to participate in the cooking making fun. And by participate, I of course mean, eating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puppy Kisses</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/puppy-kisses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/puppy-kisses/</guid>
      <description>Visit here for more WW posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Role Play</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/role-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/role-play/</guid>
      <description>Our oldest daughter had a little fun getting into her character for Halloween. When posing for pictures in their costumes, she decided to fully act out the part of Snow White.

I think my favorite part of the reenactment was when she asked us to take her picture sleeping with the apple. &amp;quot;Skip the ol posing by the door with the trick or treat basket, we’ll go for playing dead on the floor with an apple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hmmm… Notice Something Missing Here?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hmmm-notice-something-missing-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hmmm-notice-something-missing-here/</guid>
      <description>As my 4 yr old sat coloring in the waiting room this afternoon the mom beside me commented on her neat job of staying in the lines. Then we both did a double take and looked over at each other. 
Don’t  mind the fact that the dress is green and should “really” be yellow… I love the fact that my girl goes against the flow and colors it how she wants… sure give Belle purple hair and a green dress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An End of Summer Tradition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-end-of-summer-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-end-of-summer-tradition/</guid>
      <description>Of the 32 years I’ve been a Steelers fan, I only had the joy of being a hometown fan for only 8 of those years (5 of which I was 5 and under so it doesn’t really count in my book). My sophomore year of college, I moved to PA for 3 years. I was thrilled to get to watch the Steelers on a weekly basis. Unfortunately, this was during the Kordell Stewart, Tommy Maddox era, which wasn’t exactly the Steelers golden era of football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He Spoils Us</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/he-spoils-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/he-spoils-us/</guid>
      <description>Time and time again our fourth child has blown us away with his easy going, flexible, happy-go-lucky approach to life. It has made the transition to a family of 6, for this family on-the-go, SO MUCH easier—a fact I am truly, truly grateful for.
This weekend, he really went above and beyond our expectations though.
Not only did he fall asleep in the tent both nights, while the rest of us were out at the camp fire, but he even napped in the tent Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Hour at the Beach</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-hour-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-hour-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>Most people think that perfect beach weather is a bright sunny day, but we discovered unexpected joy in a trip to the Florida beach on an overcast evening following an afternoon rain storm.

Shuttle launch in the morning, nap in the afternoon, beach in the evening, and free Chick-Fil-A right before bed… it was a perfect day in Florida… totally worth the 32 hours of driving it took to get there and back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyday Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everyday-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everyday-fun/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a good week at the circus. Nothing incredibly note worthy, but fun times all around… thought I’d share a few pictures from our week. I love summer… seriously love it. Love the long daylight hours… love the freedom… even love the hot summer sun. 





How about you? What are some of your highlights from the week?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few Little Gems</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-few-little-gems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-few-little-gems/</guid>
      <description>While looking through pictures recently, I stumbled across a few which truly captured life at the circus in its essence.
Exhibit A: taken in December of 2010

Here they are working on the pine wood derby car for Cub Scouts. Notice how everyone, even the baby, is in on the action? Noticed the leotard? My girls wear leotards every.single.day…. even though gymnastics is only twice a week, I can guarantee you those leotards are on more often than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The way They Love Him</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-way-they-love-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-way-they-love-him/</guid>
      <description>As Scott and I worked to put together the scrapbook and video collage for our son’s 1st birthday, we looked at lots and lots of pictures and video clips. As we did, one reoccurring theme, was brought to mind.
This boy is adored by his siblings.
He really has been from day 1. And by day 1, I mean, the day Scott and I told them about the baby in my belly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning Back Time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/turning-back-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/turning-back-time/</guid>
      <description>Ya know that feeling you get when you look at your kids and you just wanna freeze time? You don’t want them to grow up, not one bit, so you just try your best to hold on to the moments while you can.
Well, we figured out a way to freeze time here at the circus…just a little…

Our littlest crew member turned one earlier this month. Not sure how that year flew by so fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting a Closer Look</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/getting-a-closer-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/getting-a-closer-look/</guid>
      <description>I was so glad Scott had the camera handy to snap this shot of our oldest daughter trying to use the view finder at the zoo the other day.

Too short to see through the peep holes?
No problem, I’ll just hoist myself up there with my own 2 arms and take a closer look.
Yea…at 5 she’s already stronger than her mom. No way I could do a chin up, and hold it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Smell Trouble…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-smell-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-smell-trouble/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belly Laughs</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/belly-laughs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/belly-laughs/</guid>
      <description>There are few sounds I cherish more than that of my oldests son’s belly laugh. You just can’t help but smile when something strikes him as truly funny because his laugh is infectious.
Until recently nothing could bring out that laugh like Tom and Jerry or Snoopy. But, then I gave him his very first copy of Mad Libs. And as I listened to him laugh out loud while he filled it in and read it to himself on the couch, well, I had to grab the camera and snap a few pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Does a 1 yr old Eat a Donut?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-does-a-1-yr-old-eat-a-donut/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-does-a-1-yr-old-eat-a-donut/</guid>
      <description>While we’re making him wait till the end of the month to savor his first taste of cake (at his party when his grandparents can be there to ooh and aah), we couldn’t let his day go by without some sort of yummy mess. Enter baby’s first donut for breakfast.

First, he ate each individual sprinkle off of the donut. 

Then, it was time to ditch the hat, and tack a dab at the icing… again using his fingers to scrape it clean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sum, Sum, Summa time!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sum-sum-summa-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sum-sum-summa-time/</guid>
      <description>With temperatures in the nineties this weekend and heat indexes in the hundreds, I’d swear we were celebrating the 4th of July this weekend rather than Memorial Day. We seemed to have gone from winter to summer, with very little spring in between. Wasn’t it just a few short weeks ago we were bundled up at baseball practice in our coats and hats? 
The kids don’t seem to mind a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping with the Cub Scouts</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/camping-with-the-cub-scouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/camping-with-the-cub-scouts/</guid>
      <description>This weekend the family went on a Cub Scout camp out from Friday- Saturday evening. The kids have been begging to go camping again, and this over nighter was the perfect little get away for us. As an added convenience it was at a State Park not far from our house, so it was quite easy to pop home if you needed something and made it no big deal when we got a late start on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break at the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-break-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-break-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>The past week has been spring break at the circus and while it is technically true, we did break from our studies, other than that, it was a jam packed, super busy week.
It is now Monday… school resumes tomorrow, and today I am trying to catch up on laundry and dishes and cleaning… right now, we’re back from gymnastics and the kids are down for quiet time. I am thankful for an iced coffee and the fact that it is warm enough for a skirt and flip flops…oh how I love warm sunny days!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to Once Again Roll that Beautiful Bean Footage</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/time-to-once-again-roll-that-beautiful-bean-footage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 12:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/time-to-once-again-roll-that-beautiful-bean-footage/</guid>
      <description>One of my very first blog posts ever was on my children’s love of kidney beans. It is now 3 years later and my girls have moved on to baked beans. Seriously, the love my daughter has for baked beans can NOT be overstated. Last week I figured it was time to try the kidney beans out on number 4. (let the playgroup mocking begin).


What do you mean I shouldn’t eat too many at once?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time for a Little Mischief</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/time-for-a-little-mischief/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/time-for-a-little-mischief/</guid>
      <description>Quick! I gotta get to the bookshelf to have some fun before one of my siblings notices and tries to stop me.

I know that book is around here somewhere… I just gotta throw some of these papers out of the way first.

Don’t tell Mom it was me, kay? I’m just gonna sit over here and pretend those books were like that when I got here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You think I’d know by now…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-think-id-know-by-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-think-id-know-by-now/</guid>
      <description>When my son asked if he could bring his light sabers or guns to his sisters first soccer practice, I said no. Because sometimes it is awkward to deal with the whole gun issue out in public.
Obviously I forgot that little boys will turn absolutely anything into a gun.
So today I said what the heck, bring the gun. Which apparently translated to, go crazy, carry a gun in each hand and a concealed weapon… Heck, why not wear the entire uniform!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Months Old Today</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/9-months-old-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/9-months-old-today/</guid>
      <description>Look at those chubby hands stuffing his face

I seriously couldn’t stop clicking the camera

Oh, little man, you have captured your Momma’s heart</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potential Black Mail?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/potential-black-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/potential-black-mail/</guid>
      <description>I love that my 3 yr old will happily dress herself in the morning, without even needing to be told. I need, however, to work with her on not wearing clashing patterns&amp;hellip; checkered meets stripes…meets polka dots…

Oh My!!

Apparently, I also need to have the “less is more” discussion with her on make up application. 
Unless of course she plans to be a clown when she grows up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Hodgepodge of Circus Updates</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-hodgepodge-of-circus-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-hodgepodge-of-circus-updates/</guid>
      <description>What day is it? We’ve been a bit out of sorts here at the circus… snow days and a power outage resulting in a fun sleepover at Nana and Pop’s… …now it is Friday, but sure feels like Monday…. we’re home and trying to play catch up on schoolwork, house work and laundry… good news is, when we are done… we’ll still have the weekend to enjoy! And next week is Super Bowl week… and in case you missed it… Pittsburgh’s Going to the Superbowl!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2010</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-2010/</guid>
      <description>Just a few of my favorite pictures of our fun on Christmas morning!
Someone got a lil sleepy waiting up for Santa

The grandparents eagerly waiting for the kids to wake up on Christmas morning.

Does this capture the excitement of Christmas morning, or what? (I wish knew what had just been opened)
 
This tender moment was brought to you by “Lego Star Wars for Wii”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>While You Were Sleeping</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/while-you-were-sleeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/while-you-were-sleeping/</guid>
      <description>I found my 3 yr old like this during nap time today… it seems baby doll has been displaced from her bed. 
It reminded me of a picture I snapped a few weeks ago of both on my girls as we found them when we peeked in on them before going to bed.

YES… they are both sleeping INSIDE of their drawers!
And since I am sharing sleeping pics, why not share a few of my lil man snoozing as well?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am Smitten</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-am-smitten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-am-smitten/</guid>
      <description>You’d think doing this 3 times over already, I would have been prepared.

And yet, once again, my breath has been taken away. I have fallen, and hard.
 
With your irresistible smile, your easy going personality, and your snuggly hugs, I am smitten. 
How can it be that 6 months have already passed since you joined our family? In some ways it seems like you were just born yesterday and in others it seems like you’ve always been a part of our family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bet Your Harvest Party Never Had One of These</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bet-your-harvest-party-never-had-one-of-these/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bet-your-harvest-party-never-had-one-of-these/</guid>
      <description>We decided to add a little pizazz to our normal morning chaos as we got ready to leave for our tutorial today. Since it’s the last day the tutorial is meeting before Thanksgiving, they had a Harvest Party at the end of the day and the children were encouraged to come in costume.
My son went as an Indian and his little sister went as a Pilgrim. (costumes courtesy of Mommy’s costume bin from her school days… I was Pocahontas one year for Halloween and the “Pilgrim” dress was actually a costume from a church play).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Own Little Rebel Alliance</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-own-little-rebel-alliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 03:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-own-little-rebel-alliance/</guid>
      <description>I’ve always wanted a little Yoda for Halloween.

Queen Amidala made an appearance

We also had Padme Amidala

And, of course,Luke Skywalker.

We’re pretty much, eating, breathing, sleeping Star Wars…24/7 round here these days</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highlights from the Week</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/highlights-from-the-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/highlights-from-the-week/</guid>
      <description>A few pics to sum up the week and highlight a few of my favorite moments.

My favorite part of our home schooling day is the beginning. We start with the pledge and a very loud and off key rendition of The Star Spangled Banner. Warms my patriotic soul!
Q: What do home schoolers wear to school?

A: whatever they want.. ie leotards and camos
We made a discovery this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/september-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/september-fun/</guid>
      <description>First Day of School (1st grade and preschool)

County Fair

Soccer Games


Waiting on the sidelines

Learning to play with toys

Steelers 3-0.

It’s been a fabulous month here at the circus!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Hey, Hey, Goodbye!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hey-hey-hey-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hey-hey-hey-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>So long summer 2010….
We’ll forever hold you close in our heart for you were the summer that we welcomed dear sweet, squeezable number 4 to our fold.

We enjoyed your lazy hazy days as we spent time playing in our back yard and splashing in our pool…

We enjoyed time with family



We caught our first keeper… and enjoyed time on Nana and Pop’s boat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Em or Sit Em?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/start-em-or-sit-em/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/start-em-or-sit-em/</guid>
      <description>Woa Dad! What are you thinking? Your starting him on your fantasy team?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lately…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lately/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lately/</guid>
      <description>You may or may not have noticed that lately, I haven’t been blogging much. I can’t put my finger on why exactly.
 
It’s not his fault… he is super easy going. And it isn’t due to lack of fodder… the circus crew provides me with a never ending supply of bloggable material. But, my days have been “more full” lately. Our schedule includes home school, tutorial, gymnastics, soccer, (and cub scouts starting soon).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can’t Get Enough of You Baby</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cant-get-enough-of-you-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cant-get-enough-of-you-baby/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just In Case You Were Wondering…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-in-case-you-were-wondering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-in-case-you-were-wondering/</guid>
      <description>


The youngest circus member is thriving! At 2 and a half months he’s weighing around 15lbs. (my biggest baby yet). So far he is really easy going and super snuggly. A perfect combo for my youngest cast member. We’re on some what of a flexible schedule/routine, which is a huge praise, as we’re starting school next week with the older crew members! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisters</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sisters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sisters/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite things about parenting, is watching my children interact with each other (when they aren’t fighting that is). It’s fascinating to me to see the differences in their bonds and relationships. One relationship which I have observed recently growing is that between my two girls. 

With only 17 mths, and a few inches and pounds between them, they are in so many ways peers. They share much in common, and yet are so very different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bet You’ve Never Seen an Army Quite Like This One</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bet-youve-never-seen-an-army-quite-like-this-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bet-youve-never-seen-an-army-quite-like-this-one/</guid>
      <description>Alternate Title: How Your Army Looks When You Have 2 Younger Sisters

I couldn’t help but smile when I looked out the window and saw this scene…makes me laugh when looking at it on the computer as well. Quite a motley crew we have defending the fortress… the leader in his camo’s with his walking stick (or staff as he refers to it), his trusty sidekicks following in their fairy wings, and Uncle Jim covering from behind with the ever elusive fluorescent double barrel shot gun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess Who’s Back in Town?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/guess-whos-back-in-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/guess-whos-back-in-town/</guid>
      <description>A year ago today my SIL was due to have her first born, my sweet nephew Eli, who the circus children affectionately call “baby Ewi”. I can’t believe he turns one next week!! He’s in town this week eagerly awaiting the arrival of his daddy from Iraq for his R&amp;amp;R.
I am so thankful that I have a SIL who is willing to travel, b/c even though they live in El Paso, we’ve gotten to see them 4 times this past year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s to You Simon and Garfunkel</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/heres-to-you-simon-and-garfunkel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/heres-to-you-simon-and-garfunkel/</guid>
      <description>If summer could have a theme song, well then I think this would be mine for the summer of 2010.
 Slow down, you move too fast. You got to make the morning last. Just kicking down the cobble stones. Looking for fun and feelin&#39; groovy.
Ba da, Ba da, Ba da, Ba da&amp;hellip;Feelin&#39; Groovy.
Hello lamp-post, What cha knowin&#39;? I&amp;rsquo;ve come to watch your flowers growin&#39;. Ain&amp;rsquo;t cha got no rhymes for me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Princess Turns 3</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-princess-turns-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-princess-turns-3/</guid>
      <description>Our third born has literally been on the fast track since birth. I swear she was born holding her head up and eagerly chasing after her older 2 siblings, not wanting to be left out for even a second. She was clearly not meant to be the “baby” of the family.

Most of the time when my kids celebrate a birthday, I find myself reflecting on how quickly time passes and marveling at how could they be so old so fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poor Dad, Get’s No Respect</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/poor-dad-gets-no-respect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/poor-dad-gets-no-respect/</guid>
      <description>While capturing this “precious” Father/Son moment the other day…
 my mind instantly flashed back to a similar “bonding” moment between father and son which I captured 6 years ago…

Seems both my boys enjoy sticking their tongues out at dear old Dad!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday America</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/happy-birthday-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/happy-birthday-america/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Revealed</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mystery-revealed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mystery-revealed/</guid>
      <description>What were my kids doing on the quilt in that picture yesterday? Were they tracking an escaped ant from their ant farm? Were they studying the quilt pattern in preparation for making one of their own? Were they praying over their baby brother?
Not quite
Believe it or not, underneath that pile of circus cast members was our youngest child…
 You kinda get a little glimpse of him here…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Going on Here???</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-is-going-on-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-is-going-on-here/</guid>
      <description>Anyone care to wager a guess as to what is going on in this picture??Winner gets bragging rights</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firsts</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/firsts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 05:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/firsts/</guid>
      <description>First baseball game
 First Wednesday Night Sailing race

First trip to the beach

So many firsts for him to experience…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Was Good While it Lasted</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/it-was-good-while-it-lasted/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/it-was-good-while-it-lasted/</guid>
      <description>Those of you with more than one kiddo know how insanely difficult it is to get a good picture of all your children together….if you don’t know what I am talking about, check out this post or this one, and you will get an idea of what I am referring to. You have aspirations of all three children sitting still, smiling, and looking at the camera. After about 30 clicks of the camera and at least 20 begs and pleas to “look at mommy” and “please sit down” you suddenly set your sights a bit lower and just hope for all of them smiling… who cares where they look and how they sit….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bath time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bath-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bath-time/</guid>
      <description>Visit here  or here  for more Wednesday pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discharge Instructions</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/discharge-instructions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 19:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/discharge-instructions/</guid>
      <description>When our son was 36 hours old we were getting ready to leave the hospital and the nurse came in for official discharge. Those of you who have had kids know this is the time they give you all those important instructions, “back to sleep”, “umbilical cord care….” Those of you who have had more then one kid know that this speech gets progressively less interesting with each discharge. While I am sure the nurse had Scott’s undivided attention the first time we heard the speech, he seemed easily distracted this time around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting the Circus Family</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/meeting-the-circus-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/meeting-the-circus-family/</guid>
      <description>Our son was born at 10:27pm. Unfortunately, because he was born so late, his brother and sisters didn’t get to meet him until the next morning. We loved the first night with him but it felt like the birthing process was somehow incomplete until we were all together. When the moment finally came Scott brought them up and they eagerly ran to the bed to meet him. 
When I told them his name, my son’s face light up as it registered that he got the baby brother he was longing for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s a Boy!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a-boy/</guid>
      <description>This week we welcomed a new member to our family. 
Our sweet baby boy was born this week…
weighing in at 8 lbs 14 oz and measuring 20” long. 
It was love at first sight for all of us. We really can’t get enough of him, so it seems.  I can’t wait to fill you in on the labor story and share the pictures from his fist visit with his big brother and sisters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Pretty, Pretty Princesses</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-pretty-pretty-princesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-pretty-pretty-princesses/</guid>
      <description>Visit here or here for more fun with pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Reason I Love Annapolis</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/another-reason-i-love-annapolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 04:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/another-reason-i-love-annapolis/</guid>
      <description>Each year the Blue Angels perform a show at the Naval Academy in celebration of commissioning week. Taking the kids to watch the show has become one of my favorite Annapolis traditions.
 They fly so close you see the pilot!
 Scott says I have to point the crazy small distance between the wings of the first plane and the cockpit of the next – They do corkscrew loops in that formation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bully Years</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-bully-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-bully-years/</guid>
      <description>I love pictures. I’ll often find myself just staring at the screen saver on our laptop as the pictures scroll by. These two blasts from the pasts crack me up every time they pop onto the screen. They were taken on two totally different occasions, thought it appears my son was approximately the same age in both. It also appears that his red striped shirt was his bully apparel. Does he not look like the kid who would steal your lunch on the playground?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Time Traditions</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-time-traditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-time-traditions/</guid>
      <description>For the past 3 years the kids and I have gone to a local strawberry farm to pick our own berries. It is a tradition I cherish. 
We are suburbanites. We don’t even really garden. But, I love for my children to get some real life farm experiences. I love for them to walk down the rows upon rows of plants.

This year my son really went to town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Tag</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shadow-tag/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shadow-tag/</guid>
      <description>Visit here  or here  for more picture fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where’s Waldo?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wheres-waldo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wheres-waldo/</guid>
      <description>My daughter sleeps with so many animals, pillows, dolls, and blankets in her bed, that sometimes when I go in to kiss her before I go to bed, I can’t find her. One night I thought I saw her and then realized I almost kissed her cabbage patch doll. Can you find her in the pile? It reminds me of the old Where’s Waldo books.
Here’s a closer look… there she is!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just a girl and her dog</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-a-girl-and-her-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-a-girl-and-her-dog/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our All American Boy</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-all-american-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-all-american-boy/</guid>
      <description>We took a lot of pictures of my son’s first baseball game of the season,

but without a doubt, this one is my favorite.

His look truly says it all. Is that the face of a happy ball player or what?
This is what little league is all about…the pure love of the game. May he never outgrow it.
Visit here or here for more picture fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Acres We are There</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/green-acres-we-are-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/green-acres-we-are-there/</guid>
      <description>As the kids and I frolicked around the local farm park with friends the other day, I couldn’t help but smirk at my youngest in her “farm girl” attire.

As she eagerly peeked in on the baby piglets in with her dazzling shades and hot pink purse…

 She wrinkled her nose and said, “Mommy, something is stinky!”
 I couldn’t help but think of Za Za Gabor in Green Acres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teacher’s Helper</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/teachers-helper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/teachers-helper/</guid>
      <description>My daughter really is a very patient teacher’s assistant. She will sit quietly without ever saying a word and listen to her big brother as he sounds out the words to read the Bible story each night. It is quite precious.
And the other day I discovered that having her quiz him on flashcards is the perfect way to let her be involved in school. She happily sits and holds the cards up for him and will praise him when he gets the answers correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign of the Season</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sign-of-the-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sign-of-the-season/</guid>
      <description>You know warm days are once again upon us, when you stumble across your bathroom sink looking like this. 
Probably had something to do with the hours my kids spent digging in the dirt in our backyard this afternoon.
 While they didn’t quite make it to China, they were thrilled to dig down to clay.  I love spring… even with the rings round my tub and the dirt deposits left in my sinks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Smiling Soccer Star</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-smiling-soccer-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-smiling-soccer-star/</guid>
      <description>This weekend my daughter had her second soccer game and I am happy to report it went MUCH better than her first. No tears or pouting and lots of smiles and cute waves to Mom and Dad on the sidelines. She enthusiastically went after the ball and always cheerfully raised her hand to kick off or make the corner kick when they asked for volunteers. Like I said, a drastic improvement over game one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Girls Will Sleep Anywhere</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-girls-will-sleep-anywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-girls-will-sleep-anywhere/</guid>
      <description>I went in to wake my daughter from nap time today and found her like this. 
I’m not sure if she fell asleep while playing or if she was just doing all she could to keep herself from falling asleep. Either way, looks rather uncomfortable to me.
Then there’s her sister.
We looked down during a soccer game a few weeks ago and found her like this.
Yes, that would be my youngest asleep ON the soccer field, during a game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weekend of Egg-citement!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-weekend-of-egg-citement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-weekend-of-egg-citement/</guid>
      <description>This weekend was full of family fun and excitement! Saturday morning the kids went to the neighborhood egg hunt with both sets of grandparents, while Scott and I went to a wedding reception.

The kids had a blast finding eggs and getting their faces painted. 
(some enjoyed the face paint more than others)
That evening (after my son and I got back from a trip to the the after hours clinic where he was diagnosed with pneumonia), we gathered the grands again to dye Easter eggs with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check Your Windows…I think pigs are flying</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/check-your-windowsi-think-pigs-are-flying/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/check-your-windowsi-think-pigs-are-flying/</guid>
      <description>I can’t explain it, but there is some innate, motherly, compulsion,need, desire to force my kids to pose nicely in their Easter clothes. More often than not, this event results in a very patient dad who kindly obliges his wife and tortures his kids, 3 restless and bored children and ultimately a disappointed mom who is stuck with 30 pictures of her kids in their clothes, and yet not one where they are all smiling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Fish, Two Fish</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-fish-two-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-fish-two-fish/</guid>
      <description>On Friday night we took advantage of the aquarium’s last discount priced Friday night of the season and enjoyed some family fun.

We took 293 pictures during our 3 hours at the aquarium. From those we narrowed down 42 keepers. 
And from those, I have the difficult task of dwindling down some for the blog. 
The kids favorite part of the evening was the dolphin show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backyard Warfare</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/backyard-warfare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/backyard-warfare/</guid>
      <description>There is a huge pile of bamboo in our backyard waiting for a run to the dump on Saturday. Until then, it provided the perfect landscape for my son to build a fort and play war. He stayed out there for hours and was so proud of his camouflage. 
Unfortunatly, his gun kinda gives him away.
When I showed this picture to my husband I said it should be called,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Quite Big Enough for The Job</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-quite-big-enough-for-the-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-quite-big-enough-for-the-job/</guid>
      <description>As we were walking out the door this morning, I heard my daughter exclaim, “Oh it’s raining, better grab my umbrella!” 
I wondered what she was talking about since we don’t have any umbrellas in our house. (Who needs one more thing to juggle? We just get wet, it’s the circus way)! Then I saw her walking to the car with her Little People umbrella over her head. She then carried this umbrella over her head into and out of the grocery store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Many Outfits Can One Girl Wear?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-many-outfits-can-one-girl-wear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-many-outfits-can-one-girl-wear/</guid>
      <description>My girls, especially my youngest, love to change clothes. And often. It borders on ridiculous. I knew if I didn’t document it, no one would believe me.
So, take a look at Thursdays attire here at the circus. (I will mention that we never left the house today). The day started at 7:00am, didn’t have the camera ready then, but here she is at 8:30am. (wearing the clothes she wore last night plus a coat)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Dance</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-wanna-dance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-wanna-dance/</guid>
      <description>I’ve seen various posts every now and then linked up to I Heart faces weekly photo contests. And I’ve thought about entering, but then never did. When I heard the theme this week was “I Wanna Dance” I knew I had to link up a picture from our impromptu New Years Eve dance party in our living room. The hardest part for me, was picking which picture. Hope I made the right choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow Week Math</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/snow-week-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/snow-week-math/</guid>
      <description>Thought you might enjoy a little simple math to recap the week here at the circus. Add together the following totals….
 2 major snowstorms 33 inches of snow fallen 1 official blizzard  
 20 cups of hot chocolate drank 2 types of cookies baked  
 1 Daddy sized igloo built  
 1 sledding hill      0 power outages
 1 sleepover with our cousin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Then and Now</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/then-and-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/then-and-now/</guid>
      <description>Took the kids for a walk to the park. Nothing exceptional about that, except I realized when looking through pictures that exactly 2 years before I had done the same thing.
We were compelled to go because of the exceptional weather.
Funny how life repeats itself.
Only it doesn’t.
2 years ago, we didn’t wear jackets.  
 In fact, if you look close… some of us weren’t even wearing shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Winter Unlike Any I’ve Ever Seen</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-winter-unlike-any-ive-ever-seen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-winter-unlike-any-ive-ever-seen/</guid>
      <description>Most years when I put together our family scrapbooks, our “Fun in the Snow” spread looks something like this. Notice the grass poking through the snow and the pathetic little snowball snowman my son built?
But, this winter has been crazy! We had a record breaking snowfall in December. Then, last week we got a good 6 inches of snowfall (which in any normal MD winter, would have made us giddy with excitement).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seems I’m Not the Only One with a Baby Bump</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/seems-im-not-the-only-one-with-a-baby-bump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/seems-im-not-the-only-one-with-a-baby-bump/</guid>
      <description> I looked at my daughter this morning and noticed her belly had gotten much bigger. “What is in your jammies”, I asked. She informed me that she too had a baby in her belly.

If only my pregnancy could be so short and my delivery so easy. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Look</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-look/</guid>
      <description>This week my baby girl asked me to put her hair in two braids. When did her hair get long enough to braid? 
She was quite excited to pose for me afterwards.
 Doesn’t she look so grown up? Seriously, when did this happen?

Visit here or here for more fun with pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old School E-mail</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/old-school-e-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/old-school-e-mail/</guid>
      <description>My oldest two have gotten into the habit of “e-mailing” each other at the beginning of nap time. And by e-mailing they really mean they are drawing pictures and writing messages back and forth to each other. We’ve worked out a system in which they are allowed to e-mail for the first 30 minutes of nap time. Then, they have to have quiet time in separate rooms for the remaining hour and a half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Choose the Caption</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-choose-the-caption/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-choose-the-caption/</guid>
      <description>Didn’t take many pics around the circus this week, but when I downloaded pics off of my camera this afternoon, I stumbled across this gem from last week. 
Please help me pick a title. My brain is a bit mushy this Friday afternoon. Winning caption gets put at the top of my post! I know that’s an honor your all scrambling to achieve, so please… tell me your thoughts and brighten this circus mom’s day with some comment love!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silly Sisters Sharing Secrets</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/silly-sisters-sharing-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/silly-sisters-sharing-secrets/</guid>
      <description>Visit here or here for more pictures!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dancing in the New Year</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dancing-in-the-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dancing-in-the-new-year/</guid>
      <description>This year we celebrated New Years in two parts. We did a family fun night with the kids concluding at 8 with followed by a date night with the two of us to officially ring in the new year. 
Here are some pictures of my son cutting it up on the impromptu dance floor in our living room. He was having a blast, as I am sure you can tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Someone Stole a Cookie from the Cookie Jar</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/someone-stole-a-cookie-from-the-cookie-jar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/someone-stole-a-cookie-from-the-cookie-jar/</guid>
      <description>Who me?
 Couldn’t be

Then, who?

Visit here or here for more fun with pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas from the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/merry-christmas-from-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/merry-christmas-from-the-circus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Since There’s No Place to Go…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-since-theres-no-place-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-since-theres-no-place-to-go/</guid>
      <description>Let it Snow, Let it Snow, Let it Snow!!!
Growing up and living in the midAtlantic region means that snow is something we are familiar with, but we don’t encounter on a regular basis. It’s not like we’re living in Houston and a dusting of snow occurs once a decade. But, it also isn’t unreasonable that I don’t go out and purchase snow suits for my kids every winter either. We can typically anticipate seeing snowfall at least once a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weekend of Celebrating</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-weekend-of-celebrating/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2009 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-weekend-of-celebrating/</guid>
      <description>What a full and festive weekend we had here at the circus! Friday night Scott and I got all dressed up for a fun and fancy Christmas party! We got to enjoy tasty appetizers, holiday drinks, and the opportunity to sit and chat with old friends. A super way to start the weekend. (Though the baby did not like the cheese dip I ate too much of and I paid for that with an upset stomach later that night).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Thing I was Planning on Baking</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/good-thing-i-was-planning-on-baking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/good-thing-i-was-planning-on-baking/</guid>
      <description>What is it about stick of butter that my children find so irresistible? Why is it when I have the forethought to set the butter out on the counter to soften, my children see it as invitation to squish it? At least this time, they didn’t use their fingers and smear it all over the counters.
  Thankfully, it wasn’t butter to be spread on bread, but instead I am hoping to bake some cookies this afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Tradition: Cutting Down Our Tree</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-favorite-tradition-cutting-down-our-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-favorite-tradition-cutting-down-our-tree/</guid>
      <description>The hunt begins…
Gloves?

Check.
Tree cart?

Check.
Now to find the perfect tree.
“How about this one I suggest?”
“No, that looks like an angel tree,” my son says. “We need to find a star tree.”
My son doesn’t like when there are too many branches on the bottom as they are harder to cut down. (We always pick spruces and they are quite painful and prickly).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There She Is!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/there-she-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/there-she-is/</guid>
      <description>Is someone there?

Nope…
 Oh, yes there is…..
 
That girl sure makes me smile. I don’t want to overdo it but I had to at least provide a link to just one more of my favorites from this series for those so inclined.
Or, click here or here for more wordless Wednesday fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons Learned While Raking Leaves</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lessons-learned-while-raking-leaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lessons-learned-while-raking-leaves/</guid>
      <description>1. Two rakes and three kids does not make for a happy equation. 2. Make sure your kids have their shoes securely tied before you begin raking. Otherwise you could rake a pile like this only to have your son tell you it was time to go on a “treasure hunt” to find his missing shoes in said pile.
3. If your going to jump into the pile with the kids, don’t wear baggy jeans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Momma Bear Protecting Her Young</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/momma-bear-protecting-her-young/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/momma-bear-protecting-her-young/</guid>
      <description>Visit here or here for more Wednesday Picture Fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field Trip Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/field-trip-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/field-trip-fun/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite parts about home schooling has been the field trips. We have tutorial sessions on Mon and Wed. Tues we have school at home and typically it is a catch up day for me around the house. I try to keep Tuesdays open as I need that day to just be at home. Thursdays we have school at home, plus BSF in the morning, and often a play date over lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Girl Learns to Fly</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/super-girl-learns-to-fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 03:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/super-girl-learns-to-fly/</guid>
      <description>Visit here or here for more fun with pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trick or Treat Time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/trick-or-treat-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/trick-or-treat-time/</guid>
      <description>
Super Girl  Bumblebee the Transformer

And our Little Kangaroo

We had a wonderful time playing with and visiting with our neighbors, dressing up in costumes, and begging for candy. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only at the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/only-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2009 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/only-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>In the past month, these pictures were taken during meal time at our home. I can assure you that these antics don’t take place regularly around here, but at the same time, they do happen. After all, it is the circus.
Exhibit A: playing with our food

“Look Mom, I can make vowels with my spaghetti!”

Exhibit B:  Yes, that would be my son eating his applesauce while sitting on his Daddy’s shoulders (and yes, to make it truly circus like, he’s in his underwear).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Hurts</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/love-hurts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/love-hurts/</guid>
      <description>I love this picture. I love it because it shows the kids and my husband engaged in play after a long day of work. 
I also love how the big kids seem to be attacking him b/c he’s got the youngest on his shoulders. Almost as if they are trying to get in on the action and attention. But take a closer look, because if you check out Scott’s face, you’ll find another gem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Exactly Something You See Everyday</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-exactly-something-you-see-everyday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 07:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-exactly-something-you-see-everyday/</guid>
      <description>Not everyday you see an Oriole wrapped in a Steelers Terrible Towel. Click here or here for more picture fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony Rides</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pony-rides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 05:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pony-rides/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Much Has Changed</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-much-has-changed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-much-has-changed/</guid>
      <description>Here’s my daughter sleeping in her crib at 8 months old.
 And here she is at 14 mths old. Still enjoys sleeping “folded in half”, as we refer to it.
 
Earlier this week when my husband went in to kiss the kids goodnight, he found her at 3 and 1/2 sleeping in the very same position she favored as an infant.  I would think with age this position would grow more impossible and uncomfortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Picking</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/apple-picking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/apple-picking/</guid>
      <description>We came home with so much more than freshly picked apples…

 

we returned with smiles, laughter, and many fond memories
  Visit here or here for more fun with pictures!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Than Just the Animals</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/more-than-just-the-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/more-than-just-the-animals/</guid>
      <description>This year in addition to the farm animals, the kids enjoyed some other treats at the county fair. Rides


Cotton Candy
 
And a visit with Spiderman himself

So, what’s your favorite part of the fair? The animals, the rides, the food, or the super heroes?
Visit here or here for more fun with pictures!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun at the County Fair</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fun-at-the-county-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 03:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fun-at-the-county-fair/</guid>
      <description>Every fall, since my first born was only 5 months old, I’ve taken my children to the county fair. We don’t by any stretch live in a rural area, so I am sure some of you country folk would laugh and heckle what we call a county fair. But, for my suburbanite children and I, it offers a rare opportunity to see some farm animals up close. It is a fall tradition we look forward to all summer long!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Big and Yet So Small</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-big-and-yet-so-small/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-big-and-yet-so-small/</guid>
      <description>After months of deliberating, praying, waiting, and a little second guessing, the first day of school finally arrived this week. As you may recall we decided to home school, but with a twist. We’ve enrolled our son in a home school tutorial that he attends two days a week. So he has school at home with me three days a week, and at his tutorial 2 days a week. In a lot of ways, it’s the best of both worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Déjà vu</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/d%C3%A9j%C3%A0-vu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 03:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/d%C3%A9j%C3%A0-vu/</guid>
      <description>Last week I captured this sweet father/daughter moment. 
Which reminded me an awful lot of a very similar moment captured a year ago.
Funny how life repeats itself, isn’t it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summa Time Favs</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summa-time-favs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summa-time-favs/</guid>
      <description>With the arrival of cool, autumn like weather this week and Labor Day weekend approaching at the weeks end, I suppose it’s time to admit that summer is over.
To commemorate it’s end, I thought I’d share a few of my favorite things about summer here at the circus. So here they are…in no particular order…
Lightening Bug Catching

Wednesday Night Races

Swimming

Fishing

Corn on the Cob</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures Can’t Do the Day Justice</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pictures-cant-do-the-day-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pictures-cant-do-the-day-justice/</guid>
      <description>During our recent visit to El Paso, we survived the desert trek to reach Carlsbad Caverns ( number 23 of the 47 U.S. National Parks we plan to visit in our life together). It was a perfect day alone with the man of my dreams exploring and enjoying God’s creation. We spent 5 hours exploring the caves 800 feet below the earth’s surface.
Pictures truly can’t do it justice, but I’ll try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daddy’s Girl</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/daddys-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/daddys-girl/</guid>
      <description>Can you tell she loves her Daddy? You can almost hear her giggle with glee as she hugs him. That’s love…
So pure and sweet
 
   May it only grow stronger with time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Exactly Girlie Girls</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-exactly-girlie-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-exactly-girlie-girls/</guid>
      <description>(though they are wearing dresses)
Visit here or here for more Wednesday fun with pictures!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s a Bird, It’s a Plane, It’s…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a-bird-its-a-plane-its/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a-bird-its-a-plane-its/</guid>
      <description>Super Girl!
Fighting for justice for little sisters everywhere!!

Bad guys (and brothers) beware!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not quite picture perfect</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-quite-picture-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-quite-picture-perfect/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago we celebrated our youngest child’s second birthday. Naturally on an occasion as significant as a birthday, we had our camera out quite a bit trying to capture every moment of the celebration. It wasn’t till we looked at the pics later on the computer that I realized at perhaps some moments would have been better left, not captured!
Since she loves dogs, we did a puppy dog theme for her party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spellbound</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spellbound/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spellbound/</guid>
      <description>I was enchanted by my youngest on Saturday as she played with her dolls. She played quietly and contently for at least an hour. I could have done so much with that time and yet I couldn’t take my eyes off of her. She barely noticed my presence as she sat and arranged her dolls, poured their imaginary tea, and made sure everyone got a sip. Then repeated the endearing process over and over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof is in the batter</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proof-is-in-the-batter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proof-is-in-the-batter/</guid>
      <description>Yea… the older two never would have been allowed to lick the cake batter on their second birthday cakes… “The babies of the family always get away with more.”
Click here for wordless or here for wordful wednesday photos!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Picture Perfect Day on the Farm</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-picture-perfect-day-on-the-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2009 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-picture-perfect-day-on-the-farm/</guid>
      <description>I think my girls make good farm gals, don’t you?

Visit here or here for more Wednesday fun with pictures!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabulous Fourth Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fabulous-fourth-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fabulous-fourth-fun/</guid>
      <description>My little crew in red, white, and blue.
 First time playing with sparklers.
 
Visit here  or here  for more Wednesday picture fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And now for something completely different</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-now-for-something-completely-different/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2009 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-now-for-something-completely-different/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been to a few parades in my day. Unlike the kids, I’m not all that surprised by what I see. I’ve come to expect the fire trucks, army tanks, corvettes, marching bands…
This year however, there were a few things I hadn’t seen before. 
Gotta love keeping it green with the organic fertilizer. Not your typical parade entry.
This was probably my favorite though. 
I’m all for safety, really I am, but if that missile accidentally goes off, how much good will that fire extinguisher do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pirates Life for Me</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-pirates-life-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 18:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-pirates-life-for-me/</guid>
      <description>This weekend, I surprised Scott and the kids with a high seas adventure in Annapolis. After donning their costumes  
And getting their tattoos

We were ready to board the ship and set sail in search of our treasure

The kids used their loot to purchase ice cream for dinner. A good time was had by all. Though I fear the pirate life may agree too well with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Little Photo Journalist</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-little-photo-journalist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-little-photo-journalist/</guid>
      <description>We keep our digital “point and shoot” camera on the counter. My 5 year old calls it “his camera.” He has permission to run and grab it to snap photos when something catches his fancy. Every now and then I’ll download them and enjoy a glimpse of life around the circus through the eyes of my eldest. He was so excited about this puddle that he found on the deck a few weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Someday, maybe</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/someday-maybe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/someday-maybe/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been a mom of three for almost two years and I have yet to figure out how to successfully take a good pic of my three kids together. And yet, I keep trying…call me hopelessly optimistic, stubborn, or just plain slow to learn, but I keep holding out hope that one day I’ll snap that illustrious shot of my circus crew.
Here we have two sideward glances with a smirk and one squinter in the sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep on Reading Girlie</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keep-on-reading-girlie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keep-on-reading-girlie/</guid>
      <description>Looking forward to seeing how things improve at the circus after she finishes with her quiet reading time.

Visit 5M4M or 7 Clown Circus for more fun with pictures!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things That Make Me Smile</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/things-that-make-me-smile/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2009 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/things-that-make-me-smile/</guid>
      <description>Pigtails on toddlers

Polish on toenails

Dirt covered faces

Band aid mustaches</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One of My Favorite Springtime Traditions</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-of-my-favorite-springtime-traditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 03:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-of-my-favorite-springtime-traditions/</guid>
      <description>Each May the Blue Angels do an air show at the Naval Academy as part of the commencement week celebrations. It is practically a holiday around here. (If you don’t believe me, check the sign out sheets that afternoon at the local schools). Scott actually saves half a vacation day each year so we can enjoy them as a family.



Hmm, do you think we enjoyed ourselves?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where did my baby go?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/where-did-my-baby-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2009 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/where-did-my-baby-go/</guid>
      <description>Something happened to my baby girl.
Seems she was just learning to crawl.
How is that she’s running around, skinning her knees and swinging beside the big kids?
Didn’t she know she wasn’t supposed to grow up so fast?
She’s my baby.
What is she doing conversing and counting and going on the potty?
Where did my baby go?
And who is this pig tailed princess that’s serenading us in the morning with her sweet cherub voice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Could Do This All Day</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-could-do-this-all-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-could-do-this-all-day/</guid>
      <description>Vist 5M4M  for more WW</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clowning Around</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/clowning-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2009 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/clowning-around/</guid>
      <description>For a good time at the circus
 
simply wear your underwear on your head!!

My son pleaded to his Daddy the other night,
“Please, Please, Please wear underwear on your head…It can be clean!” </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Just Like That He Turned Me Into a Baseball Fan</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-just-like-that-he-turned-me-into-a-baseball-fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-just-like-that-he-turned-me-into-a-baseball-fan/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5M4M for more WW</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Role Reversal</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/role-reversal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/role-reversal/</guid>
      <description>The other night at dinner my daughter was not so excited about eating her peas.

So, her little sister decided to step in and help her!

Sisters make everything better… even eating your greens!

Sometimes you just need a little encouragement!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barefoot Princess</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/barefoot-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/barefoot-princess/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5M4M for more WW!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe for a Good Time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/recipe-for-a-good-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2009 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/recipe-for-a-good-time/</guid>
      <description>Two cookies
 One mug of milk
 
And two sisters

Visit 5M4M  and Angie’s 7 Ring Circus for more Picture Fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Bend: From Sunup to Sundown</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/big-bend-from-sunup-to-sundown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/big-bend-from-sunup-to-sundown/</guid>
      <description>The sun’s rays cast a bright orange glow on the rocks when it rose in the morning.

As the day went on, the bees came out to pollinate the flora.

As the day progressed, we were able to pose for the very significant sign shot. Click here to learn of it’s high importance.

As the sun began to set the rocks began to change color yet again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just the Three of Us</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-the-three-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-the-three-of-us/</guid>
      <description>Timely, we are not.
But we do follow through…eventually.
We promised our daughter on her third birthday in early Feb, that her gift from us would be a special trip with Mommy and Daddy to make her own teddy bear.
Two months later, the magical moment happened.
After dropping her siblings off at Nana and Pop’s, Scott and I realized this was the first time we had spent time, just the three of us, since she was in the hospital three years ago!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snap Shots of the Circus This Week</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/snap-shots-of-the-circus-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 06:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/snap-shots-of-the-circus-this-week/</guid>
      <description>Not exactly wordless this week, but since it is in fact Wednesday, I decided to share some pictures from our week.
Our Little Lady: All dressed up with no place to go!

She was so proud when she discovered her “new trick” “Mom, I can do my ‘noisy medicine’ (aka nebulizer) while playing legos…this is my new trick!”

Someone got into Mommy’s dresser and proudly paraded down the hall saying, “Pretty”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Someday</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/someday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/someday/</guid>
      <description>Someday when I open my silverware drawer I will find each piece sitting neatly in the slot it belongs.
Someday my kids won’t come running when they hear me opening the dishwasher, eager to help put the dishes away.
And I will look back on these days when my 19 mth old did it all by herself with longing.
So, today I am enjoying the help!
 
Check out 5M4M for actual Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the Hood</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/in-the-hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2009 05:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/in-the-hood/</guid>
      <description>My daughter loves to change her clothes. We go through a clothing change at least, AT LEAST 4 times a day. Thankfully, she can dress herself and requires little assistance from me. Typically she rotates through her most favorite articles of clothing. In addition to her candy pants, she’s added a silk pair of pj pants to her collection, as well as a too tight Winnie the Pooh pajama shirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Miss Independent Dresses Herself</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/little-miss-independent-dresses-herself/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/little-miss-independent-dresses-herself/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5M4M  for more WW!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy Spring Weather</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/crazy-spring-weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/crazy-spring-weather/</guid>
      <description>From this

to this

in just 5 days!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Snow Angel</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-snow-angel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-snow-angel/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5MFM for more Wordless Fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing Dress Up</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/playing-dress-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/playing-dress-up/</guid>
      <description>“A sister shares childhood memories and grown-up dreams.”

 Check out 5MFM for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Circus Clown</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-circus-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-circus-clown/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Wednesdays!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She’s Got the Look</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shes-got-the-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shes-got-the-look/</guid>
      <description>My oldest daughter has been demonstrating her growing independence and her new sense of style these days. Her new favorite pants are these orange leggings with candy corn on them that she got at Halloween. I don’t know what made her take such a liking to them this January but she wants to wear them EVERY. SINGLE. DAY. When she wanted to wear them to the park a few weeks ago with her purple sweater, I started to try and persuade her to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everybody Needs a Friend</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everybody-needs-a-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 03:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everybody-needs-a-friend/</guid>
      <description>This is what I found after my daughter was playing with her doll house.

 Visit 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrestling with Daddy</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wrestling-with-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wrestling-with-daddy/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5 Minutes for Mom for more WW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here We Go Steelers, Here We Go!!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/here-we-go-steelers-here-we-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 19:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/here-we-go-steelers-here-we-go/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5M4M for more WW</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Can Stop At Just One Oreo?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-can-stop-at-just-one-oreo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-can-stop-at-just-one-oreo/</guid>
      <description>Click here for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Christmas Bliss</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/more-christmas-bliss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/more-christmas-bliss/</guid>
      <description>After spending Christmas morning at our house with my wonderful in-laws and grandpa in law, we went to PA this weekend to celebrate with my parents and my brother&amp;rsquo;s family. I just had to share some more candid gems because they just warmed my heart and I feel my hubby did a great job of capturing the love and fun of our day together.
We all had lunch together on Sunday and afterwards the youngest two of our crews took naps while everyone else enjoyed a relaxing afternoon of play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas in the Capital</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-in-the-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-in-the-capital/</guid>
      <description>While these were beautiful sights to behold,

[ ] (https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/12/img-11623.jpg)

She stole the show for me.
[] (https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/12/img-11263.jpg)
And while we did enjoy taking in the lights,

and some holiday cheer,


Everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite part was the journey home. &amp;lt;&amp;ndash; Last Mondays Post
Visit 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candid Gems</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/candid-gems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/candid-gems/</guid>
      <description>Christmas provides you with many gems&amp;hellip;photos which capture the moment, in real life. Nothing like posing in front of the tree to bring out the true personality of your child.
Yes&amp;hellip; this is def what I meant when I said , &amp;ldquo;Smile in front of the camera so Mom can have a picture of you in your nice church clothes.&amp;rdquo;

I love this pic&amp;hellip; I am entitling it Christmas bliss&amp;hellip; I love that it is not posed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jesus&#39; Birthday Party</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/jesus-birthday-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2008 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/jesus-birthday-party/</guid>
      <description>Last night the kids helped me decorate a birthday cake for Jesus and after singing Him Happy Birthday, followed by a few favorite Christmas carols, we enjoyed cake and ice cream.

Apparently, it is an unwritten rule in our house that when you eat Jesus&#39; birthday cake, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to use silverware.
[] (https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/12/seriously-forks-are-overrated-in-this-house.jpg)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Morning at the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-morning-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-morning-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Cookie Baking Time!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-cookie-baking-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-cookie-baking-time/</guid>
      <description>After years of research in my test kitchen, I have found that Krusteaz sugar cookie mix tastes better than any of the &amp;ldquo;from scratch sugar cookies&amp;rdquo; I have made.
And not only do they taste good, but literally, you pour the mix, add water, and stir!!

This is crucial for me, because with my three preschoolers, Mommy needs to spend her time managing the flour and cutting out of the cookies, not measuring and mixing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY long enough for pig tails</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/finally-long-enough-for-pig-tails/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 19:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/finally-long-enough-for-pig-tails/</guid>
      <description>Now if I could just get her to leave them in longer than the time it takes for me to pull them up&amp;hellip;
.
Visit 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof that the sound of quiet isn&#39;t a good thing...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proof-that-the-sound-of-quiet-isnt-a-good-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 06:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proof-that-the-sound-of-quiet-isnt-a-good-thing/</guid>
      <description>Hmmm, it&amp;rsquo;s a bit too quiet, better go investigate&amp;hellip;

What Mom? You didn&amp;rsquo;t want me to wash my sister&amp;rsquo;s hair?
Hmm, well I wasn&amp;rsquo;t doing that, honest&amp;hellip; I was ummm washing my hands&amp;hellip;
Yea&amp;hellip;no idea how her hair got so wet&amp;hellip;.

Mom, When&amp;rsquo;s payback time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Saint Nicholas</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/meet-saint-nicholas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/meet-saint-nicholas/</guid>
      <description>My son often refers to Santa as Saint Nicholas. I guess it&amp;rsquo;s because of reading Jolly Old Saint Nicholas and Twas the Night Before Christmas.
This week my son decided he wanted to pretend to be Saint Nicholas.
Meet Jolly Old Saint Nick himself&amp;hellip;

Check out his sleigh (the blanket&amp;hellip;see him holding the reigns?) and note the stuffed bear playing the roll of reindeer.

Filling the stockings&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOTCHA!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gotcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gotcha/</guid>
      <description>Visit 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Wonders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow, What Fun!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/snow-what-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/snow-what-fun/</guid>
      <description>The kids were treated to a few inches of snow at Grandma and Grandpa&amp;rsquo;s last week. It was just enough for some sledding!

It&amp;rsquo;s easy to see that a good time was had by all. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t my baby look like an oompa loompa? I gotta confess I had quite a few laughs at her expense watching her try to walk around in her big sisters boots and snow suit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Leaf Jumping!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/extreme-leaf-jumping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/extreme-leaf-jumping/</guid>
      <description>Visit 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Fun</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Only...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/if-only/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/if-only/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I took a nature walk last week. As we walked along the path, I realized we had necessary elements for some great pictures.
1. Happy Kids
2. Setting sun
3. Fall leaves
However, we forgot the photographer.
After frolicking along the path gathering leaves and sticks, I noticed that the suns rays were really quite beautiful. I remembered Scott saying that one of the best times of days to get pictures is before sunset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Cry Over Spilled Milk</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-cry-over-spilled-milk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-cry-over-spilled-milk/</guid>
      <description>I have to tell myself this quite often at the circus. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s just milk, no use crying over it or making anyone else cry over it.&amp;rdquo; This time, the spill was my fault as I dropped the full gallon of milk over myself and my floor&amp;hellip;

No use crying over it, so I snapped a picture. Check out 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordess Wednesdays!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Rock Star?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/future-rock-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/future-rock-star/</guid>
      <description>Last week the kids were having a jam session in the living room with their play guitar and drums. As we looked at my son&amp;rsquo;s pose, with his tongue out, and his fingers holding the &amp;ldquo;chords&amp;rdquo; on the guitar, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but think he had a startling resemblance to KISS (minus the face paint)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Generic Diapers are NOT my Friends!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/why-generic-diapers-are-not-my-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/why-generic-diapers-are-not-my-friends/</guid>
      <description>Click here for more pics which need no explanation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kiss From Her Prince</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-kiss-from-her-prince/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 19:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-kiss-from-her-prince/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trick or Treat!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/trick-or-treat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/trick-or-treat/</guid>
      <description>[] (https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/11/img-9181.jpg)
Our neighborhood has two days of trick or treating&amp;hellip;because one night of filling your pumpkin with candy just isn&amp;rsquo;t enough. The shopping plaza in our neighborhood hosts a trick or treating event every year the day before Halloween. It feels like a celebration right out of Gilmore Girls as we stroll from store to store getting candy. It&amp;rsquo;s become a sort of tradition for us to visit Scott&amp;rsquo;s parents and grandparents after this so they can see them in their costumes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick em up!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/stick-em-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/stick-em-up/</guid>
      <description>I cracked up laughing when they came down the hall like this. Don&amp;rsquo;t they look like a couple of bank robbers? The best part is that later that week when I went to put this pair of underwear on my son, he told me, &amp;ldquo;Mom, I can&amp;rsquo;t wear these, they are my mask!&amp;rdquo;

Check out 5 Minutes for Mom, for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Can Almost Hear Him Giggle</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-can-almost-hear-him-giggle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-can-almost-hear-him-giggle/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Things Are Timeless...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-things-are-timeless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 05:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-things-are-timeless/</guid>
      <description>Bil Keane originally published this in the 60&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;isn&amp;rsquo;t it great to know some things never change?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puppy Love</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/puppy-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/puppy-love/</guid>
      <description>Check out 5 Minutes for Mom, for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death of a Scare Crow</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/death-of-a-scare-crow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/death-of-a-scare-crow/</guid>
      <description>My oldest two kids and I decided to commemorate the beautiful fall weather this week, by making our very first scare crow. Because we don&amp;rsquo;t live on a farm and straw is horribly overpriced in these city parts, we opted to stuff our scare crow girl with leaves. We built her during our baby&amp;rsquo;s nap time, but she woke just in time to watch us put the finishing touches on her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Those Pesky Alumni Shots</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/those-pesky-alumni-shots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/those-pesky-alumni-shots/</guid>
      <description>Our College has an alumni book which they publish quarterly. In the back is a section where they put baby pics of the alumni&amp;rsquo;s children (wearing their GCC shirts of course).
When our son was born we were so excited to contact the school and get our tee shirt. I remember taking the picture when he was around 10 mths old. Our hard drive crashed the next day and while we did eventually get all the pictures back, when we did that GCC pic was no longer in the fore front of my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Point of View</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-point-of-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 19:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-point-of-view/</guid>
      <description>Look who&amp;rsquo;s facing forward now!
(Yes, I know she&amp;rsquo;s been legal for 2 mths now, but I read somewhere it was technically safer to face backwards as long as possible, so we delayed turning her around).

Her response, &amp;ldquo;Hey! Where&amp;rsquo;d my brother and sister go? Now I have to stare at the back of Mommy and Daddy&amp;rsquo;s head!&amp;rdquo;

Check out 5 Minutes for Mom  for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Days are so Fleeting</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/these-days-are-so-fleeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/these-days-are-so-fleeting/</guid>
      <description>I gotta confess from the start, this is not quite Wordless.

As I was tidying up the house during nap time this week, I found this in my kitchen. I bent down to pick them up and decided to snap a quick picture first. Because some day, my kids will be grown and in school, and I won&amp;rsquo;t find half dressed baby dolls lying on the floor beside toy guns with my vacuum attachment stuck on top to turn it into a light saber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping with Baby Doll</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sleeping-with-baby-doll/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sleeping-with-baby-doll/</guid>
      <description>For more Wordless Wednesdays, visit 5 Minutes for Mom  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take Me Out to the Ballgame</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/take-me-out-to-the-ballgame/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/take-me-out-to-the-ballgame/</guid>
      <description>My son is an individual. Despite the fact that his parents are crazy football fans and could care less about baseball, he decided when he was about 2 that he loved baseball. He&amp;rsquo;d willingly sit and watch it on TV. We&amp;rsquo;ve even Tivoed a few games for him or let him watch portions of Sports Center. We&amp;rsquo;ve taken him to a few minor league games in the past, but tonight we took our oldest two children to their first Major League Baseball Game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story Time in a Unique Place</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/story-time-in-a-unique-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/story-time-in-a-unique-place/</guid>
      <description>For more Wordless Wednesdays, check out 5 Minutes for Mom  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Got Back</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/baby-got-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2008 18:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/baby-got-back/</guid>
      <description>Here is what happens when you let your two year old go swimming without one of those handy, dandy swimmy diapers. We brought one along on our trip to the pond this weekend, but didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like going through the effort of taking off her bathing suit and changing her diaper.
&amp;ldquo;How much water will the diaper collect, anyway?&amp;rdquo; We naively thought.

Apparently, these Luvs diapers can hold quite a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bakers Dozen</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-bakers-dozen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-bakers-dozen/</guid>
      <description>What do you get at an annual weekend get together of 6 high school friends and their families?

13 children 4 and under (ages 4, 3, 3, 3, 2.5, 2.5, 2, 1.5, 1, 1, 1, 1, &amp;lt;1)
Check out 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Wednesdays!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is Cute!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-is-cute/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-is-cute/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday my son called for me to, &amp;ldquo;Come quick Mom and look, she&amp;rsquo;s so cute!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;hellip; I think he&amp;rsquo;s got a good eye, don&amp;rsquo;t you?

For More Wordless Wednesdays, check out 5 Minutes for Mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Taste of &#39;Kid Beer&#39;</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/first-taste-of-kid-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2008 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/first-taste-of-kid-beer/</guid>
      <description>My son was so excited about the favor we brought home from my friend&amp;rsquo;s wedding a few weeks ago. They gave out old fashioned root beer in bottles with a home made label. It was his first soda and he was so excited to drink &amp;ldquo;kid beer&amp;rdquo; as he called it.




I think he liked the idea of it more than the actual taste. He actually drank most of it the next day when it was flat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daddy&#39;s Little Helper</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/daddys-little-helper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/daddys-little-helper/</guid>
      <description>Click here for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Daddy Entertains the Kids</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-daddy-entertains-the-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-daddy-entertains-the-kids/</guid>
      <description>I downloaded pictures recently and was surprised to find this.

and this

and let&amp;rsquo;s not leave out this&amp;hellip;

It appears that Daddy decided to let this kids take pictures (a twist for us, as typically Mommy or Daddy are the ones behind the camera) When asked why the goofy faces he replied, &amp;ldquo;I had to come up with new things for them to take pictures of.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fun Summer Moment</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-fun-summer-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-fun-summer-moment/</guid>
      <description>I am entering this picture in a photo contest at 5 Minutes for Mom. This photo captures my daughters joy as she was introduced to swimming in the Chesapeake Bay. What summer fun this wasClick here for more pictures of summer fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Hear It For The Boys</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lets-hear-it-for-the-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lets-hear-it-for-the-boys/</guid>
      <description>A Father Son Camping Weekend&amp;hellip;

With 2 Dads and 2 Boys

Full of firsts&amp;hellip;

First fish caught

First canoe ride

Not the first smore, but good none the less.
Memories to last a lifetime&amp;hellip;
For more pictures (probably with a few less words),
check out 5 Minutes for Mom or,
to see what the girls did while the boys were camping, click here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Scream, You Scream, We all Scream For...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-scream-you-scream-we-all-scream-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-scream-you-scream-we-all-scream-for/</guid>
      <description>Baby&amp;rsquo;s First Ice Cream!!
 
  
 
 Visit 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Wednesdays</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hide and Seek</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hide-and-seek/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hide-and-seek/</guid>
      <description>We have a tradition at our house that we do every day when Daddy comes home. I don&amp;rsquo;t know exactly when or how it started, but as soon as Maggie (our dog) barks to let us know he&amp;rsquo;s home, my older two children dash and hide. Daddy then has to find them. I&amp;rsquo;m sure the words, &amp;quot;Daddy&amp;rsquo;s home&amp;hellip;HIDE!&amp;quot; were just the words he longed to hear after a hard day of work, but he always plays along and looks &amp;quot;high and low&amp;quot; till he finds them and is greeting with smiles and giggles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess For A Day</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/princess-for-a-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 20:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/princess-for-a-day/</guid>
      <description>This week I celebrated my birthday. As I mentioned yesterday, I love birthdays. Even though I am a &amp;quot;grown up&amp;quot; now and I am not supposed to care about my birthday, I do. A lot. I don&amp;rsquo;t just look forward to it. I count down the weeks and days until it arrives. When I was a kid I used to have my parents wake me up to say Happy Birthday at the exact minute I was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Summer Swim</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-summer-swim/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 19:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-summer-swim/</guid>
      <description>For More Wordless Wednesdays, click here
or here for WW with a Twist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ll Do to my Children for Free Chick-Fil-A</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-ill-do-to-my-children-for-free-chick-fil-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-ill-do-to-my-children-for-free-chick-fil-a/</guid>
      <description>I LOVE Chick-Fil-A. I could go on and on about how family friendly they are, how good their food is, how I think Truitt Cathy is such a great example of a godly businessman&amp;hellip; but I will save my love affair with Chick-Fil-A, the inventors of the chicken sandwich, for another post, or two&amp;hellip;
Friday was Cow Appreciation Day. I know this because I subscribe to the Chick-Fil-A e-mail updates and I am in on all things up and coming at Chick-Fil-A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mommy&#39;s Boy</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mommys-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mommys-boy/</guid>
      <description>I treasure these days when I am the girl in his life.

For more Wordless Wednesdays, click here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Fourth!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/happy-fourth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/happy-fourth/</guid>
      <description>Over the years the fourth of July has become one of my favorite family fun holidays. We took the kids and both sets of grandparents to a local parade. The streets lined with children and American flags reminded me of something out of a movie. It felt like home town America. My favorite part is always when the Veteran&amp;rsquo;s march past. As I stand and clap and cheer, I can&amp;rsquo;t hold in the tears of gratitude for these men and woman who deserve honor and recognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Night on the Town</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-night-on-the-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-night-on-the-town/</guid>
      <description>Here are my boys enjoying a beautiful evening out downtown.

For more Wordless Wednesdays, click here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day at the Beach</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-day-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-day-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist sharing these pics from our recent trip to the beach.



For more Wordless Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s, visit 5 Minutes for Mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Cast Grew (temporarily)</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-cast-grew-temporarily/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-cast-grew-temporarily/</guid>
      <description>Isn&amp;rsquo;t this a great picture?

It&amp;rsquo;s just a down to earth action shot of us all eating dinner. It&amp;rsquo;s me and my one, two, three, four?, five?&amp;hellip;. wait a minute, that&amp;rsquo;s too many. Your right, I only have three kids but we gained two new members to our circus cast this weekend as we watched the children of our very good friends while they went away for their anniversary. I got to experience life with 5 under 4 for a day and overnight!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come Play With Us</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/come-play-with-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/come-play-with-us/</guid>
      <description>I was cooking dinner last week, when the kids called out from the toy box,
&amp;ldquo;Mom, don&amp;rsquo;t you want to get us out and play with us?&amp;rdquo;
For More Wordless Wednesdays, check out 5 Minutes for Mom.
To learn more about me, check out [my 100th post!] (http://lifeatthecircus.com/2008/06/17/my-100th-post/)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Hot Dad</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-hot-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-hot-dad/</guid>
      <description>In honor of Father&amp;rsquo;s Day this week, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d use one of my favorite Daddy pics of my hubby as my Wordless Wednesday.

Check out 5 Minutes for Mom for more Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ahoy there Matey!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ahoy-there-matey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ahoy-there-matey/</guid>
      <description>Check out [5 Minutes for Mom] (http://5MinutesForMom.com)for more Wordless Wednesdays!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Circus Talent</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-circus-talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-circus-talent/</guid>
      <description>This weekend my girls demonstrated a newly acquired skill for our circus act&amp;hellip;

Meet my Sword Swallowers

For more Wordless Wednesdays, visit 5 Minutes for Mom.
Click here to check out more of my Life Under the Big Top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wee!!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wee/</guid>
      <description>Finally, our baby can get in on the fun at the playground.

For more Wordless Wednesdays, check out 5 Minutes for Mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing One VERY Important Item</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/missing-one-very-important-item/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/missing-one-very-important-item/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend my husband picked my daughter up and noticed she was incredibly wet. He commented that someone must have put her diaper on wrong (Since I was the grownup home at last diaper change, the blame obviously fell to me). I muttered something about those stupid diapers not absorbing properly.

Check out her look of disappointment. (MOM, you let me down)!

My husband called me in to check out what went wrong with the diaper&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sneaking a Little Shut Eye</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sneaking-a-little-shut-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sneaking-a-little-shut-eye/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for visiting! Since you&amp;rsquo;re here, stay awhile&amp;hellip; Might I suggest this post or this one?To view other peoples, check out 5 Minutes for Mom or visit Wordless Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Point of View</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/another-point-of-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/another-point-of-view/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s Looking at You!
[] (https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/04/heres-looking-at-you-2.jpg)
To view previous Wordless Wednesdays, click here .
Or go to 5 Minutes for Mom to see what other people have posted!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Picture of Happiness</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-picture-of-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-picture-of-happiness/</guid>
      <description>Mothering takes a lot of hard work and a lot of late nights. While I only have four years of experience to look back on, I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure it is moments like these that I will cherish when I&amp;rsquo;m old and gray.

5 Minutes for Mom is hosting a Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day Photo Contest asking bloggers to post a picture that defines motherhood; I knew right away that I had to recycle this previous Wordless Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s One Patient Dog!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thats-one-patient-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thats-one-patient-dog/</guid>
      <description>This Wordless Wednesday highlights our very patient dog.

Note the ear pulling and stroller bashing.

&amp;ldquo;What Mom? I AM being gentle!&amp;rdquo;

For more of my Wordless Wednesdays, click here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordless Wednesday</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wordless-wednesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 08:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wordless-wednesday/</guid>
      <description>[] (http://bp2.blogger.com/_CPk-Aq1-YMw/R_N_COitYQI/AAAAAAAAARE/Z-V-67NcFdQ/s1600-h/025+%282%29+%282%29.JPG)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
