<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking Back on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/looking-back/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Looking Back on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 07:14:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/looking-back/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Soccer Momma</title>
      <link>/posts/soccer-momma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 07:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/soccer-momma/</guid>
      <description>Our youngest child had his first soccer practice this week. 
As I struggled to put him into his shin guards and knee socks and cleats, all while watching him grin from ear to ear, my mind drifted back to going through this same right of passage with his older siblings….
Fall 2009


Fall 2010


Spring 2011


Gosh…. look at all those chubby cheeks and teeny tiny legs chasing after those soccer balls….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life is Good</title>
      <link>/posts/life-is-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/life-is-good/</guid>
      <description>Years ago Aunt Karen gave our oldest child a Life is Good soccer shirt. Because the color and theme were gender neutral, I ended up passing it down to my daughter a few years later. It actually became that perfect shirt for younger siblings to wear to soccer games so she could feel like she was a part of the team too. By the time my third child wore it, it was worn with shin guards and sometimes even cleats TO WATCH the older 2 practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Oldie But Goodie</title>
      <link>/posts/an-oldie-but-goodie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/an-oldie-but-goodie/</guid>
      <description>When I uploaded my last video to you tube, I got side tracked with a little trip down memory lane as I then watched other videos the circus fam has posted to you tube in the past.
And I came across this gem.
A few things I noticed while re watching the video.
1. My oldest son used to have that cute 4 year old voice you swear you’ll never forget but inevitably do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
