<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Motherhood on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/motherhood/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Motherhood on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 12:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/motherhood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>No Words</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-words/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, the kids spent a long weekend at my parents while Scott and I enjoyed St Louis. While they were there, my parents took the kids to a friends farm. The kids had a blast. Seriously, a day doesn’t go by that they don’t mention the horses or the chickens or the barn cats. They even got to ride on the horses. Right up there with all those memory making experiences, was another new life experience for my 4 year old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I can fly!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-can-fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 08:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-can-fly/</guid>
      <description>“Hey Mom,” he said to me this morning. “I figured out how I can fly like superman, look.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Baby Shower Gift for All of Us</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-baby-shower-gift-for-all-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 05:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-baby-shower-gift-for-all-of-us/</guid>
      <description>I’m going to a baby shower today for my one of my best friends. I met her when we both taught together at a small Christian school, 12 years ago, though truthfully it feels like eons ago. She’s the kind of person that once your friends with her, you feel like you’ve always been friends. She’s also the kind of person that makes everyone feel like her best friend. I was thinking this morning what a blessing she was to me during my early months and years of mothering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When You Give a Mom a Minute...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-you-give-a-mom-a-minute/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-you-give-a-mom-a-minute/</guid>
      <description>My own paraphrase of a very busy 30 minute period of time here at the circus on our first day back at school at home, based on the &amp;ldquo;If you give a&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo; book series. There is no embellishment here. This is how it really went down at the circus house this morning.
If you give a mom a minute, she&amp;rsquo;ll sneak a peak at facebook.
And when she sneaks a peak at facebook, she&amp;rsquo;ll see one of her friends posted a crock pot recipe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Need a Little Art</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-need-a-little-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-need-a-little-art/</guid>
      <description>We are on break here at the circus. And I couldn’t be more excited about it. I have been looking forward to this week for ages. The week before Christmas. All I want to do is enjoy the kiddos and catch up on some house work. And bake. And do some shopping. And maybe see some friends. (ha, ha… can you tell I am an introvert? read over that list, when I proof read this and re read it, it made me laugh)…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Sport for the Circus Fam</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-sport-for-the-circus-fam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-sport-for-the-circus-fam/</guid>
      <description>As a mom, there are several roles I play in the lives of my children. One of my favorite roles is that of cheer leader. I truly enjoy watching them compete/perform in whatever activity they are involved in and cheering them on as they do so. Yes, that’s right. I am that Mom you hear above the crowd cheering and squealing. This fall my son began a new sport. After years of wanting to try martial arts, he started Brazilian Jiu Jitsu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Startling Realization</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-startling-realization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-startling-realization/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago Scott and I attended the wedding of a friend of ours from high school. As we sat there watching, I had this rather startling realization. Weddings are different for me now than they used to be. I can remember going to wedding for friends when we were in college. As I rejoiced with our friends over the start of their life together, I also found myself taking note of things I’d like to do in my own wedding “someday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deja Vu</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/deja-vu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/deja-vu/</guid>
      <description>My kids have gotten the Minecraft bug. Started first with my oldest son. He shared the obsession with my 6 year old daughter… and then even my child who doesn’t really like to play games, joined in the fight against zombies. Yesterday they finally figured out how to do multi player, which means they can all play at the same time on various different wireless devices in the same world. Giggles could be heard as they found each other walking around in their worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Moment in Time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-moment-in-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-moment-in-time/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday afternoon the girls got their baby dolls and strollers and headed to the court to walk their babies. I don’t know what it was about that particular moment in time, but it struck a chord in this Momma’s heart and made me all sappy. 
As I watched them pushing their dolls and pretending they were walking to China… with a stop in Tennessee for some Chick-Fil-A, I found myself longing to take in the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting to the Heart of the Ring Pop</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/getting-to-the-heart-of-the-ring-pop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/getting-to-the-heart-of-the-ring-pop/</guid>
      <description>The kids were outside playing and I took a few minutes to prep lunch and wash a few dishes. As I walked by the back door, I saw my youngest sitting in a box on the deck.

How cute I thought and went to grab the camera.
My little man spotted me.
I went back to my chores and then noticed he had moved.
This time he was on the other side of the door and had set up a barricade with another box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes I forget</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sometimes-i-forget/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 08:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sometimes-i-forget/</guid>
      <description>Since birth she’s always been trying to keep up with the older two. And most of the time, because she can hold her own with them, I think of her and treat her like she’s older than she really is. One night last week as we went in to peek on her before going to bed we saw her sleeping in her bed with her stuffed animals and dolls lying all around her… it was a little nest of sorts with her in the middle of her beloved toys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Clean Once Again Proves Himself to be a Worthy tool in the Arsenal of Motherhood</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mr.-clean-once-again-proves-himself-to-be-a-worthy-tool-in-the-arsenalof-motherhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mr.-clean-once-again-proves-himself-to-be-a-worthy-tool-in-the-arsenalof-motherhood/</guid>
      <description>I don’t really know what it is that possesses a child to just randomly on a whim pick up that crayon and suddenly decide to make the world (or in this case the bathroom) his canvas. We have crayons out every single day in our house. I do my best when I see a stray one on the floor to nab it lest it suddenly look inviting to my toddler. But, truly they are laying on the school table, in reach, every single day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tee Shirt Love</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tee-shirt-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tee-shirt-love/</guid>
      <description>Scott has been a huge help and support to me this week… taking time off of work so I can rest up (apparently surgery takes more out of you, then you anticipate)… driving the kids to their activities, helping with school, and meals and cleaning up… So, today, I thought I’d show my appreciation and wear my “My Husband Rocks” tee shirt. My 7 year old looked at my shirt, read it aloud and said, “So, why did you wear that today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Why</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/remembering-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/remembering-why/</guid>
      <description>So it was one of _ those _ library trips where I was really regretting going. We were pushing close to past bed time and Momma was tired. But, I knew there were some books on the hold shelf waiting for me and I had two bags of books in the van to return, so I figured we’d run in “real quick.” But, of course, it wasn’t real quick. I had to help my Kindergartner find a book on cats for her science book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And I am Sure Momma’s Everywhere Can Relate…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-i-am-sure-mommas-everywhere-can-relate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-i-am-sure-mommas-everywhere-can-relate/</guid>
      <description>This afternoon I was finishing up in the shower, when my youngest walked into the bathroom. I told him, “Hold on bud, Momma’ just needs a minute. Can you give me some privacy?”
His response?
No Mommy. I can’t. I can’t find your pivacy. Neither can I…. going on 9 years now since I lost it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My little circus clown</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-little-circus-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-little-circus-clown/</guid>
      <description>The youngest circus member is 2 and a half now. (HOW CAN THAT BE?) And I have to tell you he makes me laugh. EVERY.SINGLE.DAY with the cute little things he says, the WAY he says them and those precious little facial expressions. He totally has my heart. 
He still LOVES choo-choos. Plays with them every day. He has also recently started enjoying Sesame Street…particularly Elmo (who he affectionately calls Emo) (like Nemo only no N) He loves to run around the circle on our main level… many, many times a day he will run laps around that circle then come to me and say “faster and faster?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gift of Words</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-gift-of-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-gift-of-words/</guid>
      <description>I am a words person. Always have been. I love cards, and notes, texts and e-mails. And I save them. Yup… every note Scott ever passed me in high school, every birthday card, Valentine card, anniversary card… I have them all in a box.
So, it should come as no surprise, that when my kids start writing, I started hoarding those precious words as well. I know can’t save them all, but I do try to save the “significant ones”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even Super Man Sleeps</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/even-super-man-sleeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/even-super-man-sleeps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Look at My Girls Brains</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-look-at-my-girls-brains/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-look-at-my-girls-brains/</guid>
      <description>I was scrolling around on pinterest one night and a graphic caught my eye that made me stop in my tracks. It showed 2 sides of the brains and listed descriptions for left/brain right brain people. 
I think often people are largely a little bit of both. However, when I looked at this graphic, it was like a portrait of my daughters.
I swear my 6 year old could be the poster child for the left brained person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Muffins and Memories for Breakfast</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/making-muffins-and-memories-for-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/making-muffins-and-memories-for-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>Not sure which I like best about this snapshot, the smiles on the girls faces, my daughters hand in the peanut butter jar or my son sneaking yet another lick out of the bowl….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 year old in the House</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/2-year-old-in-the-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/2-year-old-in-the-house/</guid>
      <description>Number one sign you have a 2 year old boy in the house.
Nothing is safe. He will drag chairs to the counter to score out of reach cookies, he’ll fill cups with ice only to dump them on the floor, he’ll drink soda, coffee, whatever he finds left sitting out with reckless abandon. And he’ll sunscreen my dining room furniture. 
I had even seen the sunscreen lying out earlier and moved it to the center of the dining room table, “just incase”….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bittersweet Thoughts of Gratitude</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bittersweet-thoughts-of-gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bittersweet-thoughts-of-gratitude/</guid>
      <description>I remember vividly the first night we spent in our house. We were first time home owners.
And we were giddy. As we lay on the floor in our bedroom looking up at the ceiling I remember Scott commenting on the ceiling fan. “Look at that ceiling fan! We own it!” I on the other hand couldn’t get my eyes of the red blinking light from the smoke detector…. wondering how would I fall asleep with it constantly blinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Cold Turkey</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/going-cold-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/going-cold-turkey/</guid>
      <description>For the past four and half years, this has been her “go to” position for comfort. 
As a baby it was great… she totally self soothed… no pacifiers to chase down or beloved blankey to snuggle. Just pop her index and middle fingers in her mouth backwards and start rubbing her ear (or twirling her hair) and she could instantly calm herself to sleep. We knew of course this would have it’s trade off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freezing This Moment in Time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/freezing-this-moment-in-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/freezing-this-moment-in-time/</guid>
      <description>This past week our oldest son turned 8. As quickly as that time seems to have flown, it is frightening to me to realize in just as little time, he’ll be waving goodbye as he backs a car out of the driveway. AACK! In the midst of this busy stage of life, I want to take time to reflect on who he is now at this stage, so I can cherish and savor it for years to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 05:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/memory/</guid>
      <description>She pretty much whips me at this every Monday and Wednesday… and I wouldn’t trade the sweet memories we’re making for anything in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DATE DAY</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/date-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/date-day/</guid>
      <description>While we didn’t plan it like this at first, Sunday ended up being date day for each of our 4 kids. Each child ended up with some one on one time with either mom, dad, or Aunt Karen. Good times had by all!
One of the duties of our church deacons is to unlock the church on Sunday mornings. When Scott became a deacon 3 years ago, he started taking one child with him on his deacon duty mornings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-R-O-U-B-L-E</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t-r-o-u-b-l-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 03:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t-r-o-u-b-l-e/</guid>
      <description>This afternoon my smiley, mild mannered, easy going baby suddenly channeled his inner Dennis the Menace and went all toddler boy on me for 30 minutes. First I looked over and found him standing on his tool bench (oops look who forgot to put away the advent calendar with her Christmas decorations)

I got him down and shortly after realized things had been mighty quiet for awhile and went searching for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life With 2</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-with-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-with-2/</guid>
      <description>Now that my oldest 2 are at their tutorial two days a week, I find myself with just 2 children at home on those mornings. It is a truly odd feeling and a dynamic I am not yet used to. Though I am sure it is nothing compared to the strangeness I’ll feel next year when I am left with only my lil man two days a week. I am hoping to use this time to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Date with my Son</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-date-with-my-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-date-with-my-son/</guid>
      <description>6 Flags Amusement park offered a free ticket to any K-6 grade student that registered for their Read to Succeed program and completed 6 hrs of non school required reading. As a bonus, the teacher who enrolled the student also got a free ticket. So, that meant this home schooling momma got a ticket for herself and her son to 6 Flags.
I kept track of his reading in the spring and when he completed 6 hrs of recreational reading, unannounced to him, I registered him for the free ticket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice Needed</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/advice-needed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/advice-needed/</guid>
      <description>My daughter is a fierce competitor. Everything, and I mean everything can be turned to a competition with her. Last weekend when we were driving back to the camp site from training camp, Scott and I drove my parents van and let my parents follow us with the kids in our van. We pulled in to Dairy Queen as a fun surprise and she says to my dad, “Now’s your chance to beat them… keep driving Papa!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He Spoils Us</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/he-spoils-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/he-spoils-us/</guid>
      <description>Time and time again our fourth child has blown us away with his easy going, flexible, happy-go-lucky approach to life. It has made the transition to a family of 6, for this family on-the-go, SO MUCH easier—a fact I am truly, truly grateful for.
This weekend, he really went above and beyond our expectations though.
Not only did he fall asleep in the tent both nights, while the rest of us were out at the camp fire, but he even napped in the tent Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desiring to be a Woman of Faith</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/desiring-to-be-a-woman-of-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/desiring-to-be-a-woman-of-faith/</guid>
      <description>Years ago my Mom and I attended a Women of Faith Conference…I believe our first was when I was in college. We drove to Cleveland, OH to attend the conference. We left refreshed and inspired and vowing to make it a tradition to attend some sort of spiritual conference together as often as we could. Since then, we’ve attend Women of Faith, Beth Moore, and a few women’s retreats together. I appreciate the opportunity to worship, and grow alongside my mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyday Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everyday-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everyday-fun/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a good week at the circus. Nothing incredibly note worthy, but fun times all around… thought I’d share a few pictures from our week. I love summer… seriously love it. Love the long daylight hours… love the freedom… even love the hot summer sun. 





How about you? What are some of your highlights from the week?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few Little Gems</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-few-little-gems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-few-little-gems/</guid>
      <description>While looking through pictures recently, I stumbled across a few which truly captured life at the circus in its essence.
Exhibit A: taken in December of 2010

Here they are working on the pine wood derby car for Cub Scouts. Notice how everyone, even the baby, is in on the action? Noticed the leotard? My girls wear leotards every.single.day…. even though gymnastics is only twice a week, I can guarantee you those leotards are on more often than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The way They Love Him</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-way-they-love-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-way-they-love-him/</guid>
      <description>As Scott and I worked to put together the scrapbook and video collage for our son’s 1st birthday, we looked at lots and lots of pictures and video clips. As we did, one reoccurring theme, was brought to mind.
This boy is adored by his siblings.
He really has been from day 1. And by day 1, I mean, the day Scott and I told them about the baby in my belly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning Back Time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/turning-back-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/turning-back-time/</guid>
      <description>Ya know that feeling you get when you look at your kids and you just wanna freeze time? You don’t want them to grow up, not one bit, so you just try your best to hold on to the moments while you can.
Well, we figured out a way to freeze time here at the circus…just a little…

Our littlest crew member turned one earlier this month. Not sure how that year flew by so fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Insignificant?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/feeling-insignificant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/feeling-insignificant/</guid>
      <description>Last week after telling my kids the Bible story of baby Moses, I decided to offer a little application for them. I pointed out how neat it was that God took care of Moses as a baby by allowing the princess to find him. I even told how amazing it was that his own mother was allowed to take care of him before he went to live at the palace. After discussing how Moses grew up in the Egyptian palace, I pointed out how God used that later in his life when Moses led the Israelites out of captivity in Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When You Care Enough to Send the Very Best</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-you-care-enough-to-send-the-very-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 06:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-you-care-enough-to-send-the-very-best/</guid>
      <description>Before having kids, I used to go to my local Hallmark store and browse the selection of cards. It seemed there was always SOMEONE who could benefit from a little Hallmark cheer. I love cards. LOVE them… and prior to having kids I was pretty good about buying and sending them.
Somehow though bringing 2, then 3, now 4 active kids into a card store lost its appeal… something about them reaching out of their strollers and pulling card after card onto the floor while I was trying to find that perfect card made it loose its charm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Gifts This Mothers Day</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-gifts-this-mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-gifts-this-mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>I am sure Scott and the kids have something planned for me on Sunday… or at the very least, I am sure by Sunday morning they will have something planned for me on Mother’s Day. They never fail to make me feel cherished.
But the truth is, as I ponder this Mother’s Day, I can’t help but give thanks for the many gifts they’ve already given me… those precious moments each and every day, which I long to bottle up and savor forever…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Call it Crazy…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</guid>
      <description>This spring I have 3 kids in sports. On 3 different teams. This in addition to the girls both taking gymnastics twice a week and Cub Scouts.
We are busy, busy, busy with games and practices most every night… some nights we’re even double booked.
Many people look at my schedule and call me crazy. Why do you do this to yourself?
The answer is, honestly, two fold. 1. We love it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break at the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-break-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-break-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>The past week has been spring break at the circus and while it is technically true, we did break from our studies, other than that, it was a jam packed, super busy week.
It is now Monday… school resumes tomorrow, and today I am trying to catch up on laundry and dishes and cleaning… right now, we’re back from gymnastics and the kids are down for quiet time. I am thankful for an iced coffee and the fact that it is warm enough for a skirt and flip flops…oh how I love warm sunny days!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting to the Heart of Parenting</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/getting-to-the-heart-of-parenting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/getting-to-the-heart-of-parenting/</guid>
      <description>Before having kids I watched/read excerpts from Shepherding a Child’s Heart by Ted Tripp. The premise that you need to do more than just manage behavior, but get to the heart of what is causing our child’s behavior, made a lot of sense to both Scott and I. And through the years I think we have tried to apply this approach to our parenting. But, there is something very different about reading a book before having kids and reading one with both feet in the trenches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Mothering</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thoughts-on-mothering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thoughts-on-mothering/</guid>
      <description>Lately I have found myself biting back tears and praying for wisdom as I work with my daughter on obedience and respect. These battles leave me tired and stretched and yearning for some chocolate chip cookie dough and a bottle of coca cola classic.
One battle area for us has been over her having to wear her eye patch. Seems the novelty has faded and she really doesn’t like wearing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sparkle of a True Princess</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-sparkle-of-a-true-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-sparkle-of-a-true-princess/</guid>
      <description>“Momma, don’t we look beautiful?”
As I praised them for their lovely fashion choices and snapped picture upon picture of their dress up fun, it dawned on me that this was an opportunity to reinforce what true beauty is. Ya know, I said. To be truly beautiful, you have to be kind and loving to others. In fact, you can be wearing the prettiest dress ever, but if you act mean and unkind to others, you aren’t beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Priceless</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/priceless/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/priceless/</guid>
      <description>Container of dish soap: $2.00

Chip in my favorite coffee mug: $10.00

Keeping 2 sisters happy and entertained for an hour: Priceless</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Months Old Today</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/9-months-old-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/9-months-old-today/</guid>
      <description>Look at those chubby hands stuffing his face

I seriously couldn’t stop clicking the camera

Oh, little man, you have captured your Momma’s heart</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Such a Time As This?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/for-such-a-time-as-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/for-such-a-time-as-this/</guid>
      <description>There are all kinds of people in the world. Some morning people, some night owls. I truly think your propensity towards one or the other is an inborn part of your personality. True, you can work on becoming more of a morning person (and society pretty much dictates this to some degree), ones natural inclination, I think, is innate.
For a glimpse of this, one must simply observe my two daughters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Many Miles Can We Get Out of This? or Milking This One for ALL its Worth</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-many-miles-can-we-get-out-of-this-or-milking-this-one-for-all-itsworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-many-miles-can-we-get-out-of-this-or-milking-this-one-for-all-itsworth/</guid>
      <description>Some of you may remember my post last December (as in 2009) in which I shared one of Scott’s moments of sheer brilliance at the dinner table. Well, I feel the need to tell you that 13 months later and my kids are STILL eating their vegetables to spite their Daddy. I am sure this says something of their character… for which we must spend some time rectifying, but meanwhile my mean spirited little children are eagerly gobbling up their vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Hodgepodge of Circus Updates</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-hodgepodge-of-circus-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-hodgepodge-of-circus-updates/</guid>
      <description>What day is it? We’ve been a bit out of sorts here at the circus… snow days and a power outage resulting in a fun sleepover at Nana and Pop’s… …now it is Friday, but sure feels like Monday…. we’re home and trying to play catch up on schoolwork, house work and laundry… good news is, when we are done… we’ll still have the weekend to enjoy! And next week is Super Bowl week… and in case you missed it… Pittsburgh’s Going to the Superbowl!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Babies Don’t Keep</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/babies-dont-keep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/babies-dont-keep/</guid>
      <description>My lil guy isn’t a newborn anymore. I’ve known it for awhile.. he’s eating solids, vocalizing, and working on crawling. But, recently, I also realized his days of simply sleeping in my arms are fleeting. He’s working himself into a rhythm… sleeping through the night… taking 2 solid naps a day…The days of just holding my tiny, sleeping newborn in my arms are over. So on those random Sunday afternoons when he falls asleep in my arms, I am going to stay put and savor the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banner Day at the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/banner-day-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/banner-day-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>Dishes piled in the sink, pjs on till 2:00 in the afternoon, laundry waiting to be folded, counter cluttered…
But today, it doesn’t bother me. (ok, it doesn’t bother me too much anyway)…
because…
Today, I finally took the time to snuggle on the couch with my almost 5 year old and work with her on reading… and today that precious light bulb went off as she first went up and down the blend ladders and then graduated to three letter words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Savoring the Moment</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/savoring-the-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2010 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/savoring-the-moment/</guid>
      <description>The week has been full of shopping, cleaning, baking, laundry, card writing, visits with friends, and last minute preparations for the festivities at the end of the week. But, in the midst of all the hustle and bustle, I’ve had a few precious moments which I want to quickly record lest I forget them in days gone by.
Monday evening I took my 4 year old daughter shopping for her sister’s Christmas present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am Smitten</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-am-smitten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-am-smitten/</guid>
      <description>You’d think doing this 3 times over already, I would have been prepared.

And yet, once again, my breath has been taken away. I have fallen, and hard.
 
With your irresistible smile, your easy going personality, and your snuggly hugs, I am smitten. 
How can it be that 6 months have already passed since you joined our family? In some ways it seems like you were just born yesterday and in others it seems like you’ve always been a part of our family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/today/</guid>
      <description>Today I had planned to write a sweet and nostalgic motherhood type post about my littlest cast member. But, when quiet time rolled around my head was aching, my mind racing, and the right words and sentiments weren’t coming to me. Because today…
*Today I tried to do 2 days worth of school in one morning since we’ll be out of town on Monday
*Today I made banana chocolate chip pancakes for breakfast</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mothers Day in October</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mothers-day-in-october/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mothers-day-in-october/</guid>
      <description>I heard the alarm go off and was grateful when Scott woke to take the first shower. Shortly after I heard the enthusiastic chatter of my youngest daughter in the bathroom and I happily rolled over for a little more shut eye.
Next thing I know I hear Scott turn off the tv and gather the big 3 to “have a chat”. I then hear, “ Guys, what does Daddy do for her job?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Don’t Wanna Miss a Thing</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-dont-wanna-miss-a-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-dont-wanna-miss-a-thing/</guid>
      <description>So many things I want to remember from this stage of life…the sweet way she mispronounces her baby brother’s name…. and the way his face lights up with recognition when I walk in a room…the raspy way she belts out songs in the back seat, and the sweet way he kisses his sisters goodbye before heading into school… I know I think I’ll never forget and yet those who’ve gone before me say I will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highlights from the Week</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/highlights-from-the-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/highlights-from-the-week/</guid>
      <description>A few pics to sum up the week and highlight a few of my favorite moments.

My favorite part of our home schooling day is the beginning. We start with the pledge and a very loud and off key rendition of The Star Spangled Banner. Warms my patriotic soul!
Q: What do home schoolers wear to school?

A: whatever they want.. ie leotards and camos
We made a discovery this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’ve Got Nothing</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ive-got-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ive-got-nothing/</guid>
      <description>Writers block
Momnesia
Mushy brain
Call it what you will, but I am sorry this circus mom has nothing to give ya. I’ve sat down and started posts 3 separate times this week only to stop half way through. I wanted to fill you in on our hamster wheel paced life the past few weeks but when I write it all out it just seems boring. Really, do you want to hear about the circus family’s daily routine?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lately…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lately/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lately/</guid>
      <description>You may or may not have noticed that lately, I haven’t been blogging much. I can’t put my finger on why exactly.
 
It’s not his fault… he is super easy going. And it isn’t due to lack of fodder… the circus crew provides me with a never ending supply of bloggable material. But, my days have been “more full” lately. Our schedule includes home school, tutorial, gymnastics, soccer, (and cub scouts starting soon).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Mouth of Babes</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/out-of-the-mouth-of-babes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/out-of-the-mouth-of-babes/</guid>
      <description>It’s been one of those days… please tell me you know the ones…took the circus crew to the pediatrician’s for my 3 yr old’s check up. One would have thought by the amount of shrieking that took place in the hall that we were attempting to tie her down and give her 30 shots, when really we just wanted her to take her sandals off and stand on the scale. From that humbling spectacle we were off to the grocery store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Close Talker</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-close-talker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-close-talker/</guid>
      <description>Dear Son,
When you grow up and notice that every time you talk people kinda take a step back from you… its not your fault.
You will have come by these socially awkward close talking tendencies quite naturally.
Blame your older sisters for your lack of personal space. Because they can’t seem to talk to you without their face literally centimeters from yours. 
Waking or sleeping, car seat, or bassinet or bouncy seat or swing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tag! Your it!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tag-your-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tag-your-it/</guid>
      <description>Divide and Conquer
That would be the name of the game lately at the circus.
I’ll take the youngest two to the grocery store while Scott takes the older ones with him to build the new to us play set. Or Scott takes the big 3 to the year end baseball ceremony while I stay home with the babe.
At this stage of the game, tag teaming has seemed crucial for surviving and for attempting to keep the household running somewhat smoothly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Times Two</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-times-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-times-two/</guid>
      <description>Because I am used to the chaotic and crazy lifestyle I live, I sometimes forget how it can look to the outsider. It feels normal to me to walk down the street with a gaggle of kids surrounding me, fighting or singing or playing (or all of the above). And when I combine my circus life with that of my close friend (whose blog could also easily be called Life At The Circus as she has 4 boys ages 5, 4, 3 and 3 months) well the chaos only multiplies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One Where I’m Tempted to Move to Florida</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-one-where-im-tempted-to-move-to-florida/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-one-where-im-tempted-to-move-to-florida/</guid>
      <description>I hear his cries and stumble out of bed. Cradling my son in my arms I make my way down the hall and to the couch where I sit to nurse him. My eyes are burning, begging me to let them close again. Instead I grab my phone and start scrolling through face book trying to keep myself awake while my little guy eagerly chugs down on his 4 am meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Forgot…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-forgot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 05:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-forgot/</guid>
      <description>Funny how time dulls the memory. It’s been 3 yrs since I’ve had a newborn around the house and it seems I forgot a few things, like….
 How many diapers a newborn goes through…this little man seems to poop, all-the-time, already went through the two small packs of newborn diapers we had in less than a week. Thankfully I had bought a huge box of Swaddlers size 1-2 which he can technically fit in and which totally saved the day night when we ran out of the newborn sized diapers in the middle of the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s a Boy!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a-boy/</guid>
      <description>This week we welcomed a new member to our family. 
Our sweet baby boy was born this week…
weighing in at 8 lbs 14 oz and measuring 20” long. 
It was love at first sight for all of us. We really can’t get enough of him, so it seems.  I can’t wait to fill you in on the labor story and share the pictures from his fist visit with his big brother and sisters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimme a Break</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gimme-a-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gimme-a-break/</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to make oral reading more fun, I gave my son the option of picking any location in our house to do his reading time.  He chose my closet.
Would not have been my first choice, but no worries, to the closet we went… I brought a pillow for me to sit on as the floor isn’t so comfy for this 9 mth pregnant momma. My son looked at me and said, “Hey, how come you aren’t sharing that pillow with me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queen for a Weekend</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/queen-for-a-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 20:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/queen-for-a-weekend/</guid>
      <description>This weekend I was reminded of how a little care and attention can make one feel loved and cherished. They lathered me with love as they enthusiastically rubbed my legs and feet with lotion.

Then my son found a battery powered fan and eagerly cooled me down when our power went out on Saturday afternoon. (seriously, was I living the high life or what?)

On Sunday they woke me up with breakfast in bed and flowers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She got it</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/she-got-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/she-got-it/</guid>
      <description>Earlier, I alluded to the fact that my daughter finally got it after her first game of soccer. As the season has progressed, she has truly gotten it, indeed!
Here she is getting ready to steal the ball from the pack.
 Hmmm… notice a little blocking going on here?

And she goes in for the score!
 She did it! I love the look on her face after scoring another goal!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reaching His Goal</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/reaching-his-goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/reaching-his-goal/</guid>
      <description>Tonight I was reminded of the value of hard work. For the past two years I’ve had the joy of teaching my son’s beginning catechism class at our church on Sun evenings. The kids are working through the The Shorter Catechism Questions, and by completion of level 3 the kids will have memorized all 150 questions and answers. My son was in the beginning class which covers questions 1-32. Last year he came really close to getting them all, but we didn’t quite get them all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Years…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/6-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/6-years/</guid>
      <description>6 years ago, I was also carrying a baby in my belly. (In fact, this picture was taken exactly 6 yrs ago to the date). The nursery was prepped, the hospital bag had long been packed. I was basically sitting around waiting to have a baby. I do not recommend going with that strategy… what a long week of waiting that was. Now I try to plan things right up to and past the due date, so I am not in that hurry up and wait mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Praying for my Kids</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/praying-for-my-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/praying-for-my-kids/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago a woman from my church passed out these prayer cards written by Bob Hostetler to the ladies in our MOPS group. Each card had 31 Biblical Virtues to pray for your children, with verses included. I thought this was a great idea and instantly tucked it away inside my Bible.
Only to forget about it and lose track of it with all the other papers stuffed in there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Letter to My Baby</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-letter-to-my-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-letter-to-my-baby/</guid>
      <description>Dear Sweet Baby of Mine,
Every time I sit down or lay down I can feel you move around inside of me. You are more active than any of your sisters or brother were in the womb. Perhaps you are trying to tell us already that you are eager to jump in and join in the chaos and fun that is our family. The feeling of you turning over or kicking and punching my sides…it’s almost as if you are saying, “Hey Mom!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>His First “Published Work”</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/his-first-published-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 18:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/his-first-published-work/</guid>
      <description>The other day after quiet time my oldest emerged from his room with his first book. I knew nothing of his project until he emerged but was blown away by what he produced. On the cover page his listed himself as the “osr” and “iliusha” (author and illustrator). For his first book, he pretty much spells out the gospel message in word and pictures.
Page One: “God loved us” (I must say the spelling on this one def made me chuckle).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Crew Visits the OB</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-crew-visits-the-ob/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-crew-visits-the-ob/</guid>
      <description>I typically schedule my OB appointments for first thing in the morning so that the kids can stay home with Scott. This time however, his work schedule didn’t cooperate, so I brought the circus crew with me for my check up. I knew at 28 weeks they wouldn’t be doing an exam, so I felt comfortable having them tag along. I did come prepared with coloring books, crayons, snacks, and even lollipops which I saved for the very end if they were “super stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eager to Serve</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/eager-to-serve/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 01:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/eager-to-serve/</guid>
      <description>The other day my son told me he wanted to make all of us breakfast the next morning. The only problem with this very sweet gesture was that it was the end of the month and we were at the “creative” stage of the month/meal plan.
Bread? No
Milk? No
Cereal? No
Not much available for a 5 yr old to fix, so I convinced him to wait till after I went grocery shopping on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Thoughts on Spring</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/random-thoughts-on-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/random-thoughts-on-spring/</guid>
      <description>Guess what the kids and I spotted outside this afternoon?  Crocuses!!! Oh, how I love those little purple blooms… they are the signal to me that spring is around the corner! And as much as I have loved, (and truly, I know I whined that one day, but really, I have loved this record breaking snowy winter), but I am excited for spring.
And I am really excited… I am looking forward to taking walks with the kids in the evenings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Thing I’ve Got Thick Skin!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/good-thing-ive-got-thick-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/good-thing-ive-got-thick-skin/</guid>
      <description>Last night I was holding my girls on my lap when they began to play a little rough. I reminded them that there was a baby in my belly and they needed to be gentle. My 4 yr old then said, “Mom, I don’t think you really have a baby in your belly. I think it is just food.”
I assured her there really is a baby in there and reminded her that she’s seen the baby’s picture and heard the heart beat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look Who’s a Big Girl Now!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/look-whos-a-big-girl-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/look-whos-a-big-girl-now/</guid>
      <description>That’s right after her total regression back to diapers in August (after a completely embarrassing trip to the grocery store which involved my wiping pee up off of the floor&amp;ndash;twice, the shopping cart, not to mention our groceries….I thought I would never leave the house with her in underwear again) but after Christmas we decided to give the ol potty train a try once more. My mom told her at Christmas it could be her New Years resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Something You Know About?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/whats-something-you-know-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/whats-something-you-know-about/</guid>
      <description>My son always has tons of questions about the world around him and the way things work. Most of the time, I am at a loss as to how to answer these questions. For example, the other day he wanted to know about signals and how we could see them. As in, radio signals or cell phone signals. He wondered if they were like infrared light and could only be seen with special glasses or if we can’t see them at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s a…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a/</guid>
      <description>BABY!!!!!

This morning we had our sonogram appointment. While it is our fourth pregnancy, I try as hard as I can to not take anything for granted. I don’t think I realized how much I was “holding my breath” so to speak before the appointment. Words can’t adequately express the feelings of thanksgiving that overwhelmed me when the tech and then the doctor told us that everything looked healthy and normal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Date with my Daughter</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-date-with-my-daughter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-date-with-my-daughter/</guid>
      <description>As many of you with more than one child know, it’s often hard to find one on one time with your children. I’ve found you really have to be intentional, in order for it to happen. I’ve also found that it doesn’t always have to be a big elaborate event. Often it is just taking advantage of the few minutes of snuggle time when one child wakes up first in the morning, or after nap time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinary Miracle</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ordinary-miracle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ordinary-miracle/</guid>
      <description>During this stage of the game, sometimes it’s easy to forget there’s a person growing inside me. Yes, my jeans are fitting more snugly these days and I tend to nod off on the couch each night around 10, but other than that I don’t feel all the different. And so I go through each day making meals, cleaning up messes, and trying to accomplish lessons, errands, and other excursions and quite often forget that all the while there’s a life growing inside of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Boot Camp</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/baby-boot-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2009 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/baby-boot-camp/</guid>
      <description>It appears my oldest daughter is trying to prepare me for life with 4 kids. She has taken on the job of mothering her baby doll “baby Eli” literally 24-7. When we sit down to eat, she makes sure Eli has his bib on and a special seat at the table. We now set our table for 7 (b/c our youngest has to include her baby Eli too). 
When she’s getting ready for bed, baby Eli also gets tucked into his bed, with his own baby and she is always certain to read him his special Bible story as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pregnancy Update</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pregnancy-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pregnancy-update/</guid>
      <description>Many of you have asked for the details on my pregnancy. Some you will just have to infer for yourself as this is a family friendly blog :-) But, as for the rest….I am around 11 weeks pregnant. According to a site I read online that gives me the update each week, this week my baby gets his/her irises and finger nails and he or she weighs in a whopping 7 grams!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon to a Circus Near You</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/coming-soon-to-a-circus-near-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 03:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/coming-soon-to-a-circus-near-you/</guid>
      <description>That’s right folks, we have a new circus member due to arrive here in early June 2010!! And the circus cast couldn’t be more excited!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Peanuts Gang</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-peanuts-gang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-peanuts-gang/</guid>
      <description>Those of you that have been visiting the circus for awhile know that I don’t use my kids names on the blogs. I once entertained the idea of pseudonyms but never came up with any I liked. So I’ve pretty much stuck with “ my son,” “my 3 year old daughter” and “my baby” for the past year or so. So far, I have no real intentions to change that, but I did realize last week, that had this been “Life with The Peanuts Gang” or something more catchy, I’d have perfect pseudonyms to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time After Time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/time-after-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/time-after-time/</guid>
      <description>The concept of time is a funny thing. Who can really grasp it? On one hand it seems like ages ago that I brought my little one home from the hospital, and at the same time it feels just like yesterday. How does one go about teaching the concept of time to little ones? To them a day truly is like a thousand years! I read somewhere that its helpful to give children a specific time (as in you have 10 minutes to play and then we are cleaning up) then set the timer and when the timer goes off, clean up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Enjoys a Little Pampering</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everyone-enjoys-a-little-pampering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everyone-enjoys-a-little-pampering/</guid>
      <description>I realized recently, that while I spend lots of time with my kids, too often it&amp;rsquo;s easy for me to spend the day with them, without really playing with them. So, these past few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing a lot more playing. And I gotta say, I&amp;rsquo;m loving it.
One hit with the circus crew recently has been beauty shop. To make it an equal opportunity for all, I did a little hair spiking for my son.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sick Days</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sick-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sick-days/</guid>
      <description>Well, the local public schools went back in session at the beginning of the week and even though we are homeschooling this year, we’ve already got sick germs at the circus. Seems we’re not holding out for long sleeves and sweaters to welcome in those lovely, little germs.
But, can I tell you a little secret?
Part of me likes sick days.
No, I don’t like to see my kids suffering, and no I am not a big fan of the whining or continual moaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Nye’s Got Nothing on my Little Guy</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bill-nyes-got-nothing-on-my-little-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 03:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bill-nyes-got-nothing-on-my-little-guy/</guid>
      <description>The kids have been into “experimenting” these days. We even have science journals with which to record our results. (Yes, we can thank Sid the Science Kid for that brilliant idea).
It started with freezing stuff.
I overheard my son tell his sister with a hushed voice of excitement, “Sis, you watch…we’ll put this cup of water into the freezer and then later when we come back it will be ice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But, of course!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/but-of-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 11:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/but-of-course/</guid>
      <description>I am a home body. Truth be told, I can go a good four days of staying at home before I go stir crazy and need to get out and about. And as a home body, I love, LOVE days where we go no where and just stay home all day. These days don’t happen all too often, maybe about once a week. Because, my kids LOVE to go out. Even if it is grocery shopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Best</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sunday-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sunday-best/</guid>
      <description>My little man loves to look spiffy for church on Sunday. He’s been asking for “shiny church shoes” for months now. But penny loafers are expensive and I hadn’t been able to find any at the consignment shop. Until this week when I went on a consignment store quest hoping to find some cool looking picture frames for a fun idea I had for my dining room. No luck with the picture frames but we did score a cooler and a pair of “shiny church shoes” in size 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Hard (or hardly working)</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/working-hard-or-hardly-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/working-hard-or-hardly-working/</guid>
      <description>My son is quite the little entrepreneur. The other night after dinner my husband was reading the girls a book and I sat on the couch to read a little myself. I looked over to see what my son was up to and discovered he had put all the dishes in the sink, and was scrubbing the dining room table. He even asked where the sandwich bags where so he could bag up the leftovers and put them in the fridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partners for Life</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/partners-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/partners-for-life/</guid>
      <description>The relationship between siblings is a funny thing. I once read a Times magazine article about siblings that really struck me. It’s funny, 3 years later and I still remember this one line “Our spouses arrive comparatively late in our lives; our parents eventually leave us. Our siblings may be the only people we&amp;rsquo;ll ever know who truly qualify as partners for life.”
Being the mother of three children, I think a lot about the bonds of siblings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick a Fork in Me…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/stick-a-fork-in-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2009 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/stick-a-fork-in-me/</guid>
      <description>I am done!
Whew! What a week at the circus! This was not one of those stay in your pjs all day and relax by the pool kinda weeks. Not at all. Rather it was one of those, get the kids up, fed, dressed, in shoes (no small feat for the circus crew) and to the soccer field by 9 am every.single.morning. Hello? Even during the school year, it was only M-W-F for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life on the Sideline</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-on-the-sideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 18:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-on-the-sideline/</guid>
      <description>Life on the sidelines can be rough. I know, I’ve been there. Sat the bench for 4 years of high school lacrosse. But unlike her mother, my little girl sits on the side because she is too young, not because she isn’t good enough.
[
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/06/IMG_8358.jpg)
My daughter is dying to play like her brother. It is so cute and yet so painful to watch her on the sidelines. When the coach calls the team to line up at the bench during practice, she is right there with the rest of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And You Wondered Why I Call it Life at the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-you-wondered-why-i-call-it-life-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-you-wondered-why-i-call-it-life-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes a mother’s ability to multitask isn’t a good thing… as I attempt to juggle one to many balls, I find that I can accidentally drop one and not even realize it for several hours.
Last week while I was talking on the phone and cleaning up the living room, I noticed the kids sitting on the floor with some stuffed animals and scissors.
I keenly observed that something looked amiss, so I grabbed the scissors from my sons hands, quickly told him that they needed to be used only at the table, and went to the other room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tough Week</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tough-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2009 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tough-week/</guid>
      <description>I knew being a mom wouldn’t be easy. And I’ve survived the middle of the night feedings, the tantrums of the terrible twos, the struggle for independence…but that all feels like child play compared to the task of this week.
This week I was reminded of the fact that sometimes there is very little a mom can do to protect her young from getting hurt. Sending your children off into the world, is like sending your heart out there, exposed for the world to trample on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the Elevator</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/in-the-elevator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2009 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/in-the-elevator/</guid>
      <description>There is something alluring, almost magical about the buttons on an elevator. My kids enthusiastically clamor for the opportunity to press the shiny buttons both outside and inside of the elevator. We have a routine when entering elevators which typically works flawlessly. One child pushes the button on the outside. The second child then pushes the same button. Once inside they each get a turn pushing the button for the floor we want to go on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma Blankets</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/grandma-blankets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 04:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/grandma-blankets/</guid>
      <description>My kids each have a blanket that their grandma made for them before they were born. Being the creative individuals that they are, they call them their “grandma blankets.” I know, ingenious, huh?
The other day I was laying on my daughter’s bed when I had a realization. “Hey”, I said, “this blanket is my grandma blanket.” She laughed and thought I was joking.
“No,” I said, “this blanket right here was made for me by my grandma when I was a little girl, so it is my grandma blanket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Hear Your Thoughts</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lets-hear-your-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lets-hear-your-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>My oldest son is five. He’s gotten to the point where he wants things. And his birthday and Christmas are over. He’s already proven that he has the self control and discipline to save up for things. But he has no income.
I would like to start developing in him the discipline to save and to choose wisely how to spend his money. So, I was wondering, do any of you give your children allowances?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Childhood Pleasures</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/childhood-pleasures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/childhood-pleasures/</guid>
      <description>Mudpies

Slugs

Puddle Jumping

We’ve had plenty of baths at the circus this weekend. But the extra laundry and baths are totally worth it to see my kids truly delighting in the simplest of pleasures and enjoying the world around them. Mud, and slugs, and puddles…giggles, wonder, and smiles…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where did my baby go?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/where-did-my-baby-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2009 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/where-did-my-baby-go/</guid>
      <description>Something happened to my baby girl.
Seems she was just learning to crawl.
How is that she’s running around, skinning her knees and swinging beside the big kids?
Didn’t she know she wasn’t supposed to grow up so fast?
She’s my baby.
What is she doing conversing and counting and going on the potty?
Where did my baby go?
And who is this pig tailed princess that’s serenading us in the morning with her sweet cherub voice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pomp and Circumstance</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pomp-and-circumstance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pomp-and-circumstance/</guid>
      <description>I can’t believe the school year is over all ready. More than that I can’t believe my little guy is going to be a kindergartener next fall. Where did the time go? It truly seems like it wasn’t that long ago when he was taking his first steps. And now he’ll be stepping across the stage…ready to commence a new stage of life.
He is no longer a preschooler.
I’m so proud of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Value of A Penny Saved</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-value-of-a-penny-saved/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-value-of-a-penny-saved/</guid>
      <description>When my little man sets his heart on something, you better watch out. Because he will hold on tight with his 5 year old death grip on life!
 His preschool had an art festival last week. It was the single best fundraising event I have ever attended. Parents paid a $10 admission per child and the kids got to engage in numerous, fun, messy, outside art projects. It was a glorious way to spend a sunny Saturday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Sharing My Heart This Morning</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-sharing-my-heart-this-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-sharing-my-heart-this-morning/</guid>
      <description>Been sorting through the kids clothes, bagging up the stuff too small, cleaning out stuff in the nursery&amp;hellip;. I am so sad.
It is so weird to think we might be done having babies&amp;hellip;. so strange&amp;hellip;. so sad&amp;hellip;. I feel on the brink of tears. I have been trying all week to mentally prepare that we might be done, to figure out how to clean out the stuff and move on, but it is a lot harder than I thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Girl Wants</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-a-girl-wants/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 03:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-a-girl-wants/</guid>
      <description>Today was a big day in the life of sibling relations at the circus. Around my daughter’s third birthday, my strong willed, independent, knows what she wants toddler, morphed into a “whatever big brother does, that’s what I want too” little sister (she still kept her strong will however). Her favorite color went from purple to red (her brother’s fav color). For the past week she has been telling me how she wants a Spiderman cake just like her brothers when it is her birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Girl That Knows What She Wants</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-girl-that-knows-what-she-wants/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-girl-that-knows-what-she-wants/</guid>
      <description>Apparently my daughter’s week long rebellion was against sleeping alone in her crib and not on sleeping in general. Tuesday was a break through day for us!
She napped and slept through the night without screaming for hours first.
As I said goodnight to her in her sister’s bed, she had the BIGGEST grin on her face. Seriously, I have never seen a kid so excited about sleeping in a bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re Ruining Her</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-ruining-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2009 06:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-ruining-her/</guid>
      <description>Since we first brought my youngest home from the hospital at two days old, she has been a good sleeper. You could just lay her down and walk away and she would soothe herself to sleep. Scott and I commented a few months ago that we haven’t had to go in the middle of the night to help soothe her back to sleep. Even when she threw up in her crib in the middle of the night, she just rolled back over and went to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Little Spidey</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-little-spidey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2009 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-little-spidey/</guid>
      <description>My son is obsessed with all things Spiderman. I remember when he was about 2 and he saw a picture of Spiderman on something in the grocery store. He asked me what that was and I told him Spiderman. I remember he giggled saying that was so silly, to have a spider man. Sometime since then, he got bit by the spidey bug! I love this picture…the smile on his face was worth all the effort it took to make that cake!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traveling Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/traveling-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/traveling-circus/</guid>
      <description>Our bags are packed, checked, we’ve passed security, and now the circus crew is sitting in the terminal snacking on bagels, waiting to board the plane for El Paso (well, to Jackson to Huston to El Paso)!
 
You haven’t see the circus till you’ve see 2 adults, three preschoolers, our 8 checked bags and our 4 carry on items go through the check in line and security. Let’s throw in a little reshuffling of items in our bags to try and make all of our bags meet the weight limit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The REAL Winner</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-real-winner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-real-winner/</guid>
      <description>To the smart mom or dad who invented the quiet game.
I say, “THANK YOU!”
Seriously, you’ve changed my life…or at least my commute to and from the grocery store. Last week in a desperate attempt to keep my sanity as I drove my three overly tired, overly hungry, did I mention whiny, children home from B.J.’s I remembered this game of my youth. And given the highly competitive nature of my two oldest, I thought they just might take to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just the Three of Us</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-the-three-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-the-three-of-us/</guid>
      <description>Timely, we are not.
But we do follow through…eventually.
We promised our daughter on her third birthday in early Feb, that her gift from us would be a special trip with Mommy and Daddy to make her own teddy bear.
Two months later, the magical moment happened.
After dropping her siblings off at Nana and Pop’s, Scott and I realized this was the first time we had spent time, just the three of us, since she was in the hospital three years ago!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like a Fool</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/like-a-fool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/like-a-fool/</guid>
      <description>I’m always looking for something to spice things up here at the circus. And this year I think the kids are old enough to really enjoy some pranks tomorrow for April Fools. I was delighted to open my recent addition of Family Fun magazine and find some fun little pranks to pull on the little ones. All sweet innocent fun!
So, tomorrow we’ll be having some arctic cereal. ( The night before April Fools&#39; day, pour milk over half a bowl of cereal and put it in the freezer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>His Dream Come True</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/his-dream-come-true/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 20:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/his-dream-come-true/</guid>
      <description>My son loves baseball. I am not sure exactly where this love comes from since his dad and I are both avid football fans, but could care less about baseball. Didn’t even watch the World Series. In fact, the only baseball I’ve watched over the past few years, I’ve watched with my son. As a 2 year old, he would ask for it on TV and we’d sit and watch several innings on ESPN or catch a little on Sports Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Through the Eyes of My Soon To Be 5 Year Old</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/through-the-eyes-of-my-soon-to-be-5-year-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/through-the-eyes-of-my-soon-to-be-5-year-old/</guid>
      <description>When my oldest doesn’t take a nap, I am often looking for creative ways for him to play quietly while the girls sleep and I do “whatever I do” during nap time. Often time he plays quietly in his nap room (I separate the kids during nap time so they aren’t sleeping in the same room) or will play a computer game. Some days, however, I give him the point and shoot and let him have fun with his artistic side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Someday</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/someday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/someday/</guid>
      <description>Someday when I open my silverware drawer I will find each piece sitting neatly in the slot it belongs.
Someday my kids won’t come running when they hear me opening the dishwasher, eager to help put the dishes away.
And I will look back on these days when my 19 mth old did it all by herself with longing.
So, today I am enjoying the help!
 
Check out 5M4M for actual Wordless Wednesdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby, I’m Yours!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/baby-im-yours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 06:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/baby-im-yours/</guid>
      <description>5 years ago if you had told me that I would care, I mean really care, about a little stuffed animal blankey, I would have laughed. Shortly before I stopped teaching my third graders threw me a “surprise” baby shower. One of my students gave me a blankey/stuffed animal all in one. You know those things that have an animal head on one end, blankey in the middle and feet and buttom on the other end?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T.G.I.F.</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t.g.i.f./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t.g.i.f./</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;It&amp;rsquo;s Friday night/And the mood is right/Gonna have some fun/Show you how it&amp;rsquo;s done, TGIF..&amp;quot;
Remember those days? Nothing better topped off a hard week of going to school and talking on the phone like a little Full House, Family Matters, and Perfect Strangers. T.G.I.F.
If ever there was a week that needed an end, this week here at the circus, was it.
What with puke, and then puke, then a missed gymnastics performance due to puke, and then missing your best friends birthday party thanks to your sisters puke, followed by more puke, then a power outage, puke, snow, still more puke, then Daddy away on a business trip, his homecoming strangely enough followed the next morning by still more puke…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying to Bottle It Up and Save it For Later</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/trying-to-bottle-it-up-and-save-it-for-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/trying-to-bottle-it-up-and-save-it-for-later/</guid>
      <description>These days pass quickly as I’ve been warned and I stink at keeping a journal, so lately I’ve been quickly opening up my e-mail and trying to jot down the things the kids do and say that I want to remember and then saving it in my drafts folder. Here are some recent memories recorded so I don’t forget…
son: AWWWWWWWWWWWAAAHHHHHHHH Scott: What is wrong? son: My guitar.&amp;amp;#160; I was playing the guitar and she pulled my pretend guitar plug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All About Me: According to My Son</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/all-about-me-according-to-my-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/all-about-me-according-to-my-son/</guid>
      <description>I saw this little questionnaire on face book this week and the responses from my friend’s daughters had me laughing out loud. So, I asked my son this list of 25 questions about his mom and here is what he said… 
  What is something mom always says to you? Son: no response (nice to know I leave such an impression)
  What makes mom happy? Son: obeying mom and loving mom</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plant a Seed…or two!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/plant-a-seedor-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 05:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/plant-a-seedor-two/</guid>
      <description>I am so excited to share some news with you all. After my post on Friday about how much I loved the Seeds Family worship CDs, Michelle from Seeds contacted me. She’s offering all of my readers a 20% discount off of any of their CD’s. I have my very first discount code! How cool is that?!
Simply enter the code CIRCUSREADERS09 when purchasing a CD from their site. I plan to buy some more myself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Are Always Listening</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/they-are-always-listening/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/they-are-always-listening/</guid>
      <description>Kids make good accountability partners. Whether you ask them to be or not.
As a SAHM mom, I am with my kids pretty much all day and evening. With the exception of an evening out here or there. And my kids are watching me. They are taking in what I listen to on the radio, how I respond when I am tired, stressed. They are there for it all.
I have been impressed and sometimes surprised with how carefully they are listening to the words of the lyrics we listen to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Exactly Frosty…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-exactly-frosty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-exactly-frosty/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a few years since we’ve had a good snow fall here in MD. And by good I mean accumulating enough so that you don’t see the grass poking through the snow. This is the only snowman we were able to scrape together this winter at the circus. Don’t the kids look kind of forlorn? 
Seriously, take a closer look at our “snowman.” I am sure my friends up north are rolling on the floor with laughter at our patheticness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be Careful of Mr. Black</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/be-careful-of-mr.-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2009 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/be-careful-of-mr.-black/</guid>
      <description>Today a dental hygienist visited my son’s class at preschool. In the car he told me we needed to get him some dental cloth. “Floss?” I asked. “Yes,” he told me, “We gotta get rid of Mr. Black.”
pause
My son then commented, “I have no idea who Mr. Black is but we gotta get rid of him.”
I suggested maybe he was a cavity.
“Yea or dead food.” he replied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little Out of the Ordinary</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-little-out-of-the-ordinary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-little-out-of-the-ordinary/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it takes very little to turn the ordinary into something memorable. If your willing to change things up a bit, you can have fun with really, very little effort.
The other day the kids and I baked some cookies for a care package, but we saved some to enjoy with Daddy after dinner. While we don’t have dessert everyday, a chocolate chip cookie after dinner is not all that memorable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret’s Out</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/secrets-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/secrets-out/</guid>
      <description>You ever ever start playing a game without even realizing it until it’s well underway? Two years ago the kids and I were shopping in the candy aisle at Rite Aid looking for cheap V-day candy after the 14th, when we stumbled across this guy selling on clearance for a little over a dollar.

 My son was big into motorcycles and Snoopy, so it was fun gift for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Me!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 04:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-me/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Not Me! Monday! This blog carnival was created by MckMama. You can head over to her blog to read what she and everyone else have not been doing this week.
While I was posting about my true love story each day last week, a whole circus load of activity was going on around here.
I did not…
 put my kids to bed without having them brush their teeth because we got home late from a church meeting and I was trying to rush the bedtime routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Daughter</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dear-daughter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dear-daughter/</guid>
      <description>We celebrated my daughter’s third birthday last weekend and in honor of that milestone, I thought I’d write her a letter. Perhaps I will take Wilma’s idea and pen it out to give to her at a later date. Until then, at least I will have the thoughts preserved.
Dear Daughter,
 I can’t believe it’s been three years since you entered the world. You are a tiny girl with a lot of spunk and you’ve always had a connection with your daddy that only daughter’s can have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jury’s Still Out…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/jurys-still-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/jurys-still-out/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned before, that Scott and I have not made any decisions regarding the size of our circus crew. Some days we feel quite complete with our trio, others there’s that desire to add another little one to the crew. So, we haven’t done anything drastic and we’re spending some time praying and thinking on it. But the crew members are starting to share their feelings on the matter. Not that we asked them their opinion mind you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Communism Began</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-communism-began/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 05:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-communism-began/</guid>
      <description>We have a few daily battles here at the circus which I have to mediate carefully. One involves who buckled their top straps first in the car seat and the other is over who gets to eat off of the coveted plate at meal time. I made the innocent mistake of purchasing three different animal face plates last year at Target. I also bought some basic color plates as well. I was careful to make sure I got red and purple (my son and daughter’s favorite colors as well as 2 others since they baby didn’t yet have an opinion on colors and it was nice to have extras for when friends are visiting).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Wish I Was Kidding</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-wish-i-was-kidding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-wish-i-was-kidding/</guid>
      <description>Wasn’t able to snap a picture of this one, because it was too disgusting for me to do anything but stop it right away…
But if anyone wondered why I call it life at the circus…
…just caught my 18th month old brushing her teeth with her brother’s tooth brush, in the dog bowl…
gross on so many levels…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Daybook</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-daybook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-daybook/</guid>
      <description>My Daybook: Monday January 12 **Outside my window&amp;hellip;**the sun is shining brightly and Christmas lights still hang on the front of the house (though no longer on the roof…we’re half way there) **I am thinking&amp;hellip;**I really need to stop putting off folding the laundry piled beside my bed I am thankful for&amp;hellip; the Steelers victory last night advancing them to the AFC Championship **From the learning room…**working on Catechism questions From the kitchen&amp;hellip; Scott will be making pancakes for him and the kids for dinner tonight **I am wearing&amp;hellip;**jeans and my Steelers Superbowl XL Champions Tee I am creating&amp;hellip; I am not that creative, I do hope to tackle hemming my sons pants this week, does that count?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Said Gingerbread Houses Were For Christmas?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-said-gingerbread-houses-were-for-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-said-gingerbread-houses-were-for-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Much like the decorating of the pumpkin, the constructing of the gingerbread house didn’t happen according to the traditional time line. We here at the circus like to do things in our own time, thank you very much!
I mentioned before that this year I decided to go with the kit over baking from scratch. I bought the kit in early December and kept waiting for that evening when we were all home and not already busy with something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candid Gems</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/candid-gems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/candid-gems/</guid>
      <description>Christmas provides you with many gems&amp;hellip;photos which capture the moment, in real life. Nothing like posing in front of the tree to bring out the true personality of your child.
Yes&amp;hellip; this is def what I meant when I said , &amp;ldquo;Smile in front of the camera so Mom can have a picture of you in your nice church clothes.&amp;rdquo;

I love this pic&amp;hellip; I am entitling it Christmas bliss&amp;hellip; I love that it is not posed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weenie Whistle</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/weenie-whistle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2008 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/weenie-whistle/</guid>
      <description>2 days before Christmas, Scott was talking with our son and he mentioned how he asked Santa for a remote control Lighting Mcqueen car.
OK here&amp;rsquo;s a slight problem because we hadn&amp;rsquo;t gotten him a remote control one. I had just gotten him a little matchbox size mcqueen car for his stocking (because Santa does the stockings at our house).
So, I went out to Target on Christmas Eve to try to find a remote control Lighting Mcqueen car, with no such luck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Morning at the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-morning-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-morning-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes It&#39;s All in the Journey</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sometimes-its-all-in-the-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sometimes-its-all-in-the-journey/</guid>
      <description>We decided to take a spontaneous trip to DC this Saturday. And by spontaneous, I really mean spontaneous. When we left the house we were deciding between a trip to Hersheypark or the local train garden and drive through light display. Basically, we were looking for a fun evening out enjoying some holiday cheer. As we were driving, we got the idea of going into DC to see the National Christmas Tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One&#39;s for You Mom...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-ones-for-you-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-ones-for-you-mom/</guid>
      <description>When I was little if you wanted to make my mom mad, all you had to do was ask her who was visiting when she was cleaning house. Oh how I remember the look she&amp;rsquo;d get on her face when I would say that&amp;hellip;.seems my turn has come&amp;hellip;

After decorating our cookies yesterday, I realized it was time to deep clean my kitchen. Once I scrubbed down the icing covered counter, it only made me realize how scummy the other counters looked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Cookie Baking Time!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-cookie-baking-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-cookie-baking-time/</guid>
      <description>After years of research in my test kitchen, I have found that Krusteaz sugar cookie mix tastes better than any of the &amp;ldquo;from scratch sugar cookies&amp;rdquo; I have made.
And not only do they taste good, but literally, you pour the mix, add water, and stir!!

This is crucial for me, because with my three preschoolers, Mommy needs to spend her time managing the flour and cutting out of the cookies, not measuring and mixing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>this one was written just for me..</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-one-was-written-just-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-one-was-written-just-for-me/</guid>
      <description>The circus crew and I went to run some errands this morning&amp;hellip;Target and Michale&amp;rsquo;s were ok&amp;hellip; granted we did crack the sugar sprinkle container when the baby threw it on the floor, and my older daughter soon had the spilled sugar all over her face and hands after &amp;ldquo;sampling it&amp;rdquo; but we only got a few looks when the kids were singing jingle bells as they hung off the side of the cart while I finished my shopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Know You Have Preschoolers When...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-know-you-have-preschoolers-when/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 04:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-know-you-have-preschoolers-when/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;you start spelling anything you don&amp;rsquo;t want others to over hear.
Case in point&amp;hellip;
Scott and I had parked the car in a crowded parking garage recently, and I knew better than to shout, &amp;ldquo;Hey Honey did you lock the car?&amp;rdquo;
So, without even thinking, I said, &amp;ldquo;Scott, don&amp;rsquo;t forget to L-O-C-K the van!&amp;rdquo;
But, unlike the preschoolers at home who I am accustomed to spelling around if I don&amp;rsquo;t want them to figure out what I am saying, MOST thieves can spell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof that the sound of quiet isn&#39;t a good thing...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proof-that-the-sound-of-quiet-isnt-a-good-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 06:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proof-that-the-sound-of-quiet-isnt-a-good-thing/</guid>
      <description>Hmmm, it&amp;rsquo;s a bit too quiet, better go investigate&amp;hellip;

What Mom? You didn&amp;rsquo;t want me to wash my sister&amp;rsquo;s hair?
Hmm, well I wasn&amp;rsquo;t doing that, honest&amp;hellip; I was ummm washing my hands&amp;hellip;
Yea&amp;hellip;no idea how her hair got so wet&amp;hellip;.

Mom, When&amp;rsquo;s payback time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Saint Nicholas</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/meet-saint-nicholas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/meet-saint-nicholas/</guid>
      <description>My son often refers to Santa as Saint Nicholas. I guess it&amp;rsquo;s because of reading Jolly Old Saint Nicholas and Twas the Night Before Christmas.
This week my son decided he wanted to pretend to be Saint Nicholas.
Meet Jolly Old Saint Nick himself&amp;hellip;

Check out his sleigh (the blanket&amp;hellip;see him holding the reigns?) and note the stuffed bear playing the roll of reindeer.

Filling the stockings&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing School from a New Perspective</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/playing-school-from-a-new-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/playing-school-from-a-new-perspective/</guid>
      <description>My daughter loves to play school. She asks me to play All.The.Time.
But, my daughter has never been to school.
And everything she knows about school, she learned from watching her big brother.
So when we &amp;ldquo;play school&amp;rdquo; it goes something like this&amp;hellip;
My daughter takes her booster seat down from the table and sets it up in the hall to be her &amp;ldquo;car seat&amp;rdquo;. She then has me strap her in and drive her to school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crafty Tuesdays</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/crafty-tuesdays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/crafty-tuesdays/</guid>
      <description>Crafty, I am not. But, I was an elementary education major, so I do know how to use scissors and glue. And, I have found that I really enjoy doing simple arts and crafts projects with my children.
But, the circus life can get rather busy. And as with most things, if I am not intentional, the opportunities and the moments pass me by.
So, this year I have designated Tuesday as &amp;ldquo;Crafty Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly Away dear boy Fly Away!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fly-away-dear-boy-fly-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fly-away-dear-boy-fly-away/</guid>
      <description>Who would ever thought soccer cleats could be so cute? When I took my son to get his cleats at the beginning of the season, I thought those cleats were far cuter than any baby bootie I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen. I&amp;rsquo;ve never been into bronzing the baby shoes, but I will be tucking these cleats away in a box to look at years from now when I complain of the big stinky cleats I find sitting in my doorway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Late Than Never, Right?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/better-late-than-never-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 03:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/better-late-than-never-right/</guid>
      <description>We didn&amp;rsquo;t get to carving pumpkins this year. The kids each got to pick a pumpkin at our field trip to the petting farm, and while they were quite content with this size of their pumpkins, they weren&amp;rsquo;t exactly jack-o-lantern material. I am sure we&amp;rsquo;d have had to pay a trip to the ER if we attempted to carve such small pumpkins. I kept holding out for a trip to a &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; pumpkin patch, but it just wasn&amp;rsquo;t in the cards this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh Yes I Did</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/oh-yes-i-did/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/oh-yes-i-did/</guid>
      <description>Isn&amp;rsquo;t she a cutie? I&amp;rsquo;m embarrassed to admit that twice in the last week I took my poor baby girl out in these shoes. Yea&amp;hellip; go ahead take a closer look incase you missed it at first. Same style, but ummm different color. The first was on a Sunday morning. I was doing that mad dash for the door b/c we were already going to be late and I was literally just grabbing whatever shoe I could find with hopes that by the time I reached the door I&amp;rsquo;d have at least one match in my hand (and banking on that fact that if I didn&amp;rsquo;t, the other half would be waiting in the van).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anyone Miss Me??</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/anyone-miss-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/anyone-miss-me/</guid>
      <description>I know I didn&amp;rsquo;t post this weekend AND it is now Monday afternoon and still nothing&amp;hellip;
I started a brief summary in pictures of my weekend&amp;rsquo;s activities 2 hours ago, but then 5 phone calls and 3 kids up from there naps later and I am still left with this&amp;hellip;.
yea, so&amp;hellip;. I am now feeding my kids some scrambled eggs and then am off to drop my kids off at a friend&amp;rsquo;s and head to set up for our MOPS meeting tonight&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homeward Bound</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/homeward-bound/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 12:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/homeward-bound/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little Mommy</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-little-mommy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-little-mommy/</guid>
      <description>Our two year old as gotten quite attached to her baby doll. She mothers her in all sorts of ways.
She reads her stories at nap time.

And arranges a spot for her (and almost every one of her stuffed animals) to sleep beside her at nap time.

She gives her a nebulizer treatment because she had a bad cough.

She even started potty training her this week!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Days are so Fleeting</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/these-days-are-so-fleeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/these-days-are-so-fleeting/</guid>
      <description>I gotta confess from the start, this is not quite Wordless.

As I was tidying up the house during nap time this week, I found this in my kitchen. I bent down to pick them up and decided to snap a quick picture first. Because some day, my kids will be grown and in school, and I won&amp;rsquo;t find half dressed baby dolls lying on the floor beside toy guns with my vacuum attachment stuck on top to turn it into a light saber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worth a Thousand Words and Then Some...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/worth-a-thousand-words-and-then-some/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/worth-a-thousand-words-and-then-some/</guid>
      <description>My son had his first soccer game last weekend. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have been a more proud mom on the sideline as I watched him play. He grinned from ear to ear the entire time he was out there. By looking at these pictures you&amp;rsquo;d think he was the star of the game. (of course in my eyes, he was) Check him out as he blows past the other team and heads for the goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would you like that bun buttered?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/would-you-like-that-bun-buttered/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 04:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/would-you-like-that-bun-buttered/</guid>
      <description>My husband was grilling burgers for dinner the other day. I had set the buns out on the counter to defrost earlier in the day. I&amp;rsquo;d also set out a stick of butter because I planned to bake cookies this weekend and knew I&amp;rsquo;d need the butter to be soft.
I had seen my 2 year old daughter over by the counter asking about the bread, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t pay that much attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take Me Out to the Ballgame</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/take-me-out-to-the-ballgame/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/take-me-out-to-the-ballgame/</guid>
      <description>My son is an individual. Despite the fact that his parents are crazy football fans and could care less about baseball, he decided when he was about 2 that he loved baseball. He&amp;rsquo;d willingly sit and watch it on TV. We&amp;rsquo;ve even Tivoed a few games for him or let him watch portions of Sports Center. We&amp;rsquo;ve taken him to a few minor league games in the past, but tonight we took our oldest two children to their first Major League Baseball Game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you notice the difference?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/do-you-notice-the-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/do-you-notice-the-difference/</guid>
      <description>Do you see it? Look closer&amp;hellip; notice anything different? That extra sparkle in my eye&amp;hellip;The chest swelled with pride&amp;hellip;
I crossed yet another mommy milestone this weekend.
First came the diaper bag&amp;hellip;.no longer could I leave the house with nothing but my purse, leaving the house suddenly entailed making sure I had diapers wipes, spare clothes, pacifiers, toys, bibs, the kitchen sink&amp;hellip;. then came child two and mysteriously the diaper bag actually shrank as I realized I don&amp;rsquo;t&#39; need everything on those lists in the new mommy books&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Pathetic</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/looking-pathetic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/looking-pathetic/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t typically attempt this task on my own. Not since baby number 2 arrived anyway. But my husband had to work that day and it had to be done, so the task was left to me. And my three kids.
I pulled into the parking lot of our vet&amp;rsquo;s office, put both girls in the stroller, grabbed the dog leash, and had instructed my son to walk beside the stroller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Love Camping</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/why-we-love-camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/why-we-love-camping/</guid>
      <description>Here are the top 10 reasons why my family loves to go camping.
10. It&amp;rsquo;s cheaper than a hotel
($20 a night versus $150 a night)
9. Smores!

8. It ensures that the ground will get the water its been deprived of all summer long.

7. Beautiful views

6. Togetherness

(look how cozy our beds look in there&amp;hellip;we almost always wake with at least one kiddo snuggled up next to us)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes Life S-T-I-N-K-S!!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sometimes-life-s-t-i-n-k-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sometimes-life-s-t-i-n-k-s/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday was one of those days. I heard my baby fussing from her nap so I went in to get her. I knew when I approached the door she needed her diaper changed. It was that smelly.
However, when I went to pick her up, I was surprised to discover her diaper didn&amp;rsquo;t do it&amp;rsquo;s job. (and unlike last time, there really was a diaper there, it just didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to hold the goods)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Super Hero</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-super-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 04:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-super-hero/</guid>
      <description>We had an incident a few weeks ago at the park. One of those, turn your back for one seconds, incidents. The kids were frolicking in the grass and I turned to look at the baby, when I turned back my two year old was gone.
After suffering the sick feeling of panic in my stomach and running around like a crazy mama I heard her crying. She had fallen down during her frolic and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see her in the tall grass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Opportunity to Exercise My Patience</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-opportunity-to-exercise-my-patience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-opportunity-to-exercise-my-patience/</guid>
      <description>My hubby and I had the sad realization the other day that we aren&amp;rsquo;t as good of parents as we thought we were. See our son is 4 years old and we haven&amp;rsquo;t taught him to ride a bike or to swim.
So, we decided it was time to get the boy a bike.
Hubby thought a consignment shop was a good idea, because why spend a butt load of money when you don&amp;rsquo;t have to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/girls-just-wanna-have-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/girls-just-wanna-have-fun/</guid>
      <description>This weekend my husband and my son went away for a Father/Son camping trip. More pics and details to follow later this week. For now, it&amp;rsquo;s girl time!!
 I stayed home with the two girls. We had a wonderful time playing and bonding. We baked chocolate chip cookies. Because a girl has got to have her chocolate fix, right?  And then to be completely stereotypical, I took them shopping at the mall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agree to Disagree</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/agree-to-disagree/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/agree-to-disagree/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I see eye to eye on most things. When it comes to parenting though, we have one major disagreement&amp;hellip;
pajamas
I think they are cute and cuddly and so adorable.
Scott thinks they are impractical and a complete waste of time. &amp;quot;Why do we need to change them just to sleep,&amp;quot; He asks.
I have a hard time coming up with a real compelling reason.
&amp;quot;Because they look so cute in them,&amp;quot; is typically my reply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Knew??</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-knew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-knew/</guid>
      <description>Last week was a busy week around my house&amp;hellip;with celebrating my birthday and preparing for my baby girl&amp;rsquo;s first birthday party, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of spare time left for reading the Internet. So, of course when I checked CNN.com to scan the headlines, I only had time for one article. Which article did this homebound mommy starved for information on life outside of the circus, click on?
&amp;lsquo;It was like I was on Rollerblades,&amp;rsquo; says Miss USA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Quite Have Eyes in the Back of My Head</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-quite-have-eyes-in-the-back-of-my-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-quite-have-eyes-in-the-back-of-my-head/</guid>
      <description>Ya know how they say Mom&amp;rsquo;s have eyes in the back of their head? I&amp;rsquo;m not sure exactly when my extra set will arrive&amp;hellip; do my children have to reach a certain age, or do I need to have a certain number of children? Seems that with a 4 year old, a 2 year old, and an almost 1 year old&amp;hellip; I could really use those extra set of eyes&amp;hellip;NOW!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ll Do to my Children for Free Chick-Fil-A</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-ill-do-to-my-children-for-free-chick-fil-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/what-ill-do-to-my-children-for-free-chick-fil-a/</guid>
      <description>I LOVE Chick-Fil-A. I could go on and on about how family friendly they are, how good their food is, how I think Truitt Cathy is such a great example of a godly businessman&amp;hellip; but I will save my love affair with Chick-Fil-A, the inventors of the chicken sandwich, for another post, or two&amp;hellip;
Friday was Cow Appreciation Day. I know this because I subscribe to the Chick-Fil-A e-mail updates and I am in on all things up and coming at Chick-Fil-A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Shortest Pregnancy Yet</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-shortest-pregnancy-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-shortest-pregnancy-yet/</guid>
      <description>Time for another Sincerley Fro&#39; Me To You Post. Since my baby turns one this month, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share a pregnancy anecdote with you.
In January of last year my good friend told me she was pregnant with her third child. Her oldest son is 10 months younger than my son, and the two of them are good buddies. Her second son is 4 months younger than my middle child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Library Revisited</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/library-revisited/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/library-revisited/</guid>
      <description>I have a problem. Despite my best intentions, I seem incapable of returning library books on time. Upon returning home from the library, my husband often asks, &amp;ldquo;So, how much are these going to cost us?&amp;rdquo; It seems our library visits are taking a dramatic turn for the worst.
Even after our bad experience at the library , I took the kids back for books. This last time we weren&amp;rsquo;t scolded for our &amp;ldquo;inside voices&amp;rdquo; so I thought all was good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We made it till the third...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-made-it-till-the-third/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-made-it-till-the-third/</guid>
      <description>Kids like buttons. At least ours do. Our son was the first addict. We could keep him happy quiet for long periods of time by giving him the TV remote (with the TV off) and letting him just pound away. Him being the first, we were always careful when he got the phone. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want him to call someone unintentionally and have someone listening to uncensored Life at the Circus. He never really called anyone though, because life with one isn&amp;rsquo;t quite a circus, he just hit buttons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Love to Laugh</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-love-to-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-love-to-laugh/</guid>
      <description>I love my son&amp;rsquo;s imagination! He is at age where I wish I could just freeze time. He cracks us with his antics these days. Check out last week&amp;rsquo;s comedy routines.
My son was playing on the deck when I suddenly heard him say, &amp;ldquo;Help Mom, I&amp;rsquo;m stuck.&amp;rdquo; I turned around to see this.

As I got him out of the basketball net, I asked him what on earth he was doing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Do It</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-i-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-i-do-it/</guid>
      <description>It was a big day for me. I know your thinking, yes, we know already, you got your power back. And yes I did, but that is not what I am referring to. I pulled into the parking lot of Target (which is 20 min away) with all 3 kids, at 8:30 AM. If you have kids, you recognize the monumental occasion this is.
Wanna know the secret to my record breaking time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are we there yet?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/are-we-there-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/are-we-there-yet/</guid>
      <description>Traveling for 5 hours in a minivan with 3 young children and one dog sounds like a kicking good time, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it? Since my parents live a little over 5 hrs from us, we&amp;rsquo;ve gotten quite adjusted to the trip. And surprisingly, it isn&amp;rsquo;t that bad. We&amp;rsquo;ve had our bad trips (like the time my son got the stomach flu the morning we were heading back home and puked every 30 min the entire way home), but overall we&amp;rsquo;ve found the key to happiness is letting the kids entertain themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ahoy there Matey!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ahoy-there-matey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ahoy-there-matey/</guid>
      <description>Check out [5 Minutes for Mom] (http://5MinutesForMom.com)for more Wordless Wednesdays!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wonder of Childhood</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-wonder-of-childhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-wonder-of-childhood/</guid>
      <description>Remember the time when everything you encountered was new and exciting, something worthy of careful inspection? Bring back the kid in you and pause long enough to discover something new today.

I am entering this photo in the Nestle &amp;ldquo;The Kid in You&amp;rdquo; Photo Contest over at 5 Minutes for Mom for the chance to win a Nintendo Wii. (I played a Wii for the first time this weekend at the house of Muthering Heights and let&amp;rsquo;s just say the prize is appropriate because playing tennis really brought out the kid in all of us) !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day in the Life...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-day-in-the-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-day-in-the-life/</guid>
      <description>Ever had one of those days where you take one step forward only to take two steps back? That&amp;rsquo;s what my days felt like this week&amp;hellip; the good news is that my older two have been playing very well together, so well that I haven&amp;rsquo;t felt the need to go to playgroup or find a play date to get us all out of the house. They&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed playing their various pretend games in one section of the house, while I was able to work on something productive in a different part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Routine to Take on the Road</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-routine-to-take-on-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-routine-to-take-on-the-road/</guid>
      <description>Driving home the other day my 2 year old, called from the back of the van, &amp;ldquo;Excuse me mom, where&amp;rsquo;s baby?&amp;rdquo; I would have panicked had I not just heard her babbling moments before. Since, it was obvious she was there, I answered with something silly like, &amp;ldquo;Driving the car.&amp;rdquo; She erupted in giggles and thus began our newest comedy routine.
This was our conversation all the way to church this morning, in the parking lot after church while we were waiting for Daddy to finish talking, on the way out to lunch, on the way home&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Sisters don&#39;t make good baby dolls</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/baby-sisters-dont-make-good-baby-dolls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/baby-sisters-dont-make-good-baby-dolls/</guid>
      <description>Last week my two year old wanted desperatly to hold my 9 month old. This is a practice I don&amp;rsquo;t generally encourage, unless I am trying to take a picture of the kids together, then it&amp;rsquo;s used as a bribe. Let Mommy take your picture and you can hold your sister! This time however, it went the other way around&amp;hellip;Mommy you can take a picture if you let me hold my sister.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Guys Beware</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bad-guys-beware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bad-guys-beware/</guid>
      <description>Since Christmas my 4 year old son has built up quite a weapons arsenal.

A few days before Christmas my sister in law called to ask if it was OK for our son to have a toy gun for Christmas. Since we had just been to the store looking for one, I think our answer was pretty obvious.

In January my husband built wooden swords for him and my son to practice sword fighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Say...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kids-say-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kids-say-1/</guid>
      <description>The other day our two year old had a really bad diaper rash. Her poor bottom was BRIGHT RED and she screamed out in pain when we had to change her diaper. My son looked at her bottom and exclaimed, &amp;ldquo;Diaper rash is my favorite color!&amp;rdquo;
That boy makes me laugh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Under the Big Top (Part 2)</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/under-the-big-top-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/under-the-big-top-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I posted about how similar our life is to the real circus we visited last week. I would now like to point out two unfortunate differences.
At the circus they have these men dressed in all black that come into the ring between acts and clean up. They remove equipment, clean up poop, and set up for the next act. I need these men at my house. Imagine if after the meal (act 1) these men just instantly appeared and quietly, miraculously, cleaned up the mess when we move on to playtime (act 2).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Dream Come True</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-dream-come-true/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2008 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-dream-come-true/</guid>
      <description>Two months ago, my mom came across some of my old school papers and she passed this one along to me. I wrote it in first grade. I have no recollection of writing this, but I have to think that God smiled as I wrote it, thinking, &amp;ldquo;You have no idea Crystal that your dream will come true exactly as you wish for.&amp;rdquo; Today I thank God for allowing me to be the mom to 3 wonderful children, one son and two daughters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week End Thoughts: My Mom</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/week-end-thoughts-my-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/week-end-thoughts-my-mom/</guid>
      <description>Since Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day is this weekend, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d make my thoughtful post about my mother. Growing up my mom was my best friend. She was approachable and always willing to listen. I could ask her about anything and she never made me feel awkward or silly. Mom knew how to make things special. She decorated the house for the seasons and holidays and made our birthdays into something we looked forward to all year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s the Begining of the End</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-the-begining-of-the-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-the-begining-of-the-end/</guid>
      <description>My kids and I have truly enjoyed our local library. We go to to story time, baby story time, special events, and we go just to check out books. The kids LOVE it! It&amp;rsquo;s a happy place, a fun place, a place where a kid can be a kid&amp;hellip; until today.
I took the kids to the library earlier this week to pick out books. I know my kids can be loud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I try to give the very best...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-try-to-give-the-very-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-try-to-give-the-very-best/</guid>
      <description>If any of you are like me you love buying cards. Actually, if your anything like me you have three kids and you used to love buying cards. I remember the good old days when a friend and I would go to Hallmark and spend too much time reading, laughing, picking out cards. It was relaxing. I enjoyed finding those perfect cards to give to people. I enjoyed it so much that I would eagerly try to come up with people whose birthdays or special days were approaching somewhere in the next month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons Learned From Motherhood</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lessons-learned-from-motherhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lessons-learned-from-motherhood/</guid>
      <description>Mothers Day is coming soon and it has got me thinking about the many things I didn&amp;rsquo;t know about motherhood before I became a mom. There really is no way to mentally prepare. I remember the day after my first child was born sitting in the hospital filling out paperwork. When I saw the line for Mother I honestly thought, &amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s odd, I wonder why they need to know my mom&amp;rsquo;s name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep the Crew Happy and Quiet in a Tiny Room</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keep-the-crew-happy-and-quiet-in-a-tiny-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keep-the-crew-happy-and-quiet-in-a-tiny-room/</guid>
      <description>Keeping three kids happy while waiting at the doctors office is a difficult task. Usually we get through the waiting room without a problem&amp;hellip; the kids can rearrange the chairs, roll around on the floor, take magazines off of the shelf and occasionally sit quietly in my lap and read a book. It&amp;rsquo;s that tiny examination room that presents the problem. I know they keep the place clean but the bottom line is that doctors offices are where sick people go and I would rather we keep our germs to ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s up Doc?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/whats-up-doc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/whats-up-doc/</guid>
      <description>My oldest and youngest had well visits today. Our trip to the pediatrician&amp;rsquo;s office was a circus act in and of itself. I made the appointment for 8:30a.m. The nice thing about early appointments is that we don&amp;rsquo;t have to wait long in the waiting room. The hard part is that it takes an insane amount of work to get the three kids fed, dressed (they can&amp;rsquo;t exactly show up in dirty underwear and pjs) and in the minivan by 8:10&amp;hellip;not to mention the fact that I usually try to look presentable myself which means I have to actually shower and do something with my hair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Cry Over....</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-cry-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-cry-over/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;.Flushed Poop&amp;hellip;..
Yes, you read that correctly and if bathroom talk/humor is not your thing, then I suggest you skip this post.
The following incident actually occurred in my house today. Sometimes I wonder, &amp;ldquo;What will I write about in my blog today?&amp;rdquo; Or I worry if I will have enough stuff to write about to keep blogging far into the future&amp;hellip; then things like this occur, and I think, &amp;ldquo;Well, that&amp;rsquo;s today&amp;rsquo;s post!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Picture of Happiness</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-picture-of-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-picture-of-happiness/</guid>
      <description>Mothering takes a lot of hard work and a lot of late nights. While I only have four years of experience to look back on, I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure it is moments like these that I will cherish when I&amp;rsquo;m old and gray.

5 Minutes for Mom is hosting a Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day Photo Contest asking bloggers to post a picture that defines motherhood; I knew right away that I had to recycle this previous Wordless Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughtful Thursday: Answered Prayer</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thoughtful-thursday-answered-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thoughtful-thursday-answered-prayer/</guid>
      <description>Last week as we were running errands the Christian radio station played one of those 60 sec minisermons. The person was speaking on 1 John 4 and read the passage which states, &amp;ldquo;This is love: not that we loved God, but that he loved us and sent his Son as an atoning sacrifice for our sins.&amp;rdquo;
Son: &amp;quot; Mom, why did she say we don&amp;rsquo;t love God?&amp;quot;
Me: &amp;ldquo;They were saying that we didn&amp;rsquo;t love God first, but that God loved us and then we loved him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Blinked</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-blinked/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2008 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-blinked/</guid>
      <description>They warned me this would happen. I told myself I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t do it. And yet, I did and they were right. Darn those &amp;ldquo;experienced moms&amp;rdquo; who&amp;rsquo;ve been there and done that. Just last night I brought him home from the hospital and got up at least 8 times during the night to make sure he was still in the bassinet at the foot of our bed. During one of those middle of the night feedings I did the forbidden&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got some jewelry this week</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-got-some-jewelry-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 23:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-got-some-jewelry-this-week/</guid>
      <description>Nope, it&amp;rsquo;s not my birthday&amp;hellip; too late for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day&amp;hellip;.. too early for Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. This was just an &amp;ldquo;I love you&amp;rdquo; gift. It was made of clear fishing line with little foam charms. My son was very proud to tell me that he had made it himself with a plastic needle.
When my son gave me this bracelet which he made, &amp;ldquo;because I love you Mom&amp;rdquo; my heart melted. I wore it all day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyone has to get in on the Action</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everyone-has-to-get-in-on-the-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everyone-has-to-get-in-on-the-action/</guid>
      <description>With spring like weather finally here, we&amp;rsquo;ve been spending some more time outside. I took these series of pictures of the kids out on our deck. Note the sequence of events.
Baby is playing cutely in boat so Mommy decides to take a picture.
 Big Sister notices and has to get in on the action and spotlight.
&amp;ldquo;Hey, don&amp;rsquo;t leave me out!&amp;rdquo;
Poor baby is off to find something else to play with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up, Up, and Away</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/up-up-and-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/up-up-and-away/</guid>
      <description>Today I took the kids to the grocery store and in addition to some much needed food, the older two each got a balloon with a lollipop tied to the bottom. The store has them for free at the check out. A nice bonus for everyone! After I unloaded the van, they were out on the back deck eating their lollipops while I putting away the groceries. I heard some commotion, so I went outside and saw my daughter staring up at the sky like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Than Time and a Half</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/better-than-time-and-a-half/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/better-than-time-and-a-half/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m only one week into my blogging adventure and I already had to skip a day. Yesterday was one of THOSE days. Those of you with kids, know what I mean. It started Friday night when all 3 of my kids woke at various points throughout the night coughing, moaning and generally not feeling well (thankfully, no puking occurred). The &amp;ldquo;night&amp;rdquo; ended for good at 6:20 when I was up giving my son water, then my daughter a nebulizer treatment for her asthma and as soon as I finished, I heard the baby crying for me to nurse her!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All in a Row</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/all-in-a-row/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/all-in-a-row/</guid>
      <description>Our middle child really likes to put things in order. Before she goes to bed at night she puts each of her stuffed animals in a straight row beside her pillow. I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed recently that she seems to gravitate towards put things things into straight lines. When she plays with blocks she puts them next to each other in a row, like a road, rather then stacking them one on top of the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Little Goofball</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-little-goofball/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-little-goofball/</guid>
      <description>I love my son&amp;rsquo;s imagination. He can turn a cooking pot into a race car or become a dog by merely wearing his shoes on his hands. Here are a few pictures of his antics from this morning. They made me smile and I hope they do the same for you!
He called out to me in the other room, &amp;ldquo;Hey Mom, look I am siting on the pot!&amp;rdquo; When I heard these words, they brought a different image to mind.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
