<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dress up on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/dress-up/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dress up on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 13:08:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/dress-up/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How We Roll</title>
      <link>/posts/how-we-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-we-roll/</guid>
      <description>Round here our fairies do more than just fly around sprinkling pixy dust.

They dribble soccer balls and don football jerseys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You think I’d know by now…</title>
      <link>/posts/you-think-id-know-by-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/you-think-id-know-by-now/</guid>
      <description>When my son asked if he could bring his light sabers or guns to his sisters first soccer practice, I said no. Because sometimes it is awkward to deal with the whole gun issue out in public.
Obviously I forgot that little boys will turn absolutely anything into a gun.
So today I said what the heck, bring the gun. Which apparently translated to, go crazy, carry a gun in each hand and a concealed weapon… Heck, why not wear the entire uniform!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bet Your Harvest Party Never Had One of These</title>
      <link>/posts/bet-your-harvest-party-never-had-one-of-these/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bet-your-harvest-party-never-had-one-of-these/</guid>
      <description>We decided to add a little pizazz to our normal morning chaos as we got ready to leave for our tutorial today. Since it’s the last day the tutorial is meeting before Thanksgiving, they had a Harvest Party at the end of the day and the children were encouraged to come in costume.
My son went as an Indian and his little sister went as a Pilgrim. (costumes courtesy of Mommy’s costume bin from her school days… I was Pocahontas one year for Halloween and the “Pilgrim” dress was actually a costume from a church play).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incase You Were Wondering…</title>
      <link>/posts/incase-you-were-wondering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/incase-you-were-wondering/</guid>
      <description>This would be why more than one of my children thought chicken came from cows…
 Cow Appreciation Day at Chick-Fil-A is a tradition here at the circus.
We start them young with our indoctrination!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Pretty, Pretty Princesses</title>
      <link>/posts/our-pretty-pretty-princesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-pretty-pretty-princesses/</guid>
      <description>Visit here or here for more fun with pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Enjoys a Little Pampering</title>
      <link>/posts/everyone-enjoys-a-little-pampering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/everyone-enjoys-a-little-pampering/</guid>
      <description>I realized recently, that while I spend lots of time with my kids, too often it&amp;rsquo;s easy for me to spend the day with them, without really playing with them. So, these past few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing a lot more playing. And I gotta say, I&amp;rsquo;m loving it.
One hit with the circus crew recently has been beauty shop. To make it an equal opportunity for all, I did a little hair spiking for my son.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to the Chapel…</title>
      <link>/posts/going-to-the-chapel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/going-to-the-chapel/</guid>
      <description>I went to a wedding the other night.
The bride looked dashing in her floor length ball gown, with her shoulder length hair worn down. The groom was handsome in his navy blue jacket with a red and gray tie, and a simple black eyed susan taped to his jacket lapel. The bride carried matching black eyes susan’s picked fresh from her mother’s yard.  As the ceremony began the bride’s cell phone rang.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
