<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>comics on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/comics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in comics on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 08:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/comics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Life Lessons from Superman</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-lessons-from-superman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 08:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-lessons-from-superman/</guid>
      <description>Bet you can’t guess what movie we watched this weekend?

little boys dressed as super heroes truly melt my heart… especially this little boy… sitting at breakfast with his tussled hair and sheepish grin…
We had a family movie afternoon yesterday and watched The 1978 Original Superman with the big 3 while our three year old was napping. He woke up in time to catch the heroic finish and then fly around the basement with his cape blazing behind him while the theme music blasted from our stereo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Any other sneaks out there?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/any-other-sneaks-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 08:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/any-other-sneaks-out-there/</guid>
      <description>OK, so Halloween was 6 days ago, and I gotta tell you this circus mom has had more than her fair share of the loot. The kids are doing quite well with an occasional piece after a meal here or there. Mom on the other hand seems to go for the candy bowl come nap and bed time and she rarely stops with one. The other morning when the kids came out to the living room my son spotted a few candy wrappers sitting on the couch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Peanuts Gang</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-peanuts-gang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-peanuts-gang/</guid>
      <description>Those of you that have been visiting the circus for awhile know that I don’t use my kids names on the blogs. I once entertained the idea of pseudonyms but never came up with any I liked. So I’ve pretty much stuck with “ my son,” “my 3 year old daughter” and “my baby” for the past year or so. So far, I have no real intentions to change that, but I did realize last week, that had this been “Life with The Peanuts Gang” or something more catchy, I’d have perfect pseudonyms to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look Familiar Anyone?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/look-familiar-anyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2008 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/look-familiar-anyone/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
