<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sudan on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/sudan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sudan on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 21:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/sudan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Every Little Bit Helps</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/every-little-bit-helps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 21:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/every-little-bit-helps/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a LOOOOONG time since I’ve posted about Shopping for Sudan, but as 2011 comes to a close I thought I’d say thanks to those of you that participated with me in Shopping for Sudan. In 2011 you raised $47 dollars to help the people of Sudan. It may not seem like much but it’s a lot to the people who receive it. Furthermore, we are still matching the amount raised and so a total donation of $100 was made on your behalf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Monday</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cyber-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 08:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cyber-monday/</guid>
      <description>For those of you taking advantage of the sales found online today, I thought I’d remind you about my Shopping for Sudan opportunity. If you shop from Amazon.com, please bookmark my site and click on the (shop now) link on my top left side bar. It will take you directly to amazon.com
Help me get the word out about Shopping for Sudan! Tweet and or post a link on face book to my Shopping for Sudan post (Here is the link if you want to copy &amp;amp; paste it: http://lifeatthecircus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Were you part of it?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-you-part-of-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/were-you-part-of-it/</guid>
      <description>I was so excited at the end of the year when I checked my earnings report from Amazon. Since my last update on Nov 8th, we earned $89.32 more!

Thanks to all of you who clicked through my site first when doing your Christmas shopping at Amazon this season. I was so excited to make a donation to World Vision’s Sudan Food and Care fund for $180! Combined with the previous earnings, we have worked together to send ** $280 ** to aid the refugees in Sudan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulate Yourselves</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/congratulate-yourselves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/congratulate-yourselves/</guid>
      <description>For all of you who have bought something from Amazon and done so by clicking through my site, congratulate yourselves. I checked my Amazon affiliate account today and I have earned $50.00 thus far! As you may remember, Scott and I decided to match whatever money it earns (up to the first $200), so tonight I wrote a check to World Vision’s Sudan Relief Fund for $100! Whoohooo!  I know I just got through telling you that I don’t want to rush the Thanksgiving season, by thinking of Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
