<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 09:19:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One Year Later</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-year-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-year-later/</guid>
      <description>A year ago today Scott and I dropped the kids off at a friends house and went to sign on the dotted line about 20 gazillion times. We left with keys to our new home!
Scott and I headed to the new place to enjoy some take out Chinese on the back deck as we celebrated the immense blessing of this new home. Then as is the case quite often for us… our busy lives resumed… Scott back to work… me to grab some stuff from our old house to bring to our new house for our camp out that night… then we met up at the gym for our daughter’s Mini Olympics performance and I think we might have had a little league baseball game in there too… we got home much later that evening…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 weeks!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/2-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/2-weeks/</guid>
      <description>It’s been 2 weeks since we signed on the dotted line twenty million times and got the keys to our new home! And we’ve made some special memories in those two weeks, such as…

 camping out the first night in front of the fire place in an empty house riding bikes (every day since we got here… and I can’t believe how much better they are at riding bikes now… I have 3 proficient 2 wheelers now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humbled and Grateful</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/humbled-and-grateful/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/humbled-and-grateful/</guid>
      <description>These past few weeks have been some of the most exhausting in my life. It’s been 9 years and 4 kids since our last move and let’s just say we’ve acquired a whole lot more stuff since our last move. I purged and donated and purged some more and yet have found myself with enough miscellaneous boxes of random to sort through in the new house till Labor Day! Meanwhile we were listing our house for rent, showing it to perspective renters AND still trying to juggle the spring extra curriculars like year end home school evaluations, baseball games, gymnastics classes, play off games, mini Olympics, piano recitals, and birthdays and our anniversary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bittersweet Thoughts of Gratitude</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bittersweet-thoughts-of-gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bittersweet-thoughts-of-gratitude/</guid>
      <description>I remember vividly the first night we spent in our house. We were first time home owners.
And we were giddy. As we lay on the floor in our bedroom looking up at the ceiling I remember Scott commenting on the ceiling fan. “Look at that ceiling fan! We own it!” I on the other hand couldn’t get my eyes of the red blinking light from the smoke detector…. wondering how would I fall asleep with it constantly blinking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
