<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Me to You on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/me-to-you/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Me to You on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 12:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/me-to-you/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Things about My Day at Cub Scout Camp</title>
      <link>/posts/top-10-things-about-my-day-at-cub-scout-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/top-10-things-about-my-day-at-cub-scout-camp/</guid>
      <description>Last week my oldest son went to a week of Cub Scout Day Camp. This year he was a Webelos 1. I remember vividly his first year when he was but a wee Tiger Scout.  He loves Cub Scout camp. And who wouldn’t? 8 and a half hours outside each day, fishing, archery, BB guns, wood shop, specials, crafts…
Each parent is required to volunteer one day. Two years Scott served in this role, last year I went, but it was the last day of camp and I didn’t get to see as much of the action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She’s Got the Look</title>
      <link>/posts/shes-got-the-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/shes-got-the-look/</guid>
      <description>My oldest daughter has been demonstrating her growing independence and her new sense of style these days. Her new favorite pants are these orange leggings with candy corn on them that she got at Halloween. I don’t know what made her take such a liking to them this January but she wants to wear them EVERY. SINGLE. DAY. When she wanted to wear them to the park a few weeks ago with her purple sweater, I started to try and persuade her to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Says Happy Birthday Like…</title>
      <link>/posts/nothing-says-happy-birthday-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nothing-says-happy-birthday-like/</guid>
      <description>My little brother celebrated his birthday this week. And being the good big sister that I am, I thought I’d share some lovely pics of him growing up for my Fro Me to You post this week. Cuz’ nothing says happy birthday like having your big sister post your picture on the internet for the world to see.
Happy Birthday Little Brother!
Here we are at one of his birthdays. I am guessing he was five or 6, making me 8 or 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watching a Wedding With the Circus Crew</title>
      <link>/posts/watching-a-wedding-with-the-circus-crew/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/watching-a-wedding-with-the-circus-crew/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago Scott’s cousin was married in CA. Since the groom was from Brazil, we were among many friends and relatives that weren’t able to attend the ceremony. The family thoughtfully broadcasted the ceremony live on the internet. I had never attending a wedding this way before. While we would have preferred to attend the wedding in person and share in their celebration with them, in some ways, it was the easiest way to watch the ceremony with our three kids present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pitty Part</title>
      <link>/posts/the-pitty-part/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 20:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-pitty-part/</guid>
      <description>As a kid I really enjoyed being on stage. Had a rather significant part in our church musical when I was in third grade which led me to believe I had skill…even did a few plays in middle school (with embarrassing tales of their own to be shared on future Thursdays) but the high school band plays were my low points.
Each spring our school would put on a play written by our band director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes Good Questions, Aren’t</title>
      <link>/posts/sometimes-good-questions-arent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sometimes-good-questions-arent/</guid>
      <description>My son has always had a very inquisitive nature. When I was pregnant with my third child, he was three. He fully grasped the concept that there was a baby in my belly. But, what he wanted to know was, how the baby was coming out. At first I tried with vague, non specific responses. But they weren’t doing it for him. He kept bringing it up, again and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gingerbread Real Estate</title>
      <link>/posts/gingerbread-real-estate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2008 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gingerbread-real-estate/</guid>
      <description>My first memories of making a gingerbread house are at my high school friend Katie&amp;rsquo;s birthday party. It became a tradition. Each year her mom would bake the houses and make the icing and supply all the candy. We&amp;rsquo;d all come over for her birthday in December to decorate our houses. It was a ton of fun! We&amp;rsquo;d sit and talk, sneak candy and decorate our houses. I believe we made an all night affair out of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little Advent Music Anyone?</title>
      <link>/posts/a-little-advent-music-anyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-little-advent-music-anyone/</guid>
      <description>When I was pulling out Christmas decorations from the storage closet I came across a box of pictures&amp;hellip;perfect for my weekly blast from the past post. (I&amp;rsquo;ve got a few more set aside for the upcoming weeks).
If you notice, there is a Christmas tree in the background here. Every week my family did an advent devotional on Sunday evenings. We&amp;rsquo;d read a passage of Scripture, light the candle and sing some Christmas carols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hang on...</title>
      <link>/posts/hang-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hang-on/</guid>
      <description>Today I spent my &amp;ldquo;down time&amp;rdquo; working on some Christmas projects which needed to be finished so I could get them ordered and shipped. Then, I went about figuring out our Christmas card and ordering them.
Because, No&amp;hellip; I have not mailed my Christmas cards.
And until 5 minutes ago, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t even ordered them from Winkflash
Which means I have yet to address them or write our Christmas letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Only...</title>
      <link>/posts/if-only/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/if-only/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I took a nature walk last week. As we walked along the path, I realized we had necessary elements for some great pictures.
1. Happy Kids
2. Setting sun
3. Fall leaves
However, we forgot the photographer.
After frolicking along the path gathering leaves and sticks, I noticed that the suns rays were really quite beautiful. I remembered Scott saying that one of the best times of days to get pictures is before sunset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sign Pics Just Keep Getting Better</title>
      <link>/posts/the-sign-pics-just-keep-getting-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-sign-pics-just-keep-getting-better/</guid>
      <description>After posting last week&amp;rsquo;s goofy national park pics, many of you commented that you looked forward to the day we included the kids in these shots.
Well, wait no longer&amp;hellip;
It only took 18 mths for us to bring our son on his first national park trip.
Much like the beginning of our first trip, this pose was quite normal. Here we are in Acadia National Park.
 The next summer we had a two and half year old and a 7 month old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Too Many Park Signs</title>
      <link>/posts/one-too-many-park-signs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-too-many-park-signs/</guid>
      <description>When we&amp;rsquo;d been married a little over a year when we set out on a cross country vacation to take in National Parks, a few new cities, time with family, and a visit with friends. Because we are scrapbook geeks or maybe just geeks, we decided it would be fun to pose in front of each national park sign.
At first we posed like normal people, you know arm around each other all cute and coupley&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scary Costumes of Halloweens Past</title>
      <link>/posts/scary-costumes-of-halloweens-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/scary-costumes-of-halloweens-past/</guid>
      <description>This week the assignment for THAT Family&amp;rsquo;s carnival, was to post a scary pic from the past. So, I started looking through some old Halloween photos trying to find just the right one&amp;hellip;
I was never much into scary, though I did sport a mask in this costume when I was 4 or 5.

My son however, seems to take the prize for his scary costumes&amp;hellip;
Here he is at 6 mths sporting his ferocious dragon attire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Tough Princess</title>
      <link>/posts/one-tough-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-tough-princess/</guid>
      <description>With Halloween in the air, I decided to post one of my favorite trick or treating pictures of my middle child. It was taken last year when she a little over 18 mths old.
She might have been little, but she could hold her own. Check out the grip on her trick or treating pumpkin. And the look on that face says, &amp;ldquo;No body go near my loot!&amp;rdquo; This isn&amp;rsquo;t a damsel in distress kind of princess; she can handle things herself, thank you very much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Right of Passage</title>
      <link>/posts/a-right-of-passage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-right-of-passage/</guid>
      <description>Most scrapbooks include pictures of baby&amp;rsquo;s first steps, first food, first drink from a sippy cup&amp;hellip; but where do you put the picture of the first time baby ripped the wallpaper border above her crib? 
In our house it&amp;rsquo;s become a sort of right of passage.
Thank goodness we had lots of extra border from the first time we did the nursery. Poor Winnie the Pooh has been ripped 3 different times!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mama, Don&#39;t Let Your Babies Grow Up to Be Cow GIRLS!</title>
      <link>/posts/mama-dont-let-your-babies-grow-up-to-be-cow-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mama-dont-let-your-babies-grow-up-to-be-cow-girls/</guid>
      <description>My recent trip to Dallas, prompted me to bring home some cowboy/girl hats for my kiddos and as I snapped pictures of them playing dress up, I was reminded of some pictures from my past which look very similar.
In the picture below, I am on a riding horse with a cowgirl like hat at around 17 mths&amp;hellip; a mere 2 mths older than my baby girl. Like the old Polaroid picture?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newlywed Days</title>
      <link>/posts/newlywed-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/newlywed-days/</guid>
      <description>I was scrolling through pictures, trying to figure out what to post for THAT Family&amp;rsquo;s weekly carnival, when I came across these photos from my Newlywed Days. Aren&amp;rsquo;t these just a blast from the past?

Here we are enjoying our first dinner in our apartment&amp;hellip; yup that would be frozen pizza and champagne. We had just flown in from our honeymoon in St Lucia (you can see the unopened wedding presents behind us).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Miss Her</title>
      <link>/posts/i-miss-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/i-miss-her/</guid>
      <description>Today is my husband&amp;rsquo;s grandma&amp;rsquo;s birthday. Sadly, she isn&amp;rsquo;t here to celebrate with us as the Lord took her home this past February.
I think of her often and miss her. She used to love to bump heads with our kids. She&amp;rsquo;d lean forward so their foreheads touched and say, &amp;ldquo;bump.&amp;rdquo; My youngest will do it from time to time with me and every time I think to myself, &amp;ldquo;Grandma would have loved that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And I thought I Had it Bad!</title>
      <link>/posts/and-i-thought-i-had-it-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/and-i-thought-i-had-it-bad/</guid>
      <description>We took the kids to the county fair last week. Being the suburbanites that we are my kids don&amp;rsquo;t get many opportunities to see livestock up close and personal, so we make a point of going every fall to see the cows, ducks, chickens, goats, sheep, and pigs. Since we don&amp;rsquo;t exactly live in the country, it&amp;rsquo;s not quite as big as I&amp;rsquo;m sure some county fairs are, but a fun learning experience none the less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lucky Ones</title>
      <link>/posts/the-lucky-ones/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-lucky-ones/</guid>
      <description>Remember back in high school when you were positive that you were going to stay BFF with your group of girl friends? You were positive you were going to marry your high school sweetheart&amp;hellip; When I was in high school my friends and I dreamed of growing up, getting married, and living in the same neighborhood.
While that dream didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly pan out, our friendship has remained strong. And 5 of the 6 of us actually went on and married our high school boyfriends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not For Those With Weak Stomachs - That apparently includes my youngest</title>
      <link>/posts/not-for-those-with-weak-stomachs-that-apparently-includes-my-youngest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/not-for-those-with-weak-stomachs-that-apparently-includes-my-youngest/</guid>
      <description>**Warning, those of you that did not appreciate my poop post last week, may not enjoy this one either. Sorry for the graphic footage. My past week has truly illustrated the less glamorous side of motherhood. **
Our trip to Steelers training camp last week was one of the most eventful family car trips we&amp;rsquo;ve had in a long while. It was supposed to take 4 hrs to get to Latrobe, instead 6 hrs after we left we finally pulled into our camping space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 80s Cabbage Patch Doll</title>
      <link>/posts/the-80s-cabbage-patch-doll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-80s-cabbage-patch-doll/</guid>
      <description>My 2 year old has recently taken quite an interest in my old cabbage patch dolls. I gotta say it warms my heart to see her carrying around my old dolls, tucking them in with their blankets, putting a pillow under their heads. It&amp;rsquo;s quite cute to watch.
The other day when she handed &amp;ldquo;baby doll&amp;rdquo; to me because she was &amp;ldquo;sick&amp;rdquo; I took a good look at my old doll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talkin bout the REAL thing!</title>
      <link>/posts/talkin-bout-the-real-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/talkin-bout-the-real-thing/</guid>
      <description>Some may call it a sickness.
Others may think of me more as a loyalist.
It all stems back to an experience I had as a middle schooler.
Who knew that a trip to the grocery store could have such a lasting impact on a girl?
I was shopping with my mom one day when I was an early teen and they were conducting a blind taste test for Coke and Pepsi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Bench Warming Days</title>
      <link>/posts/my-bench-warming-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 04:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-bench-warming-days/</guid>
      <description>I was not an athlete growing up. I quit softball half way through my first season when I was 8 telling my dad, &amp;ldquo;I hate it. You get all sweaty and dirty and stuff!&amp;rdquo; (The fact that I had gotten hit in the face twice with a softball didn&amp;rsquo;t help either).

In eighth grade I found myself at a new school and decided to play lacrosse. My friends were all playing and it seemed like fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He&#39;s Got My Eyes</title>
      <link>/posts/hes-got-my-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hes-got-my-eyes/</guid>
      <description>Since the day he was born, people have been telling me that my son looks like his Daddy. He&amp;rsquo;s been referred to as Scott 2.0 and Mini-Me. I don&amp;rsquo;t argue that there is no debating who his Daddy is, but I will say that he&amp;rsquo;s got my eyes.
Make that eye.
For photography.
Check out these pictures I took of my parents when I was in elementary school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Princess For A Day</title>
      <link>/posts/princess-for-a-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 20:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/princess-for-a-day/</guid>
      <description>This week I celebrated my birthday. As I mentioned yesterday, I love birthdays. Even though I am a &amp;quot;grown up&amp;quot; now and I am not supposed to care about my birthday, I do. A lot. I don&amp;rsquo;t just look forward to it. I count down the weeks and days until it arrives. When I was a kid I used to have my parents wake me up to say Happy Birthday at the exact minute I was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Shortest Pregnancy Yet</title>
      <link>/posts/my-shortest-pregnancy-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-shortest-pregnancy-yet/</guid>
      <description>Time for another Sincerley Fro&#39; Me To You Post. Since my baby turns one this month, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share a pregnancy anecdote with you.
In January of last year my good friend told me she was pregnant with her third child. Her oldest son is 10 months younger than my son, and the two of them are good buddies. Her second son is 4 months younger than my middle child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Not To Wear</title>
      <link>/posts/what-not-to-wear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/what-not-to-wear/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Thursday again, which means I am once again using pictures from my past as blodding fodder for today.
[] (https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/07/spring-97-21.jpg)
Here is a picture of my hubby and I in the spring of 1997 at an All Night Bowling event for my youth group. Please take note of the shirt I am wearing.
Two and a half years later here we are in October of 1999 at a College Football game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Faithful</title>
      <link>/posts/old-faithful/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/old-faithful/</guid>
      <description>Its Thursday again and time for me to go into that box in the closet under the stairs and find another picture that didn&amp;rsquo;t make it into a photo album. I found a classic that is truly timely. This is a picture of me opening gifts on my 13th birthday (I think, might be 12). Can&amp;rsquo;t tell what I am unwrapping, but my brother behind me is definitely interested. Like my dangling shell earrings?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rained Out</title>
      <link>/posts/rained-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rained-out/</guid>
      <description>My Sincerely Fro Me to You post this week doesn&amp;rsquo;t go back quite as far as my others&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s actually not even a month old. We went on multi family camping trip. There were 8 kids 4 and under between the 3 families. Friday night we had a blast. The kids enjoyed playing with tent poles in the dirt while we set up camp. Then they went looking for sticks to roast their marshmallows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daddy&#39;s Football Fan</title>
      <link>/posts/daddys-football-fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/daddys-football-fan/</guid>
      <description>For as long as I can remember my Dad and I have bonded over sports. While most kids were getting quizzed on states and capitals, we&amp;rsquo;d play a game where he&amp;rsquo;d say a city and I&amp;rsquo;d have to name the baseball and or football team from that city. I loved this game! As evidenced here, he raised me as a Steelers fan since I was an infant. When I moved to MD he would tape the games not televised here and mail them to me so my husband and I could watch them mid week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Fall into Infamy</title>
      <link>/posts/my-fall-into-infamy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-fall-into-infamy/</guid>
      <description>Have you or someone you know ever gone on a short term missions trip with the desire to make a difference in the world at large? Not sure exactly what you can do but hoping that the Lord will use you to help however He can?
Well, when I was 15 years old I went on a 2 week missions trip with MTW to Mexico City, Mexico. We were there to help with building a church addition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My longest 15 minutes</title>
      <link>/posts/my-longest-15-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-longest-15-minutes/</guid>
      <description>4 years ago today my sister in law got married. My son was exactly one month old. I went dress shopping so I could find something to hide the 50 pounds of baby fat I gained. Hard to find a dress flattering enough to do that, but somehow I managed to find one that I was happy with. [] (https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/05/the-dress-2.jpg)
Until I got to the church.
I was a new mom and new at the whole nursing thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes Practice Doesn&#39;t Make Perfect</title>
      <link>/posts/sometimes-practice-doesnt-make-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2008 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sometimes-practice-doesnt-make-perfect/</guid>
      <description>Looking at this picture one would assume I was preparing to dive into the swimming pool. Don&amp;rsquo;t be fooled. Despite being on the swim team for 5 summers and having literally every adult I knew work with me one on one, I never learned to dive. This is me looking the part before I belly flopped into the swimming pool.
Starting in about 3rd grade and going through the end of middle school, I spent every summer on the swim team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Were the Cool Ones!</title>
      <link>/posts/we-were-the-cool-ones/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/we-were-the-cool-ones/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned last Thursday, I attended a small Christian High School with only 44 students in my graduating class. The school was small enough that you could play a Varsity sport without actually being good at the sport (granted I sat the bench, but still I earned a letter warming that bench) and the majority of the school was in the marching band. Seriously, you were cool if you were in the marching band.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Congenial??????</title>
      <link>/posts/most-congenial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/most-congenial/</guid>
      <description>We are THAT family is hosting a blog carnival which lets us share some flashback pictures and anecdotes. I thought I would use this as an excuse to pull one of my countless unphotogenic pictures from the archives. Maybe they can finally be put to good use.
My husband and I are high school sweethearts. We went to a small Christian school with only 44 students in our graduating class. Because our last names were on opposite ends of the alphabet we never had home room together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
