<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Darndest Things on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/darndest-things/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Darndest Things on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 12:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/darndest-things/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>His Little Friend the Bee</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/his-little-friend-the-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/his-little-friend-the-bee/</guid>
      <description>While picnicking at the orchard last weekend, a bee made his way to our 4 year olds apple. As it buzzed around and lingered around his hands, Scott thought that it might freak him out so he started to swat it away.
“No Daddy!” our 4 year old protested, “he’s trying to become my friend!”

That’s one we hadn’t heard before…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh This Boy!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/oh-this-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 04:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/oh-this-boy/</guid>
      <description>It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t shock me, but yet it does. How completely DIFFERENT each of my children are. Their personalities are so unique, it truly amazes me.
Take my youngest.
Oh my goodness&amp;hellip; he is such a goof ball, and a FLIRT, but I&amp;rsquo;ll save that for another post&amp;hellip;
Here the kids are in Boston.
&amp;ldquo;Kids, get together so mom can get a picture of the four of you by the fountains.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Words</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-words/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, the kids spent a long weekend at my parents while Scott and I enjoyed St Louis. While they were there, my parents took the kids to a friends farm. The kids had a blast. Seriously, a day doesn’t go by that they don’t mention the horses or the chickens or the barn cats. They even got to ride on the horses. Right up there with all those memory making experiences, was another new life experience for my 4 year old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Class Clown</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-class-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 05:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-class-clown/</guid>
      <description>It seems to be that when you have more than one child… their differences sometimes seem to shine out, and they can kind of fall into different roles. The peacemaker, the organizer…. not that I am advocating type casting your children or anything. I know they can all play different roles at different times.
However, when I asked the kids to pose for a picture at the strawberry patch the other day, my youngest displayed his true colors…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deja Vu</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/deja-vu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/deja-vu/</guid>
      <description>My kids have gotten the Minecraft bug. Started first with my oldest son. He shared the obsession with my 6 year old daughter… and then even my child who doesn’t really like to play games, joined in the fight against zombies. Yesterday they finally figured out how to do multi player, which means they can all play at the same time on various different wireless devices in the same world. Giggles could be heard as they found each other walking around in their worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ode to 3</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ode-to-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ode-to-3/</guid>
      <description>I love the age of 3. I really feel like the personality of your child fully starts to emerge at 3. And 3 year olds are funny. I love their sense of humor and logic and cute little mispronounciations. And they start to pretend. 3 is really fabulous in my humble opinion and I am most def going to mourn the passage of time when I no longer have a 3 year old in the house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Stories</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/animal-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/animal-stories/</guid>
      <description>My 5 year old decided she wanted to write a book yesterday. She wanted it to be a collection of stories about animals. So, she asked if I would write what she said up on our dry erase board so that she could copy them into her book. Here is what she said:

I have to wonder how many different ways a cat licks. They all look the same to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love and Marriage</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/love-and-marriage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/love-and-marriage/</guid>
      <description>I remember when my son was in kindergarten he came home and told me he asked a girl in his class to marry him. “What did she say?” I responded. “No. So I told her,why don’t we wait till we are older to decide.” I cautioned him that should he ever want to propose again, he should talk to us first and then talk to the girls parents first.
I remember this so vividly b/c I knew, I knew there would come a day when he would balk at such a discussion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tee Shirt Love</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tee-shirt-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tee-shirt-love/</guid>
      <description>Scott has been a huge help and support to me this week… taking time off of work so I can rest up (apparently surgery takes more out of you, then you anticipate)… driving the kids to their activities, helping with school, and meals and cleaning up… So, today, I thought I’d show my appreciation and wear my “My Husband Rocks” tee shirt. My 7 year old looked at my shirt, read it aloud and said, “So, why did you wear that today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And I am Sure Momma’s Everywhere Can Relate…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-i-am-sure-mommas-everywhere-can-relate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-i-am-sure-mommas-everywhere-can-relate/</guid>
      <description>This afternoon I was finishing up in the shower, when my youngest walked into the bathroom. I told him, “Hold on bud, Momma’ just needs a minute. Can you give me some privacy?”
His response?
No Mommy. I can’t. I can’t find your pivacy. Neither can I…. going on 9 years now since I lost it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My little circus clown</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-little-circus-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-little-circus-clown/</guid>
      <description>The youngest circus member is 2 and a half now. (HOW CAN THAT BE?) And I have to tell you he makes me laugh. EVERY.SINGLE.DAY with the cute little things he says, the WAY he says them and those precious little facial expressions. He totally has my heart. 
He still LOVES choo-choos. Plays with them every day. He has also recently started enjoying Sesame Street…particularly Elmo (who he affectionately calls Emo) (like Nemo only no N) He loves to run around the circle on our main level… many, many times a day he will run laps around that circle then come to me and say “faster and faster?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Needs a Bed?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-needs-a-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-needs-a-bed/</guid>
      <description>I’ve written before about the crazy places and positions I’ve found my kids sleeping in. It appears child number 4 is no exception to the random sleeping locations of the circus crew.
Last night, when I went upstairs for bed, I found him asleep in his door way like this.

Today at nap time, I again went up the stairs to find him out of his room. 
It appears he’s taken a preference for sleeping in the hallway/landing area of our home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Smile to Start this Rainy Monday morning..</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-smile-to-start-this-rainy-monday-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 05:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-smile-to-start-this-rainy-monday-morning/</guid>
      <description>Heard round the circus this past week…
From my 4 year old:
“Your right hand can’t know what your left hand is doing…unless your giving a hug, then it’s ok.”

Again from my 4 year old:
After pouring peroxide on her cut, she looked up at me with tears in her eyes and said, “Mom, that burns like Sprite!” (soooo hard not to laugh while she was obviously in pain)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number 1 Sign Your Family Might Be a Little Obsessed with Football…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/number-1-sign-your-family-might-be-a-little-obsessed-with-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/number-1-sign-your-family-might-be-a-little-obsessed-with-football/</guid>
      <description>Since it was the first day of spring this week, I decided it might be time to take down the Valentine’s wreath from my door and switch it for my Easter one. Today I thought I’d take it a step further and even pull out my spring/Easter/”leave up till I pull out the red/white/blue decorations for summer around Memorial day” decorations…as I did the girls were ooing and aahing over the little eggs, flowers, chicks and lambs…Then my 6 year old daughter saw the bunny my mother in law had given me a few years ago and said, _“Awh look at the bunny and it’s even holding a football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She said…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/she-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/she-said/</guid>
      <description>I think 4 is a great age for a lot of reasons… one of which is the funny little things 4 year olds say…

Today we were walking to the van and she was carrying her coat, Kit, and her baby. I said, “If you wear your coat you’ll have more hands.” to which she said, “No, Mom, I’ll still only have 2 hands.” Last week before she went into her gymnastics class I told her to work hard and have fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-R-O-U-B-L-E</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t-r-o-u-b-l-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 03:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/t-r-o-u-b-l-e/</guid>
      <description>This afternoon my smiley, mild mannered, easy going baby suddenly channeled his inner Dennis the Menace and went all toddler boy on me for 30 minutes. First I looked over and found him standing on his tool bench (oops look who forgot to put away the advent calendar with her Christmas decorations)

I got him down and shortly after realized things had been mighty quiet for awhile and went searching for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Girl Can Dream</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-girl-can-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 02:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-girl-can-dream/</guid>
      <description>When talking to my oldest daughter about things to look forward to in 2012, I mentioned to her that the Summer Olympics were going to happen in 2012.
“Oh,” she exclaimed, “I’ll be 6, can I be in the Olympics?”
I told her that when she was 6 she can try out for the gymnastics team at her gym, but she has to be 16 to try out for the Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Little Optimist</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-little-optimist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-little-optimist/</guid>
      <description>My four year old asked for a drink the other day. I always pour the kids small amounts since we have a propensity to spill things round the circus. When I handed her the glass she said to me, “Now Mom, that is what I call HALF FULL!” I couldn’t help but chuckle, guess we know how she sees the world. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hmmm… Notice Something Missing Here?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hmmm-notice-something-missing-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hmmm-notice-something-missing-here/</guid>
      <description>As my 4 yr old sat coloring in the waiting room this afternoon the mom beside me commented on her neat job of staying in the lines. Then we both did a double take and looked over at each other. 
Don’t  mind the fact that the dress is green and should “really” be yellow… I love the fact that my girl goes against the flow and colors it how she wants… sure give Belle purple hair and a green dress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Wants Mom’s Dead Flowers?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-wants-moms-dead-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-wants-moms-dead-flowers/</guid>
      <description>On the wall in my bedroom, tucked away in the corner on my side of the bed is a shadow box in which I pressed some dried flowers from my wedding bouquet. I’ll confess I don’t look at it often, but when I do I smile and remember that special day.
My children, however, don’t share my sentimentality.
The other day my 5 yr old and I were sitting on my bed and she said, “Mom, why do you have those old dead flowers hanging on your wall?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back Seat Driving</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/back-seat-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/back-seat-driving/</guid>
      <description>The other day I was driving my oldest two children home when they suggested I text their Nana to see if the younger two were asleep so we’d know if we needed to enter in the backdoor.
I told them I couldn’t text while driving, but maybe if I got a red light I could send her a quick txt. (I know, I know….)
Well the light was green and as we got rather close to our street my 5 yr old daughter says, “Mom, you gotta send the text!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life With 2</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-with-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-with-2/</guid>
      <description>Now that my oldest 2 are at their tutorial two days a week, I find myself with just 2 children at home on those mornings. It is a truly odd feeling and a dynamic I am not yet used to. Though I am sure it is nothing compared to the strangeness I’ll feel next year when I am left with only my lil man two days a week. I am hoping to use this time to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circus Family Sayings</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/circus-family-sayings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/circus-family-sayings/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I have a few sayings that we use often with the kids.
Life is not Fair
Life isn’t Always About You
You Can’t Cry to Get What You Want
and….
Never Trust a Bad Guy
1 -3 are pretty self explanatory… in a family of 6, you learn quickly that your not going to get what you want when you want it, you gotta wait, and that’s just the way it goes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Insignificant?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/feeling-insignificant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/feeling-insignificant/</guid>
      <description>Last week after telling my kids the Bible story of baby Moses, I decided to offer a little application for them. I pointed out how neat it was that God took care of Moses as a baby by allowing the princess to find him. I even told how amazing it was that his own mother was allowed to take care of him before he went to live at the palace. After discussing how Moses grew up in the Egyptian palace, I pointed out how God used that later in his life when Moses led the Israelites out of captivity in Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Sufficient…to a point…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/self-sufficientto-a-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/self-sufficientto-a-point/</guid>
      <description>One of the many reasons why life is easier this time around is that my older three kids are much more self sufficient.
When we need to head out the door, I can instruct the kids to get their shoes on, go to the van and buckle up. A few minutes later the baby and I arrive at the van. I buckle him in, do a quick seatbelt check on the big kids and we hit the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preserving the Memories…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/preserving-the-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/preserving-the-memories/</guid>
      <description>I think there is something about the age of 3 that makes kids say some of the cutest things. Lately, our 3 year old has been cracking me up and I have to write them down lest I forget…
 Last week Scott was playing catch with our oldest son.&amp;amp;#160; She of course wanted a turn as well.&amp;amp;#160; Scott said sure and then she said, _**“Dad, can I get closer to you when I throw the ball, since I am a girl?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ya Never Know What They’ll Say Next</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ya-never-know-what-theyll-say-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ya-never-know-what-theyll-say-next/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday my girls had me in stitches with the things they were saying. I had to go write them down so I wouldn’t forget.
 Me:&amp;amp;#160; After you eat we are going to go run some errands 3 year old:&amp;amp;#160; Erin, whose Erin? Me:&amp;amp;#160; no, we are going to go to some stores 3 year old:&amp;amp;#160; Well, can Erin stay with us while you go to the store? My 3 yr old came running to me crying over a boo boo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wasted Cookies?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wasted-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wasted-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Nothing like the holidays, to bring on some humor from the lil ones. Here’s a few I want to record for posterity.
When Scott was talking to my 4 yr old about what she wanted to get me for Christmas, she told him she wanted to get Mommy flowers and she was going to be nice. To clarify Scott asked, “So your going to be nice as a Christmas gift for Mommy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>While You Were Sleeping</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/while-you-were-sleeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/while-you-were-sleeping/</guid>
      <description>I found my 3 yr old like this during nap time today… it seems baby doll has been displaced from her bed. 
It reminded me of a picture I snapped a few weeks ago of both on my girls as we found them when we peeked in on them before going to bed.

YES… they are both sleeping INSIDE of their drawers!
And since I am sharing sleeping pics, why not share a few of my lil man snoozing as well?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apparently he isn’t the most famous of all</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/apparently-he-isnt-the-most-famous-of-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/apparently-he-isnt-the-most-famous-of-all/</guid>
      <description>I got a funny e-mail from my mom this morning. She told me to set the DVR to record Rudolph tonight b/c apparently my 3 yr old needed a refresher in holiday pop culture. According to my mom…
“We were walking in the mall on Black Friday. We went to the Build a Bear shop which had been transformed into Santa&amp;rsquo;s Workshop for Christmas. They had stuffed snowmen and deer and Santa bears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Don’t Wanna Miss a Thing</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-dont-wanna-miss-a-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-dont-wanna-miss-a-thing/</guid>
      <description>So many things I want to remember from this stage of life…the sweet way she mispronounces her baby brother’s name…. and the way his face lights up with recognition when I walk in a room…the raspy way she belts out songs in the back seat, and the sweet way he kisses his sisters goodbye before heading into school… I know I think I’ll never forget and yet those who’ve gone before me say I will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Mouth of Babes</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/out-of-the-mouth-of-babes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/out-of-the-mouth-of-babes/</guid>
      <description>It’s been one of those days… please tell me you know the ones…took the circus crew to the pediatrician’s for my 3 yr old’s check up. One would have thought by the amount of shrieking that took place in the hall that we were attempting to tie her down and give her 30 shots, when really we just wanted her to take her sandals off and stand on the scale. From that humbling spectacle we were off to the grocery store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Careful How You Advertise</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/careful-how-you-advertise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/careful-how-you-advertise/</guid>
      <description>Last week at church they gave an advertisement for our upcoming Vacation Bible School. I was a few minutes late so I missed the announcement. When I sat down my son said, “I do not want to go to VBS this year!” I couldn’t figure out why. My son said, “It’s not going to be anything like last year… it’s an adventure camp.” Figuring he must have been intimidated by the adjectives they used to describe it, I told him it is going to be really fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kegs at Church?!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kegs-at-church/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kegs-at-church/</guid>
      <description>Last week my son was reading a list of words in one of his readers. One of the words was “keg.” He asked what a keg was. I was trying to figure out the best way to describe it and so I said it was like a a big container with a spout that you could get a drink from. “Oh,” he said with a look of recognition. “I know what your talking about, like what we get lemonade from at church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Quite Big Enough for The Job</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-quite-big-enough-for-the-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-quite-big-enough-for-the-job/</guid>
      <description>As we were walking out the door this morning, I heard my daughter exclaim, “Oh it’s raining, better grab my umbrella!” 
I wondered what she was talking about since we don’t have any umbrellas in our house. (Who needs one more thing to juggle? We just get wet, it’s the circus way)! Then I saw her walking to the car with her Little People umbrella over her head. She then carried this umbrella over her head into and out of the grocery store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filing this one under &#39;Conversations I never expected to have with my little girl&#39;</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/filing-this-one-under-conversations-i-never-expected-to-have-with-mylittle-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/filing-this-one-under-conversations-i-never-expected-to-have-with-mylittle-girl/</guid>
      <description>I was cleaning the bathroom yesterday (I know, miracles never cease, huh?) when my 2 and 1/2 year old daughter came in to use the potty. “Go ahead,” I told her. (Have I mentioned that I LOVE the fact that all 3 kids can use their potty on their own, ah sweet bliss—for 11 more weeks!) Well I turned from scrubbing the tub to see her standing beside the potty. “I want to go this way!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Crew Visits the OB</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-crew-visits-the-ob/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-crew-visits-the-ob/</guid>
      <description>I typically schedule my OB appointments for first thing in the morning so that the kids can stay home with Scott. This time however, his work schedule didn’t cooperate, so I brought the circus crew with me for my check up. I knew at 28 weeks they wouldn’t be doing an exam, so I felt comfortable having them tag along. I did come prepared with coloring books, crayons, snacks, and even lollipops which I saved for the very end if they were “super stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Many Outfits Can One Girl Wear?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-many-outfits-can-one-girl-wear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-many-outfits-can-one-girl-wear/</guid>
      <description>My girls, especially my youngest, love to change clothes. And often. It borders on ridiculous. I knew if I didn’t document it, no one would believe me.
So, take a look at Thursdays attire here at the circus. (I will mention that we never left the house today). The day started at 7:00am, didn’t have the camera ready then, but here she is at 8:30am. (wearing the clothes she wore last night plus a coat)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Say…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kids-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kids-say/</guid>
      <description>Mary has created a carnival to help us record those funny and precious things our kids say, so we’ll remember them in years to come. Some weeks I’ve got nothing…this week, however, my kids gave me a few gems I don’t want to forget.  Last week my five year old and I were working on handwriting.&amp;amp;#160; Handwriting is often a battlefield for us.&amp;amp;#160; This particular day I knew he wasn’t giving it his all and I wasn’t seeing his best work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Thing I’ve Got Thick Skin!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/good-thing-ive-got-thick-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/good-thing-ive-got-thick-skin/</guid>
      <description>Last night I was holding my girls on my lap when they began to play a little rough. I reminded them that there was a baby in my belly and they needed to be gentle. My 4 yr old then said, “Mom, I don’t think you really have a baby in your belly. I think it is just food.”
I assured her there really is a baby in there and reminded her that she’s seen the baby’s picture and heard the heart beat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun with Mammals</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fun-with-mammals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fun-with-mammals/</guid>
      <description>In Science we’ve been talking about what God created on each of the 6 days of creation. Currently we’re on day 6 and discussing the creatures that walked on the land. While the kids were playing on Friday, they got the idea to group their stuffed animals according to classification. Of course they didn’t use these exact words. But, they made a pile of non mammals and another of mammals and then called me in to take a look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All About Me</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/all-about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/all-about-me/</guid>
      <description>One thing my husband and I try to stress to our kids is that life is not all about them. We love them dearly, and pour much of our time, love, energy and attention out onto them. But, because we love them, we also try to teach them that life does not revolve around them.
We are a family of 5 soon to be 6. So, in a lot of ways this is a lesson that is taught early on out of practicality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing out the Mistletoe</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/testing-out-the-mistletoe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2009 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/testing-out-the-mistletoe/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite things we did this Christmas was take the kids shopping for each other and for us. It is heartwarming to see them get so excited about giving. I also loved seeing what they picked out for others. My son is an excellent gift giver. He is very thoughtful and thinks very hard about finding a gift the person will truly like. I just had to share the story Scott told me about taking him shopping for my gift.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking At it From Their Perspective</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/looking-at-it-from-their-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 03:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/looking-at-it-from-their-perspective/</guid>
      <description>Last week we were at my parents house and my son came into the kitchen quite exasperated from going to the bathroom.
“Mom,” he complained, “can you puh-leeze tell the girls to put the seat up when they are done going potty? They keep leaving it down!”
I had to laugh. Women have complained for years about men leaving the seat up, but never, never have I heard a complaint about us leaving it down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Me Humble</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-me-humble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2009 16:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-me-humble/</guid>
      <description>I was feeling pretty good about myself this week. Got a little boost of energy with week 12 and began to tame this household which I had slacked off on over the first trimester. Finally, I can leave the guest bedroom door open as well as the master bed room. I even cleaned out the van which had reached its height of total messiness, threw away all that trash crammed in around the car seats and brought in the plethora of coats and shoes which were strewn all over the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Boot Camp</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/baby-boot-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2009 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/baby-boot-camp/</guid>
      <description>It appears my oldest daughter is trying to prepare me for life with 4 kids. She has taken on the job of mothering her baby doll “baby Eli” literally 24-7. When we sit down to eat, she makes sure Eli has his bib on and a special seat at the table. We now set our table for 7 (b/c our youngest has to include her baby Eli too). 
When she’s getting ready for bed, baby Eli also gets tucked into his bed, with his own baby and she is always certain to read him his special Bible story as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Saw the Sign</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-saw-the-sign/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-saw-the-sign/</guid>
      <description>At dinner last night I was telling Scott how cute it is to watch our 3 yr old in gymnastics. Every now and then she’ll look at the observation window, get a big grin and wave to me. Sometimes she’ll even give me a thumbs up sign. At which point she chimed in and said,
“Yea, this means good.”

“And this means Ravens”

What can I say? That’s my girl!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Very Realistic Fan</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-very-realistic-fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-very-realistic-fan/</guid>
      <description>Our son is a huge baseball fan. His team of choice is the Baltimore Orioles. As much as he likes the Orioles, he also recognizes that they don’t exactly have a winning record…
 Last week we were getting ready for soccer practice when he informed me that he didn’t feel like going to practice. Me:&amp;amp;#160; “Well you need to practice, it helps you to get better.” Son: “ But Mom, I’m already really good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gone Gold Fishing</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gone-gold-fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gone-gold-fishing/</guid>
      <description>One Sunday I picked my 2 year old son up from Sunday School and found goldfish in his bin. He had saved some of his snack to share with Mommy and Daddy. My jaw hit the floor. His thoughtfulness both touched and humbled me.
Our church has a fellowship time between services in which you can have some cookies, popcorn, coffee, and lemonade. Once my son was old enough to attend church with us after Sunday School, he got to come join us for the fellowship time as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That’s What She Said</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thats-what-she-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thats-what-she-said/</guid>
      <description>**** Updated with new quote from this very afternoon****
One of my favorite parts of motherhood, is watching my children grow and develop. As they get older it is so much fun to see their individuality and personality emerge. This week marked some big milestones in the circus family life. On Sunday, for the first time in 5 years, I didn’t drop any of my children off in the nursery for church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Misunderstood Cow</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-misunderstood-cow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 17:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-misunderstood-cow/</guid>
      <description>My children have been inundated with Chick-Fil-A from birth. The first thing I ate after my daughter’s delivery was a CFA sandwich. I have scrapbook pages in each of my daughter’s first year scrapbooks, dedicated to their first Kids Meals at Chick-Fil-A. The first logo/graphic my son recognized was for Chick-Fil-A. Anytime he saw a cursive C when he was a toddler, he thought it was the word Chick-Fil-A. They’ve known and loved the Chick-Fil-A cow since they were babies and we’ve even dressed like one for the past 5 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Lesson in Flexibility</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-lesson-in-flexibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 20:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-lesson-in-flexibility/</guid>
      <description>I love our pediatric dentist office, for many reasons….the play gym in the waiting room, the sun glasses for the kids to wear while the lights shine in their eyes, the cool prizes the kids get to pick out, the pac man games they play between the cleaning and the dentist, but mostly for the people.
Without the kind and patient hygienists and dentists, the games and toys really wouldn’t matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The President’s Car</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-presidents-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-presidents-car/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I were walking around downtown Annapolis last week when we spotted this car. My son said, “Hey, I bet that’s Barack Obama’s car!” 
You know, because naturally the president of the United States would drive a car that looked like an American flag.
I am sure the people at Beltway Brokerage.com would be so happy to know that their car gets such high billing. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Make Assumptions about Sunday School</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-make-assumptions-about-sunday-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 19:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-make-assumptions-about-sunday-school/</guid>
      <description>While walking to the car after church on Sunday, my son proudly showed me his Sunday School papers.  Upon seeing this picture, I assumed what his lesson was about that morning and decided to play a little game with him. “I bet I can guess who this picture is of,” I say jokingly. Being confident in who it is, I decide to joke around with him and intentionally say wrong answers such as “Andrew, James, or Paul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Propaganda</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/propaganda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/propaganda/</guid>
      <description>The other day the kids and I were hanging around the house cleaning the house like crazy and listening to music. “The Sharing Song” by Jack Johnson came on and he sang, “It’s always more fun to share with everyone.” My three year old got a funny look on her face and exclaimed, “Hey, he said it’s more fun to share! It is NOT more fun to share!” The way she said it and the look on her face was if she was saying, W_hat is this propaganda your spewing at me mom?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Hard (or hardly working)</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/working-hard-or-hardly-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/working-hard-or-hardly-working/</guid>
      <description>My son is quite the little entrepreneur. The other night after dinner my husband was reading the girls a book and I sat on the couch to read a little myself. I looked over to see what my son was up to and discovered he had put all the dishes in the sink, and was scrubbing the dining room table. He even asked where the sandwich bags where so he could bag up the leftovers and put them in the fridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boat Watching</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/boat-watching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/boat-watching/</guid>
      <description>Living near the Chesapeake Bay affords us many opportunities for boat watching. “What’s that?” “A sailboat.”
“What’s that?” “A motor boat”
“What’s that?” “A kayak.”
Many such conversations have gone on between the kids and I over the years. Now they happily call out the boats they see as we play at the beach or the park nearby. Last week my kids got all excited when they saw a cruise ship sailing by our park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because I’m More Forgetful Than I’d Like to Admit</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/because-im-more-forgetful-than-id-like-to-admit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/because-im-more-forgetful-than-id-like-to-admit/</guid>
      <description>The one piece of parenting advice I wish I had adhered to better is to “write down those cute things your kids say b/c you will forget.” Me forget? Come on… there’s not way I could forget those cute little things my kids say… I’m super mom.
Yea, I also never thought I’d bring my kids to church with mismatched shoes and no diaper bag…but
5 years and 3 kids later and super mom has left the building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How are You?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-are-you/</guid>
      <description>“How are you?” This simple phrase is uttered countless times a day. Though typically without the asker really wanting or waiting for a reply.
“Hi How are you?”
You say it the grocery store clerk, the man on the sidewalk, the telemarketer…and yet, honestly, how often do you wait or listen to the response?
The expected response is “Good, How are you?”
My kids could have been screaming at the top of their lungs , the dog just pooped on the rug again, and my sink is clogged and over flowing, and yet I smile and answer “Good, how are you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Role That Suits Her Well</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-role-that-suits-her-well/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-role-that-suits-her-well/</guid>
      <description>My kids made an important decision this week. After much deliberation, they’ve finally figured out their Halloween costumes for next fall. And really, not a moment too soon… what with 146 days till Halloween, it’s a good thing we’ve got it settled. My son will be Luke Skywalker (he told me this week that he wished when he was a baby we had name him Luke Skywalker). My 3 year old will be Princess Leia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Says That?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-says-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2009 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/who-says-that/</guid>
      <description>My son has always been a thinker, thinking things through one step ahead and drawing some unpredictable conclusions. The following conversation took place last week between my son and his Daddy.
Son: Dad, I really want to go fishing. Dad: Oh, that does sound like fun. The bummer though is that it&amp;rsquo;s not fishing season so we can&amp;rsquo;t go fishing. Son: Why is it not fishing season? Dad: Well, if we fished all the time we would run out of fish to fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Missing Samaritan</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-missing-samaritan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-missing-samaritan/</guid>
      <description>God Bless Sunday School teachers…especially the teachers of those dear two and three year olds. How they keep those squiggling, squirming little bodies still on those carpet squares to hear the whole lesson is beyond me.
Perhaps, it’s occasionally beyond them too. Seems they don’t always get quite the whole lesson.
At lunch today I was asking my three year old what she learned about in Sunday School. I was so excited to get an answer beyond the typical, “God” or “Jesus”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Many Ladies</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/too-many-ladies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/too-many-ladies/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago my son came up to me and asked if Prince Charming was always the prince. I told him yes. His eyes got really big and he said, “Wow, that is a lot of princesses to take care of.” Apparently, he wasn’t done pondering the subject, because later while holding up his sister’s sippy cup, he remarked, “That’s too many princesses for one guy… you’re only supposed to have one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying to Bottle It Up and Save it For Later</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/trying-to-bottle-it-up-and-save-it-for-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/trying-to-bottle-it-up-and-save-it-for-later/</guid>
      <description>These days pass quickly as I’ve been warned and I stink at keeping a journal, so lately I’ve been quickly opening up my e-mail and trying to jot down the things the kids do and say that I want to remember and then saving it in my drafts folder. Here are some recent memories recorded so I don’t forget…
 son: AWWWWWWWWWWWAAAHHHHHHHH Scott: What is wrong? son: My guitar.&amp;amp;#160; I was playing the guitar and she pulled my pretend guitar plug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All About Me: According to My Son</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/all-about-me-according-to-my-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/all-about-me-according-to-my-son/</guid>
      <description>I saw this little questionnaire on face book this week and the responses from my friend’s daughters had me laughing out loud. So, I asked my son this list of 25 questions about his mom and here is what he said… 
  What is something mom always says to you? Son: no response (nice to know I leave such an impression)
  What makes mom happy? Son: obeying mom and loving mom</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be Careful of Mr. Black</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/be-careful-of-mr.-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2009 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/be-careful-of-mr.-black/</guid>
      <description>Today a dental hygienist visited my son’s class at preschool. In the car he told me we needed to get him some dental cloth. “Floss?” I asked. “Yes,” he told me, “We gotta get rid of Mr. Black.”
pause
My son then commented, “I have no idea who Mr. Black is but we gotta get rid of him.”
I suggested maybe he was a cavity.
“Yea or dead food.” he replied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bit Mixed Up</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-bit-mixed-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-bit-mixed-up/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever been singing along to a song in front of your friends when you learn that the lyrics you thought you knew weren’t quite right?
I can remember in high school singing along to Amy Grant’s “Baby Baby” and when she says, “Baby Baby, I’m taken with the notion to love you with the sweetest of devotion” I instead belted out “love you with the sweetest talk of ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Only We Were Joking</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/if-only-we-were-joking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/if-only-we-were-joking/</guid>
      <description>Scott asked the kids their thoughts on the new stimulus bill that’s been passed. Let’s just say they are a little less than enthused. We had no idea this conversation would end in tears.
Have no fear. Scott consoled him right after we fade to black. He really does &amp;ldquo;get it&amp;rdquo; but there is no reason to let him continue to worry about something he can&amp;rsquo;t yet control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do We Have No Decency?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/do-we-have-no-decency/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/do-we-have-no-decency/</guid>
      <description>Last week the girls and I were at the auto mechanic waiting to get the oil changed in our minivan. We were sitting nicely in the the waiting room reading books and enjoying some goldfish when suddenly I look over at the older one and shockingly find her standing in the waiting room (filled with people) with her pants and underwear down to her ankles. I quickly pull them up and ask her why she did this and she explains that her “butt hurts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eggnog Talks Part 1</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/eggnog-talks-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2009 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/eggnog-talks-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Eggnog has always been a special drink at our house. Since our son was just a toddler, he’s enjoyed sipping this treat with his Daddy.
Last winter as Scott and my son were enjoying this holiday treat, Scott told him that eggnog is a talking drink. “You sip it slowly like a dessert and talk about important things,” he instructed him.
From this was born eggnog talks.
The next night my three and half year hold son asked for some eggnog, then looked up at his Daddy and said, “Dad, let’s talk…how was your day?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes Good Questions, Aren’t</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sometimes-good-questions-arent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sometimes-good-questions-arent/</guid>
      <description>My son has always had a very inquisitive nature. When I was pregnant with my third child, he was three. He fully grasped the concept that there was a baby in my belly. But, what he wanted to know was, how the baby was coming out. At first I tried with vague, non specific responses. But they weren’t doing it for him. He kept bringing it up, again and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Through the Eyes of a Child</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/through-the-eyes-of-a-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/through-the-eyes-of-a-child/</guid>
      <description>After dressing the children in their finest, and forcing them to pose for pictures in front of the tree, we went to church this evening for the Christmas Eve services.
When one of our pastors got up to read Scripture, he said he would be reading from John 1. My son leaned over to me and said, &amp;ldquo;Mom, I thought the story was in Luke 2.&amp;quot; This was probably one of my favorite quotes from the evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One&#39;s for You Mom...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-ones-for-you-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-ones-for-you-mom/</guid>
      <description>When I was little if you wanted to make my mom mad, all you had to do was ask her who was visiting when she was cleaning house. Oh how I remember the look she&amp;rsquo;d get on her face when I would say that&amp;hellip;.seems my turn has come&amp;hellip;

After decorating our cookies yesterday, I realized it was time to deep clean my kitchen. Once I scrubbed down the icing covered counter, it only made me realize how scummy the other counters looked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Entrepreneur</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-entrepreneur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 11:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-entrepreneur/</guid>
      <description>I came into the kitchen the other day to find my son lining up cups of water. I asked what he was doing and he informed me he was setting up a &amp;ldquo;Water Stand&amp;rdquo; in our house. I asked how much he was charging for a cup of luke warm tap water.
$14.00, he replied.
Any takers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly Away dear boy Fly Away!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fly-away-dear-boy-fly-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fly-away-dear-boy-fly-away/</guid>
      <description>Who would ever thought soccer cleats could be so cute? When I took my son to get his cleats at the beginning of the season, I thought those cleats were far cuter than any baby bootie I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen. I&amp;rsquo;ve never been into bronzing the baby shoes, but I will be tucking these cleats away in a box to look at years from now when I complain of the big stinky cleats I find sitting in my doorway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons on Anatomy from a Four Year Old</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lessons-on-anatomy-from-a-four-year-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lessons-on-anatomy-from-a-four-year-old/</guid>
      <description>As my kids were getting ready for their bath the other night the following conversation took place.
 Sister: What&amp;rsquo;s that? (she&amp;rsquo;s pointing at his nipple)
Brother: It&amp;rsquo;s the thing you guys (pause) girls have to give babies milk when they don&amp;rsquo;t use bottles.
 I know that I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be, but I am continually amazed by how much the information kids absorb just by watching the world around them, and how much they remember!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Does This Mean We Have a Future Brain Surgeon On Our Hands?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-does-this-mean-we-have-a-future-brain-surgeon-on-our-hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-does-this-mean-we-have-a-future-brain-surgeon-on-our-hands/</guid>
      <description>Today the following conversation took place between me and my 4 year old son as we were driving home from the store.
 Son: Mom, can I see a real brain some day?
Me: You want to see grain?
Son: No a BRAIN
pause (and I had been trying to figure out where to find grain&amp;hellip;if only&amp;hellip;)
Me: I don&amp;rsquo;t think so, that would be pretty tough
Son: Well, if someone died and then we cut their head open, then we could see what their brain looked like</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are we alone on this?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/are-we-alone-on-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/are-we-alone-on-this/</guid>
      <description>My kids have a fascination with poop.
(Have no fear no pictures included in this post)!
Every time we change our baby&amp;rsquo;s diaper, the older two want to know if it is poop and if it is they want to see it.
As odd as it is to us, it seems like an easy and harmless enough wish to comply with that my husband and I know &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t throw the diaper into the pail until you&amp;rsquo;ve held it up for all to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scary Monster!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-scary-monster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-scary-monster/</guid>
      <description>My 2 year old daughter loves Sesame Street.
Except for this guy.

Every time he comes on the screen, she does this.

or this.

The first time he scared her, I came into the room to find her laying face down on the couch crying. I asked her what was wrong and she said, &amp;ldquo;Cookie Monster yelled at me!&amp;rdquo; I think she really thought he was yelling at her when he was screaming for his cookies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Just Heard At My House</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-just-heard-at-my-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-just-heard-at-my-house/</guid>
      <description>Baby: (in high pitched voice) badadadada
4 year old son: I don&amp;rsquo;t know what she just said, but it was cute!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Pathetic</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/looking-pathetic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/looking-pathetic/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t typically attempt this task on my own. Not since baby number 2 arrived anyway. But my husband had to work that day and it had to be done, so the task was left to me. And my three kids.
I pulled into the parking lot of our vet&amp;rsquo;s office, put both girls in the stroller, grabbed the dog leash, and had instructed my son to walk beside the stroller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Taste of &#39;Kid Beer&#39;</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/first-taste-of-kid-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2008 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/first-taste-of-kid-beer/</guid>
      <description>My son was so excited about the favor we brought home from my friend&amp;rsquo;s wedding a few weeks ago. They gave out old fashioned root beer in bottles with a home made label. It was his first soda and he was so excited to drink &amp;ldquo;kid beer&amp;rdquo; as he called it.




I think he liked the idea of it more than the actual taste. He actually drank most of it the next day when it was flat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Super Hero</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-super-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 04:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-super-hero/</guid>
      <description>We had an incident a few weeks ago at the park. One of those, turn your back for one seconds, incidents. The kids were frolicking in the grass and I turned to look at the baby, when I turned back my two year old was gone.
After suffering the sick feeling of panic in my stomach and running around like a crazy mama I heard her crying. She had fallen down during her frolic and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see her in the tall grass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Opportunity to Exercise My Patience</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-opportunity-to-exercise-my-patience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-opportunity-to-exercise-my-patience/</guid>
      <description>My hubby and I had the sad realization the other day that we aren&amp;rsquo;t as good of parents as we thought we were. See our son is 4 years old and we haven&amp;rsquo;t taught him to ride a bike or to swim.
So, we decided it was time to get the boy a bike.
Hubby thought a consignment shop was a good idea, because why spend a butt load of money when you don&amp;rsquo;t have to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost in Translation</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lost-in-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/lost-in-translation/</guid>
      <description>Ever play the game Mad Gab? One team holds up a card with a gibberish phrase and the other team has to translate it. Translating what my two year old says is a lot like playing this game.
Case in point, last week my daughter was teasing my mom. My mom wanted her to call her Grandma and she knew this so she would call her everything but that. As they looked each other in the eye their charade went something like this&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Recent Quotes from Our House</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/most-recent-quotes-from-our-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 20:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/most-recent-quotes-from-our-house/</guid>
      <description>In college I had some friends who had wipe off boards and would write up some funny or amusing phrase they&amp;rsquo;d over hear and it would stay on the &amp;quot;quote board&amp;quot; until the next memorable statement. Anyone else do this?
Well, I guess I am using this blog post as my quote board&amp;hellip; here are a few memorable ones from the past several weeks.
 While drinking some water one hot evening my son said to me, &amp;quot;Mom, soon this is going to be pee!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Quite Have Eyes in the Back of My Head</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-quite-have-eyes-in-the-back-of-my-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-quite-have-eyes-in-the-back-of-my-head/</guid>
      <description>Ya know how they say Mom&amp;rsquo;s have eyes in the back of their head? I&amp;rsquo;m not sure exactly when my extra set will arrive&amp;hellip; do my children have to reach a certain age, or do I need to have a certain number of children? Seems that with a 4 year old, a 2 year old, and an almost 1 year old&amp;hellip; I could really use those extra set of eyes&amp;hellip;NOW!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spiderman Strikes at Nap Time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spiderman-strikes-at-nap-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spiderman-strikes-at-nap-time/</guid>
      <description>Since my son turned 4 I no longer require him to nap every day. But to keep my sanity ensure that he has some down time, I do require him to have a quiet, rest time in his room while his sisters are napping. Most of the time he ends up falling asleep. Other times, he reads or plays with toys on his bed. On Monday afternoon he found a red pen in his room during this time and decided to transform himself into Spider Man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clearly I Don&#39;t Wear Enough Bling</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/clearly-i-dont-wear-enough-bling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/clearly-i-dont-wear-enough-bling/</guid>
      <description>I was shopping at BJ&amp;rsquo;s the other day with the kids when we passed the jewelry counter.
My son asked, &amp;quot;Why is there jewelry at BJ&amp;rsquo;s?&amp;quot;
I responded, &amp;quot;So people can buy it.&amp;quot;
He then said, &amp;quot;Yea&amp;hellip; I guess if they were getting married and didn&amp;rsquo;t have a ring they could come here.&amp;quot;
Hmmm&amp;hellip;. clearly this Mommy doesn&amp;rsquo;t wear much jewelry, since my son thinks wedding rings are the only kind of jewelry one wears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We made it till the third...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-made-it-till-the-third/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-made-it-till-the-third/</guid>
      <description>Kids like buttons. At least ours do. Our son was the first addict. We could keep him happy quiet for long periods of time by giving him the TV remote (with the TV off) and letting him just pound away. Him being the first, we were always careful when he got the phone. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want him to call someone unintentionally and have someone listening to uncensored Life at the Circus. He never really called anyone though, because life with one isn&amp;rsquo;t quite a circus, he just hit buttons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch out Tiger!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/watch-out-tiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/watch-out-tiger/</guid>
      <description>My son really took an interest in golfing this weekend while watching my husband follow the U.S. Open. My husband rarely golfs but does have a set of clubs and after very persistent requests, my husband let my son use his clubs in the back yard. He taught him the different types of clubs (drivers, putters, irons) and when they are used. My son had a blast hitting the ball with the putter (which was almost as long as him) in the back yard and then running over to putt it into the pretend hole (between my husband&amp;rsquo;s legs).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come Play With Us</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/come-play-with-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/come-play-with-us/</guid>
      <description>I was cooking dinner last week, when the kids called out from the toy box,
&amp;ldquo;Mom, don&amp;rsquo;t you want to get us out and play with us?&amp;rdquo;
For More Wordless Wednesdays, check out 5 Minutes for Mom.
To learn more about me, check out [my 100th post!] (http://lifeatthecircus.com/2008/06/17/my-100th-post/)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Knack</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-knack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-knack/</guid>
      <description>The other morning I came around the corner to find my 4 year old son unscrewing the screw from the switch plate of our light. He had gotten his chair, pulled it up to the light switch, found the right size Phillips screw driver, and had gotten the screw mostly off. I noticed he had been quiet for awhile when I peeked around the corner to check on him and saw this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Love to Laugh</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-love-to-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-love-to-laugh/</guid>
      <description>I love my son&amp;rsquo;s imagination! He is at age where I wish I could just freeze time. He cracks us with his antics these days. Check out last week&amp;rsquo;s comedy routines.
My son was playing on the deck when I suddenly heard him say, &amp;ldquo;Help Mom, I&amp;rsquo;m stuck.&amp;rdquo; I turned around to see this.

As I got him out of the basketball net, I asked him what on earth he was doing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Electricity, Water or Internet</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-electricity-water-or-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 03:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/no-electricity-water-or-internet/</guid>
      <description>We lost power at about 4pm on Wednesday. Losing power really wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be so bad if it didn’t mean that I had to loose water too. It makes you realize how often you run to the sink to clean up messes the kids leave in their wake. the kids have been handling it really well. I told my son that the electricity was out and about a hour later the following discussion took place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Family Has It&#39;s Black Sheep</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/every-family-has-its-black-sheep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/every-family-has-its-black-sheep/</guid>
      <description>My husband and I were talking in the kitchen when my son popped in and dropped a bomb on us. We appreciate his upfront honesty but we were caught totally off guard.
We&amp;rsquo;re trying hard to take deal with this rationally, but what parents wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be devastated.
It&amp;rsquo;s just that he showed so much promise. His is so smart. We try not to get carried away with his potential but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but to dream about where his future could go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember this...(Daddy sure will)</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/remember-this...daddy-sure-will/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/remember-this...daddy-sure-will/</guid>
      <description>Today my son spontaneously came up to my 2 year old and gave her a kiss. Afterwards the following discussion took place.
Daughter: &amp;ldquo;No kiss, Only Daddy Kiss.&amp;rdquo;
Mommy: &amp;ldquo;But he&amp;rsquo;s your brother and he was being nice.&amp;rdquo;
Daughter: &amp;ldquo;No, only Daddy kiss.&amp;rdquo;
Mommy: &amp;ldquo;So, the only boy that can kiss you is Daddy?&amp;rdquo;
Daughter: &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo;
Daddy was a happy man when I shared this anecdote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everybody Dance Now</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everybody-dance-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/everybody-dance-now/</guid>
      <description>The other day I discovered a way to occupy my kids for a good 15-20 min, which many of you know is an eternity in Mommy time.
Wanna know the secret?
I let them play with my clock radio. I plugged it in and placed it on the floor in the living room. They had a blast taking turns turning it off and on and changing radio stations. It was more fun then Mommy turning on the stereo, because they had control of turning it on and off as well the fun of switching the music from station to station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Say...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kids-say-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kids-say-1/</guid>
      <description>The other day our two year old had a really bad diaper rash. Her poor bottom was BRIGHT RED and she screamed out in pain when we had to change her diaper. My son looked at her bottom and exclaimed, &amp;ldquo;Diaper rash is my favorite color!&amp;rdquo;
That boy makes me laugh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Music Truck</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-music-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-music-truck/</guid>
      <description>My son is very smart (every mother says this about her children so I might as well enjoy my entitlement). He is only 4 but he has always had a knack for asking good questions and is satisfied by only believable answers. We pride ourselves on honesty so that &amp;ldquo;believable answer&amp;rdquo; always contains the truth but not necessarily more truth then is absolutely required. Case in point: For a year we got away with calling a certain, frequent and noticeable neighborhood visitor, &amp;ldquo;the music truck&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Cry Over....</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-cry-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/dont-cry-over/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;.Flushed Poop&amp;hellip;..
Yes, you read that correctly and if bathroom talk/humor is not your thing, then I suggest you skip this post.
The following incident actually occurred in my house today. Sometimes I wonder, &amp;ldquo;What will I write about in my blog today?&amp;rdquo; Or I worry if I will have enough stuff to write about to keep blogging far into the future&amp;hellip; then things like this occur, and I think, &amp;ldquo;Well, that&amp;rsquo;s today&amp;rsquo;s post!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Brown Candy?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/charlie-brown-candy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/charlie-brown-candy/</guid>
      <description>This afternoon my son asked if he could, &amp;ldquo;have some Charlie Brown candy&amp;rdquo;. It took me a few minutes to figure out what he meant.
&amp;ldquo;Peanuts?&amp;rdquo; I asked.
&amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo;
Then I realized, &amp;ldquo;Oh Peppermint Patty?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Yup!&amp;rdquo;
I think I may start calling them that from now on :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be Careful What You Say</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/be-careful-what-you-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/be-careful-what-you-say/</guid>
      <description>I walked in on my son weighing himself in our bathroom today. He said, &amp;ldquo;Woah! I gotta slow down, I am eating too fast!&amp;rdquo; I asked him where he heard that and he said, &amp;ldquo;Daddy, when he saw a 2 and a 0 on the scale he said, &amp;ldquo;Woah, I gotta slow down and stop eating so many cookies.&amp;rdquo; (Please note, I got permission from Daddy to post this anecdote.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All in a Row</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/all-in-a-row/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/all-in-a-row/</guid>
      <description>Our middle child really likes to put things in order. Before she goes to bed at night she puts each of her stuffed animals in a straight row beside her pillow. I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed recently that she seems to gravitate towards put things things into straight lines. When she plays with blocks she puts them next to each other in a row, like a road, rather then stacking them one on top of the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Laughter</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-importance-of-laughter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-importance-of-laughter/</guid>
      <description>My son&amp;rsquo;s birthday is approaching and I asked him earlier this week who he wanted to invite to his party. After hearing the list of the usual people he said, &amp;ldquo;There is this girl in my Sunday School class that is my friend. She laughs at my jokes and thinks it&amp;rsquo;s funny when I put a banana on my head. Can I invite her?&amp;rdquo; After further talk I figured out who he meant and added her to the invite list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Little Goofball</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-little-goofball/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-little-goofball/</guid>
      <description>I love my son&amp;rsquo;s imagination. He can turn a cooking pot into a race car or become a dog by merely wearing his shoes on his hands. Here are a few pictures of his antics from this morning. They made me smile and I hope they do the same for you!
He called out to me in the other room, &amp;ldquo;Hey Mom, look I am siting on the pot!&amp;rdquo; When I heard these words, they brought a different image to mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Morning Fashion Update</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/early-morning-fashion-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/early-morning-fashion-update/</guid>
      <description>My son woke me up this morning at 6:15. Usually when this happens it is so that he can tell me he has to go potty. Today we had the following exchange, &amp;ldquo;Mommy.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Yes,&amp;rdquo; I replied very sleepily. &amp;ldquo;I am wearing red.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Yes, you are, go back to bed.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;OK.&amp;rdquo; He went back to bed until 7. Not sure why he felt the need to tell me that at 6:15 this morning, but I did get a chuckle out of it as I rolled over and went back to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
