<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>birth stories on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/birth-stories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in birth stories on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 11:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/birth-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Birth Story Number 4</title>
      <link>/posts/birth-story-number-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/birth-story-number-4/</guid>
      <description>Just a few short weeks ago I was reminiscing about the birth stories of my first 3 children… I can’t believe I am now “on the other side” of this pregnancy as well and finally able to share the details of my son’s entrance into the world.
It actually starts out very similarly to my first birth story. The night before my due date Scott and I went to bed early and as we were going to bed Scott jokingly said, “Feel free to wake me at 3 am and tell me you are in labor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flashback Friday: Labor Stories Part 3</title>
      <link>/posts/flashback-friday-labor-stories-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/flashback-friday-labor-stories-part-3/</guid>
      <description>By the third time around, one would think that a gal would have the whole labor thing down pat.
One would think….
About a week or so before my due date, I started having contractions…nothing super painful, but enough to make we wonder, “What if this ends up being it?” This time around the van was vacuumed well in advance, so no early morning trips to the gas station for Scott to clean the car before heading to the doctors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flashback Friday: Labor Stories Part 2</title>
      <link>/posts/flashback-friday-labor-stories-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/flashback-friday-labor-stories-part-2/</guid>
      <description>22 months after we brought our son into the world, we eagerly welcomed his little sister.
I came home from a MOPS meeting a week before my due date noticing on and off contractions. I remember walking up the stairs and telling my husband I was having light contractions. I then burst into tears because we hadn’t yet vacuumed the car and I didn’t want to bring the baby home in a dirty car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flashback Friday: Labor Stories Part 1</title>
      <link>/posts/flashback-friday-labor-stories-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/flashback-friday-labor-stories-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Lately some friends from church have been having babies and it is quite humorous to observe all the face book stalking that takes place now a days when one is in labor. Even just 3 yrs ago when I had my youngest, it wasn’t like this. Now when your in labor you update your status before heading to the hospital and then the whole world is checking your page and your close friends page looking for updates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
