<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Disney on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/disney/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Disney on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 18:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/disney/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Role Play</title>
      <link>/posts/role-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/role-play/</guid>
      <description>Our oldest daughter had a little fun getting into her character for Halloween. When posing for pictures in their costumes, she decided to fully act out the part of Snow White.

I think my favorite part of the reenactment was when she asked us to take her picture sleeping with the apple. &amp;quot;Skip the ol posing by the door with the trick or treat basket, we’ll go for playing dead on the floor with an apple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hmmm… Notice Something Missing Here?</title>
      <link>/posts/hmmm-notice-something-missing-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hmmm-notice-something-missing-here/</guid>
      <description>As my 4 yr old sat coloring in the waiting room this afternoon the mom beside me commented on her neat job of staying in the lines. Then we both did a double take and looked over at each other. 
Don’t  mind the fact that the dress is green and should “really” be yellow… I love the fact that my girl goes against the flow and colors it how she wants… sure give Belle purple hair and a green dress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams Really Do Come True</title>
      <link>/posts/dreams-really-do-come-true/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dreams-really-do-come-true/</guid>
      <description>Because we were only planning to do one day in Disney (I hope to take the whole family back later for a longer Disney vacation when all of the the kids are old enough to truly enjoy and appreciate it. This day in Magic Kingdom was just to hold them me over for the next 5 years or so) I didn’t even try to pretend we’d be able to do or see it all in one day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
