<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Traveling Circus on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/traveling-circus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Traveling Circus on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 16:51:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/traveling-circus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Books To Life</title>
      <link>/posts/bringing-books-to-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bringing-books-to-life/</guid>
      <description>This February the girls had their very first international meet in Orlando Florida!

And since the meet happened to be only 10 minutes from Universal Studios, we decided to add a day of Family Fun at Universal Studios before heading home from Florida.

Our oldest son has read the entire Harry Potter series more than once as well as some of the “bonus books” like Fantastical Beasts and Quidditch Through the Ages… child number two got into the Harry Potter phase this fall and is currently reading book 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Kitts: More Beach Fun and Monkeys!</title>
      <link>/posts/st-kitts-more-beach-fun-and-monkeys/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/st-kitts-more-beach-fun-and-monkeys/</guid>
      <description>Our final port of call was St Kitts.
. 
We didn’t really have a game plan for St Kitts. All we knew was we wanted to find monkeys and a beach with some shells and snorkeling. We found a taxi driver who could take us to both!



After getting a chance to hold the monkeys, we set off for the beach.


Here we enjoyed several hours of sand, sun, swimming, sea shells, and snorkeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another National Park – St. John USVI</title>
      <link>/posts/another-national-park-st.-john-usvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/another-national-park-st.-john-usvi/</guid>
      <description>When we found out the itinerary for the family cruise, Scott and I were super excited to see that the ship would be stopping at St Thomas… this meant that we could take an excursion to St John and visit US Virgin Island National Park!!!
That’s right, another vacation with a sign pic for the circus crew!!

National parks rarely disappoint and St. John was no exception. St John was our family’s favorite day of the vacation (and there were a lot of good days)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birthday in the Caribbean</title>
      <link>/posts/birthday-in-the-caribbean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/birthday-in-the-caribbean/</guid>
      <description>Our youngest daughter turned 10 during our vacation. It was the second year in a row that her birthday fell during our vacation. At first she wasn’t very excited about having to celebrate her birthday away from home….but turns out a Caribbean cruise isn’t too bad a place to celebrate ones birthday.
She has told me in the past that SOMEDAY, she would like to have an ice skating party. Um, Ice skating parties in July can be a tad tricky….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bahamas Part 2</title>
      <link>/posts/bahamas-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 12:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bahamas-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Once we had our clothing situation resolved, a weight was lifted from our shoulders and were ready to show the kids the Caribbean. We were thankful we were able to get our errand running out of the way early and get the kids so we could hit the beach. We were off the ship for round 2 before 9 am!

We had decided ahead of time that our plan for Nassau was to walk to nearby Junkanoo Beach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replacing What Was Left Behind</title>
      <link>/posts/replacing-what-was-left-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/replacing-what-was-left-behind/</guid>
      <description>The day before we left for vacation, I had commented to a friend that I found packing for our cruise to be more challenging than any other vacation because this was the first vacation we’d gone on where if we forgot something we couldn’t just run to Wal-mart to pick up what we needed…
Turns out I was worried for good reason, b/c when we arrived at the curb of the airport, we realized we had left behind one of our larger suitcases… the one with all of my and Scott’s underclothes and shorts and every day type clothing (it also had some decorations for our daughters 10th birthday that I was really excited about :-(.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmastime in the Big Apple</title>
      <link>/posts/christmastime-in-the-big-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/christmastime-in-the-big-apple/</guid>
      <description>About a month ago my youngest asked when we would see the Statue of Liberty again. We visited it a few years ago on our way to our Boston Vacation, and it has been a highlight memory of our youngest child ever since. He loves when we spot it on tv or in a picture somewhere. I replied, “Probably the next time we go to New York City.” To which he of course replied, “When can we go to New York City again?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Full, Fun Last Day of our Adventure</title>
      <link>/posts/the-full-fun-last-day-of-our-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-full-fun-last-day-of-our-adventure/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been home two and a half weeks and I am finally taking time to record the moments of our last day of vacation…. this is proof positive that I am glad I took the time to record our memories while on vacation b/c there is no way I could have gone back and done it once home.
We woke up QUITE cold on our last full day of vacation at Great Basin National Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our last National Park for this vacation!!</title>
      <link>/posts/our-last-national-park-for-this-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 01:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-last-national-park-for-this-vacation/</guid>
      <description>We left Gana’s house around 11 on Saturday. Our destination was Great Basin National Park in eastern Nevada. Our route was ‘the loneliest highway in America’. It was by far our longest drive of the trip, 8 hours with no midpoint destinations. But, of course, we made a few stops. We were not expecting much. We had mentally interpreted “loneliest highway” as “boringest highway” and thought it was going to be 8 hours of unchanging desert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time with Gana</title>
      <link>/posts/time-with-gana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/time-with-gana/</guid>
      <description>We can not make a trip to the state of California without finding a way to visit Scott’s Nana. Even though California is a big state, and being in California does not necessarily equate being in Nana’s neighborhood. Compared to the east coast, anywhere in California is MUCH, MUCH closer to Nana’s than normal. So, we knew our trip to California, MUST include a visit at Nana’s (or as the kids call her Gana for G reat N ana ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunch in San Fran</title>
      <link>/posts/lunch-in-san-fran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/lunch-in-san-fran/</guid>
      <description>I love big cities. D.C., New York City, Boston, Chicago, Seattle, Philadelphia… So, it probably doesn’t surprise anyone, Scott included, that when I was plotting our road trip from Pinnacles NP to his Nana’s north of Sacramento, I insisted we “swing by San Francisco” for lunch on our way. It was an hour drive out of the way (plus whatever time we spent in the city) but I really, really wanted to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reuniting with Family at Pinnacles National Park</title>
      <link>/posts/reuniting-with-family-at-pinnacles-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/reuniting-with-family-at-pinnacles-national-park/</guid>
      <description>During our trek across California, we wanted to also make time to see some of Scott’s family that live here. Scott’s aunt, uncle, and his cousin and her family live a few hours from Pinnacles National Park and graciously offered to meet us there and spend time with us at the park.

We met at a restaurant called Togo’s… we had never heard of it before, but Scott’s cousin described it as “like subway only better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiking to the Falls</title>
      <link>/posts/hiking-to-the-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hiking-to-the-falls/</guid>
      <description>Scott had been hoping for us to take a hike down from Glacier Point to Yosemite Valley. It would be our longest hike, but it would have been all down hill and we would pass both Nevada and Vernal Falls. Given our kids fascination with water falls, this seemed like a fun hike. Unfortunately, we learned too late that there was no shuttle from Yosemite Valley to Glacier Point, and the only way we could do this plan was if we had pre purchased tickets for a special shuttle that left early in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One of America’s Best</title>
      <link>/posts/one-of-americas-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-of-americas-best/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I visited Yosemite 14 years ago during our trip which shaped all trips. Therefore, it wasn’t a must see for this vacation. And when Scott and I were first plotting out this trip, we kind of waivered as to whether we wanted to include it or not. But, we decided that since Yosemite is one of the quintessential parks and since we were were were going to be SO CLOSE, we owed it to the kids to show them Yosemite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Ol’ Family Fun in the Canyon</title>
      <link>/posts/good-ol-family-fun-in-the-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/good-ol-family-fun-in-the-canyon/</guid>
      <description>Our campground was located pretty much on the border of Sequoia and Kings Canyon National Parks. We woke slowly and had a leisurely breakfast, then headed out to see Kings Canyon.

As we approached the visitor center, we saw a sign for a church service in the park. We were only 5 minutes late so we ran down to join them in worship. It was pretty neat to be able to join with other believers in worship, right there in the midst of God’s creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BIG TREES!</title>
      <link>/posts/big-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 23:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/big-trees/</guid>
      <description>We arrived at Sequoia National Park around 2:00. We had a picnic lunch, stopped by the Visitors Center and headed off to find some big trees.

We took a 4 mile hike in the late afternoon, that as of this point, goes down as my favorite hike of the trip. We started in the populous area of the infamous General Sherman.


Then we hiked the Congress Trail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little break from camping</title>
      <link>/posts/a-little-break-from-camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-little-break-from-camping/</guid>
      <description>After our morning at the beach, we were headed north west to prepare for the next leg of our trip. But before heading to 4 more National Parks, we were in need of hot showers, soft beds, and a washing machine.
Enter, Best Western.

We hadn’t booked a hotel in advance because we weren’t exactly sure how far we’d want to drive on Friday… we knew we wanted to get close to Sequoia National Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tide Pools</title>
      <link>/posts/tide-pools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tide-pools/</guid>
      <description>Since marine life is part of Channel Islands National park, we woke up at 5:30am so we could visit some nearby tide pools while it was low tide.

 
The kids didn’t seem to mind too much though, because the promise of seeing “cool things” was all it took to get them up and at it. Even our late sleeper had a smile on his face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Island Bound!</title>
      <link>/posts/island-bound/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/island-bound/</guid>
      <description>This trip seems to be all about extremes and remoteness. Channel Islands National Park is a group of islands located off the coast of Los Angeles. A visit here gives one a glimpse of what the California coast looked like before it was overpopulated with humanity. You can find vegetation and wild life here that doesn’t exist anywhere else. The signature element of the park however is the rocky cliffs along the waters edge and the marine life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pacific Ocean!!!</title>
      <link>/posts/the-pacific-ocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 01:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-pacific-ocean/</guid>
      <description>After leaving Joshua Tree, we were headed west for the Pacific Ocean. We checked out the visitor center and checked in with the boat company about our day trip the following day. Then we stopped at Subway to grab subs for dinner on the beach. 
We were camping at a State Park which had walking access to the beach. We all greatly enjoyed eating dinner overlooking the ocean and than splashing in the waves afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please can we climb some more?</title>
      <link>/posts/please-can-we-climb-some-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 22:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/please-can-we-climb-some-more/</guid>
      <description>While we pack a lot into these trips, the over all plan is always pretty fluid. Scott and I had always left a second night at Joshua Tree as an option in our itinerary. After a great evening sunset, animal show, morning hike, and visit to the visitors center, the heat of the day had us thinking perhaps we should move on to cooler pastures. The kids however had so much fun climbing around Jumbo Rocks that they unanimously voted we stay the second night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Playground</title>
      <link>/posts/the-ultimate-playground/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-ultimate-playground/</guid>
      <description>Our campsite was at Jumbo Rocks, aptly named being as the campground was nestled amongst big rocks.
 
As with any desert park, the key to hiking is to go early or late. Right after breakfast we set off to hike the Skull Rocks trail. The trailhead was within walking distance of our campsite. Since we were hiking in the early morning, we came across a few animal friends along our way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Tree National Park</title>
      <link>/posts/joshua-tree-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/joshua-tree-national-park/</guid>
      <description>We left the salt flats in Badwater Basin of Death Valley around 10:30am. After heading 45 minutes towards Joshua Tree we came across a road closure and had to turn around. This of course added about 2 hrs to our 4 and a half hour drive to Joshua Tree. I had found a restaurant online in Pioneertown that I had decided would be worth a little extra driving out of our way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Many Sides of Death Valley</title>
      <link>/posts/the-many-sides-of-death-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-many-sides-of-death-valley/</guid>
      <description>Don’t get me wrong. Death Valley is aptly named. It is hot. Like crazy hot. Like 95 degrees at 7am, hot. And it is desolate. Like, LITERAL MIDDLE OF NOWHERE, desolate. Not a soul in site for miles and miles. And of course the signs everywhere warning you of heat stroke and death and the need for water. I get why they call it Death Valley. And quite a lot of the park looks like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Judge a Park By It’s Title</title>
      <link>/posts/dont-judge-a-park-by-its-title/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dont-judge-a-park-by-its-title/</guid>
      <description>When we first began our quest, I assumed Death Valley National Park would be a mere checking off of a box. But, as we started planning and I began researching things to do there, I realized it really was a beautiful and unique park. 
Sunday morning we started out with a relaxing morning at our hotel near the airport in Vegas. We woke up, took showers and took advantage of the complimentary breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Adventure Begins!</title>
      <link>/posts/another-adventure-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 00:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/another-adventure-begins/</guid>
      <description>After much saving and planning, the circus fam set off for another National Park adventure. Our mission: to visit 8 national parks (7 in California and 1 in Nevada).

Because we wanted to maximize our time at the parks, we opted to fly to Las Vegas and rent a van. We plan to camp for 12 of our 17 nights of vacation. The thing about camping is it requires the same amount of stuff for one night away as it does for 5 or 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Ending</title>
      <link>/posts/perfect-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/perfect-ending/</guid>
      <description>The last true day of our vacation (the day before we headed home) was in my opinion the most relaxing day of the week.
We slept in, ate breakfast, (the kids did the dishes), and then we headed out for a morning hike along the beach.
 
The tide was out and we discovered many living creatures in tide pools on the rocky beach
.


We made our way to the other side of the island and even caught a glimpse of the Boston skyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peddocks Island Day 1</title>
      <link>/posts/peddocks-island-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 03:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/peddocks-island-day-1/</guid>
      <description>After our rain delay/rain out, we finally made it to Peddocks Island… one day late. After hiking the LONG hike uphill to our site, I am so glad we didn’t attempt it during the torrential rainstorm.
It was a big enough hassle getting our stuff from the van to the ferry, off the ferry, on to the other ferry, off that ferry, and then up the long hike up hill to our site… but the weather was gorgeous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birthday in Boston</title>
      <link>/posts/birthday-in-boston/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/birthday-in-boston/</guid>
      <description>The plan for today was to wake up and prepare to catch a ferry to Boston Harbor Island to begin the camping portion of our vacation.
However, we woke to this.

And after checking the weather saw that the day was going to be off and on rain showers for the remainder. This seemed like less than an ideal setting to haul all our camping gear onto a ferry, off a ferry, onto another ferry, to our campsite AND THEN set up a tent… a tent with a screen roof none the less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom Trail</title>
      <link>/posts/freedom-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/freedom-trail/</guid>
      <description>We chose Boston for a family vacation destination this summer because of our study this past year on the American Revolution. However, I had no illusions of dragging four kids through the entire 2 and 1/2 mile freedom trail on a hot and humid summer day. We are actually going to spend the bulk of our week camping on an island in Boston Harbor, but I did want to show the kids a few highlights of history, especially my oldest as he is the history buff of the crew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Lady Liberty Up Close</title>
      <link>/posts/seeing-lady-liberty-up-close/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/seeing-lady-liberty-up-close/</guid>
      <description>It was super fun to take the kids to see the “Statue of the Liberty” on the first day of our vacation.

It was a cloudy and overcast day so the picture of the Manhattan skyline don’t pop with color, but it was still really neat to see the skyline from this vantage point.

At first we couldn’t figure out why our youngest would lay down on the ground when we were at the base of the pedestal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Half Life Anniversary Excursion</title>
      <link>/posts/our-half-life-anniversary-excursion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 06:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-half-life-anniversary-excursion/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I started dating our senior year of high school, when we were both 17. A few years ago we were out for an anniversary date and realized that we were approaching the point in our life when we would have been together as much of our life as we weren’t together. We decided we wanted to celebrate such a momentous occasion and so we (and by we, I really mean Scott) calculated out when exactly that would be… our dates are different since we don’t share the same birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Field Trip Fun</title>
      <link>/posts/family-field-trip-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/family-field-trip-fun/</guid>
      <description>When we switched out history curriculum this year so that the whole family studies the same period of history (with varying level of work catered to their age level), one of the reasons I was MOST excited was that our field trips would be applicable to all. When our tutorial gave off for Presidents Day, I was eager to take advantage of the day free of book work to go on a field trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost Home</title>
      <link>/posts/almost-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2013 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/almost-home/</guid>
      <description>The last stop on our grand adventure of 2013 was Grandma and Papa’s house. We arrived in the afternoon on the 4th of July… just in time for a cookout. The kids greatly enjoyed tractor rides with Papa, playing board games with Grandma and running the trains in the basement.

Then they requested a visit to “The Coolest Playground Ever.” As we trekked around the US over the past 3 weeks, Scott and I learned from the kids that the playground by which all playgrounds are judged against is the wooden one by Grandma and Papa’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stopping to Play in Illinois</title>
      <link>/posts/stopping-to-play-in-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/stopping-to-play-in-illinois/</guid>
      <description>We set out from our friends in Iowa and headed north east. Our destination was the suburbs of Chicago. Scott and I visited Chicago last year for our anniversary and while I loved the city and would love to visit it again, we didn’t feel this was the trip to take the family into the city. Instead we planned a stop at Lego Discovery Center outside of the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heading East!</title>
      <link>/posts/heading-east/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/heading-east/</guid>
      <description>After leaving the Badlands, we were Eastward bound and on the homeward stretch. We planned lots of fun stops for this part of the journey, knowing it was the final stretch and wanting to change it up a bit and keep things fun and exciting.
Our first such stop was in Sioux Falls, SD. I found a hotel there that had a water slide and a splash pool. There was also a put put course in town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Park (for a long while)</title>
      <link>/posts/last-park-for-a-long-while/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2013 06:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/last-park-for-a-long-while/</guid>
      <description>Well, I am really sad to say our trip is winding down. We visited the last National Park of our vacation and we can count the number of days left on our trip on one hand. The last park on this grand vacation was Badlands National Park in South Dakota. 
We hit the Badlands on a great day and a great time of day. The sun was low in the sky making the colors pop out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animals, Animals, Everywhere!</title>
      <link>/posts/animals-animals-everywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/animals-animals-everywhere/</guid>
      <description>Saturday we left Mt Rushmore and drove 4.5 hours north to Theodore Roosevelt National Park in Medora, ND. A visit to this park meant an approximately 9 hour driving detour from what could have otherwise been a short hop from Mt. Rushmore to the SD Badlands. Sometimes a quest such as our forces your hand to take some pretty circuitous routes… we set off not exactly sure what the ND badlands had to offer that the SD badlands did not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wind Cave Take 2</title>
      <link>/posts/wind-cave-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wind-cave-take-2/</guid>
      <description>11 years ago when Scott and I did our first National Park/Cross Country trip, we drove through Wind Caves National Park. We hadn’t yet begun our quest to see every National Park, so we actually just drove through the park and enjoyed the prairie dogs and buffalo. It was literally a stop on our way, not a destination in itself. This time, Scott and I wanted to see the park the right way and go on a cave tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Whole Lotta Sand</title>
      <link>/posts/a-whole-lotta-sand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2013 08:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-whole-lotta-sand/</guid>
      <description>We arrived at Great Sand Dunes National Park in the middle of the night so our first view of the dunes was when we opened up our tent the next morning. We thought for sure we wouldn’t be able to get a site since they were first come first serve and we were so very late. But once again we were blessed with a camp site in the park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Jam Packed 24 hours</title>
      <link>/posts/a-jam-packed-24-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-jam-packed-24-hours/</guid>
      <description>We left Canyonlands mid day on Monday and got a hotel in Montrose, Co. We were greeted with a fabulous view of the snow topped Rocky Mts. Scott took the kids swimming while I did laundry. Then we splurged and went out for dinner at Applebees. It was a welcome change from fast food/Subway. The next day we hit Black Canyon of the Gunnison!

This was a hard park to fully comprehend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking in their Footsteps</title>
      <link>/posts/walking-in-their-footsteps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 21:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/walking-in-their-footsteps/</guid>
      <description>We arrived in Mesa Verde National Park a few hours before sunset. We had been hoping to catch the Twilight Tour of Cliff Palace but tickets are sold on a first come basis and, much like we expected, we weren&amp;rsquo;t the first to come. We opted for a sunset drive along the loop with some pretty overlooks and booked tours for the following morning. 
The sunset drive was really fascinating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Mom’s Dream</title>
      <link>/posts/every-moms-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/every-moms-dream/</guid>
      <description>How many times have you wished you could be in more than one place at a time? I know there’s been many a time that I’ve had that thought….
And Saturday, I had my wish. We were in four places at once.
The circus family stood in Arizona, Utah, New Mexico, and Colorado at the same time.

We goofed around a bit and then the big kids got to strike their favorite pose in 4 states at once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It really is that GRAND</title>
      <link>/posts/it-really-is-that-grand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/it-really-is-that-grand/</guid>
      <description>11 years ago this month Scott and I visited The Grand Canyon. It was my first time seeing it and it took my breath away. Now, 31 parks later, it is still my favorite of all the National Parks. Many rank high on my list, but if you could only see one, I feel like this should be the one.

The day before we took the kids, I had a little fear, much like the fear I had before taking them to Disney World.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Step Back in Time</title>
      <link>/posts/a-step-back-in-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-step-back-in-time/</guid>
      <description>Thursday we spent the day at Petrified Forest National Park, located in the painted desert of Arizona.

Here the kids worked hard to earn their Junior Ranger badges. We spent quite a bit of time learning and researching in the visitors center. 
We also took a walk to look at the petrified wood. 
We then drove through the Painted Desert. It was beautiful to see all the layers of colored dirt deposited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Desert Experience</title>
      <link>/posts/the-desert-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-desert-experience/</guid>
      <description>The kids were so excited to finally get to go camping. Day 6 of our adventure and it was our first night setting up a tent. The kids LOVE the head flashlights I picked up before we left. 
Unfortunately, we discovered we neglected to pack the poles with our tent. So we had a family meeting round the picnic table. We had 3 options. 1. Go to Walmart, get a new tent and come back and set it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Saguaro</title>
      <link>/posts/the-great-saguaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-great-saguaro/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday we left New Mexico and headed south west for Saguaro National Park in Tuscon, AZ.

We got to Saguaro National Park in time to explore a bit and then take in the parks beauty after the oppressive heat of the day was past. It really was perfect timing. We walked around a path near the visitors center which allowed us to see the cacti up close. 
The cacti were much bigger than we expected and we were delighted to find some in bloom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cadillac Ranch</title>
      <link>/posts/cadillac-ranch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cadillac-ranch/</guid>
      <description>While planning our trip, I was searching for some sort of fun diversion for our long car ride day. I wanted something free, fun, and not out of the way.
Cadillac Ranch fit the bill perfectly. 
Cadillac Ranch is a wide open field on the side of route 40 with 10 old cadillacs stuck in the ground. People can come and spray paint on them. It’s a “changing art exhibit” as people are continually coming and adding to and changing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Road Again</title>
      <link>/posts/on-the-road-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 12:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/on-the-road-again/</guid>
      <description>Sunday was one of the few days of our trip that we spent entirely in the van. While we will be in the car for portions of almost every day of our trip, Sunday was a day when the event for the day was driving. For over 11 hours. We left Ft Smith, AR around 9:45AM5am CT, quickly entered into Oklahoma, drove the top portion of Texas, and arrived in Albuquerque, NM a little after 11:00pm MT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Like it Hot</title>
      <link>/posts/some-like-it-hot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/some-like-it-hot/</guid>
      <description>The first national park on this grand adventure was Hot Springs National Park in Hot Springs, AR.

It seems we are passing on the sign picture tradition… as everyone wanted a picture of the sign with their camera. The town of Hot Springs was built to capitalize on the hot springs of water coming out of the ground in that area. 
[
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/IMG_0284.jpg)
Numerous bath houses were built here in the early 1900s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trekking Across the USA</title>
      <link>/posts/trekking-across-the-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/trekking-across-the-usa/</guid>
      <description>Saturday we left Nashville and continued further west. Our goal for the day was to reach Ft Smith, AR (on the border of AR and OK) and to visit Hot Springs National Park in Hot Springs, AR. Mission Accomplished
We were in the car from about 9:45am to 11:30pm… with the exception of 3 hours in Hot Springs. No one seemed to mind though. They had video games, movies, books, coloring pages, and crafts to pass the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off to a Great Start</title>
      <link>/posts/off-to-a-great-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/off-to-a-great-start/</guid>
      <description>We started on our grand adventure yesterday morning. We set off a little later than we had hoped due to some storm preparations we had to make in case the forecasted impending storms took out our power while we were gone.
Our plan for day one was to drive from Annapolis, MD to Nashville, TN. Our route took us through DC which was a fun start.

We left our house around 10:15 in the morning and pulled into Scott’s cousins in TN around 10:30pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Infamous Sign Pictures</title>
      <link>/posts/the-infamous-sign-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-infamous-sign-pictures/</guid>
      <description>I know I’ve posted some of them before, but as we prepare to add 11 new pictures to our collection, I thought I’d post the pictures we currently have in our flip book.
2002










2003



2005

2006



2007



2009



2010



2011

I had so much fun looking back over these pictures and recalling the stories behind them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Trip that Shaped Our Lives</title>
      <link>/posts/the-trip-that-shaped-our-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-trip-that-shaped-our-lives/</guid>
      <description>You know how sometimes a movie or book will portray how one decision or one event changed the momentum and current of the character’s entire life?
Well for Scott and I, that momentum shifting/life altering event was our vacation in 2002. Somehow or other we got to talking about cross country trips. And somehow an idea blossomed for a large out west vacation. We had a huge map of the US in our laundry room and we began plotting our course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packing the Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/packing-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/packing-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>After a week of fun, friends, field trips, house work, sleeping in, and even a camp fire, we’re topping off our Spring Break with a long weekend at Grandma and Papa’s.
I have found that packing up the circus crew of 6 for even a weekend away, can at times be a bit overwhelming. And while the kids love to help pack, sometimes they are anything but helpful. So, I found a system that works pretty well for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Her First Meet (the Good, the Bad, the UGLY)</title>
      <link>/posts/her-first-meet-the-good-the-bad-the-ugly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/her-first-meet-the-good-the-bad-the-ugly/</guid>
      <description>Our 6 year old had her first gymnastics meet this past weekend. I can’t really put into words the feelings of pride I had in watching her. When we first enrolled her in gymnastics 3 years ago, we did so because she was tiny, tough and flexible. It seemed gymnastics might be worth a try for our then 3 year old.
Somewhere in the last 3 years, a light when on inside her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just the 2 of us in Chicago</title>
      <link>/posts/just-the-2-of-us-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/just-the-2-of-us-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I got away last week, just the 2 of us, for 3 nights in the Windy City. It was a belated 10 year anniversary gift to ourselves.

And it was WON-DER-FUL!!

The city of Chicago is beautiful. The buildings are unique and interesting… truly works of art in and of themselves. We had so much fun walking around the city and taking in its beauty. The weather was overcast and it rained off and on while we were there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An End of Summer Tradition</title>
      <link>/posts/an-end-of-summer-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/an-end-of-summer-tradition/</guid>
      <description>Of the 32 years I’ve been a Steelers fan, I only had the joy of being a hometown fan for only 8 of those years (5 of which I was 5 and under so it doesn’t really count in my book). My sophomore year of college, I moved to PA for 3 years. I was thrilled to get to watch the Steelers on a weekly basis. Unfortunately, this was during the Kordell Stewart, Tommy Maddox era, which wasn’t exactly the Steelers golden era of football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He Spoils Us</title>
      <link>/posts/he-spoils-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/he-spoils-us/</guid>
      <description>Time and time again our fourth child has blown us away with his easy going, flexible, happy-go-lucky approach to life. It has made the transition to a family of 6, for this family on-the-go, SO MUCH easier—a fact I am truly, truly grateful for.
This weekend, he really went above and beyond our expectations though.
Not only did he fall asleep in the tent both nights, while the rest of us were out at the camp fire, but he even napped in the tent Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Hour at the Beach</title>
      <link>/posts/an-hour-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/an-hour-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>Most people think that perfect beach weather is a bright sunny day, but we discovered unexpected joy in a trip to the Florida beach on an overcast evening following an afternoon rain storm.

Shuttle launch in the morning, nap in the afternoon, beach in the evening, and free Chick-Fil-A right before bed… it was a perfect day in Florida… totally worth the 32 hours of driving it took to get there and back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We FINALLY have BLAST OFF!</title>
      <link>/posts/we-finally-have-blast-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/we-finally-have-blast-off/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I was a kid and saw the movie Space Camp, I’ve wanted to see a shuttle launch. Last spring when Scott told me that NASA was cancelling their shuttle launch program and their were only 3 left, I began scheming a way to get there and see one.
We planned our entire vacation around the November launch. And while our trip to Florida last November, was one of our best family vacations ever, we didn’t get to see a launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One Where I Question Our Sanity and Whine Like a Baby</title>
      <link>/posts/the-one-where-i-question-our-sanity-and-whine-like-a-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-one-where-i-question-our-sanity-and-whine-like-a-baby/</guid>
      <description>When a tour company approaches you as you board their boat offering the chance to back out with a full refund, a normal person would heed the warning, take the money and run.
But we aren’t normal. Because we have a quest to visit every national park during our married life together. And this quest brought us all the way down to Key West. And we didn’t drive all the way down to Key West only to turn around and head 100 miles north without first taking a boat 70 nautical miles further west to Dry Tortugas National Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short but Sweet</title>
      <link>/posts/short-but-sweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/short-but-sweet/</guid>
      <description>Our time at Biscayne National Park was fun, but way too short. We took a 3 hour tour (which thankfully turned out much better than the infamous 3 hr tour). I think the kids favorite part was the 45 minute ride out to Boca Chita Island. They described their ride out their as “the best rollar coaster ride ever!” The wind was really blowing. I thought it felt much like those super sonic hand dryers that look like they are ripping your skin off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everglades National Park</title>
      <link>/posts/everglades-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/everglades-national-park/</guid>
      <description>When we arrived at Everglades NP it was shortly before midnight and raining quite hard. Scott got out of the van to attempt to put up the tent, but when he remembered the top of our tent is open screen (which we then put a cover over after set up) he realized it would be futile as the entire inside of the tent would be soaked before we even set it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams Really Do Come True</title>
      <link>/posts/dreams-really-do-come-true/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dreams-really-do-come-true/</guid>
      <description>Because we were only planning to do one day in Disney (I hope to take the whole family back later for a longer Disney vacation when all of the the kids are old enough to truly enjoy and appreciate it. This day in Magic Kingdom was just to hold them me over for the next 5 years or so) I didn’t even try to pretend we’d be able to do or see it all in one day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3…2…1…</title>
      <link>/posts/321/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/321/</guid>
      <description>We chose this year and even this specific week to take our Florida trip because the Space Shuttle Discovery was supposed to make it last launch into space. Both Scott and had always wanted to see a shuttle launch and being as it is one of the last launches ever, we really wanted to take the kids to see this historical event.
The launch was originally planned for Mon Nov 1st.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Becoming a Germophobe</title>
      <link>/posts/on-becoming-a-germophobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/on-becoming-a-germophobe/</guid>
      <description>Normally, I consider myself pretty laid back. Messy faces, germs, they all go with the territory of life with small kids and I don’t sweat em.
Then last year we took our grand Texas vacation… during which you may recall I caught the circus children licking the airplane window.
Then we spent our grand Texas vacation with multiple ear and sinus infections, suspected pink eye, laryngitis, and asthma episodes culminating with a day at a clinic in downtown San Antonio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Ya Gotta Go….</title>
      <link>/posts/when-ya-gotta-go./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2010 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/when-ya-gotta-go./</guid>
      <description>The outing started out so beautiful and picturesque. The drive there was lovely… leaves just starting to change, sipping my pumpkin spice latte, even the clouds looked “fall like” (amazing how everything looks lovely when the kids aren’t requiring you to referee from the drivers seat…thank you Psalty the Singing Songbook) We got to the farm and the kids happily ate their lunches while I nursed the baby. Then we were off to pick apples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because I’m Crazy Like That</title>
      <link>/posts/because-im-crazy-like-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/because-im-crazy-like-that/</guid>
      <description>It’s been almost a year since our grand Texas vacation and already I’ve got the planning bug for another grand circus family trek. Remember how I thought we’d just swing by Houston since we’d be in El Paso? Well, I have similar aspirations for a trip to California in the fall. (I know originally I’d been thinking we’d do a Florida trip, but baby number 4 has changed that aspiration a bit)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are Now Free to Move About the Country</title>
      <link>/posts/you-are-now-free-to-move-about-the-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/you-are-now-free-to-move-about-the-country/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a random Crystal factoid for you.
I hate flying.
It not the getting to the airport hrs early or the waiting in lines for security that gets me. It&amp;rsquo;s the act of actually flying that I am opposed to. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong. I do it and though I am no frequent flier I would say I fly with some frequency; at least once sometimes twice a year. But, I hate the feeling of queasiness I get during take off and landing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prudent or Paranoid?</title>
      <link>/posts/prudent-or-paranoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/prudent-or-paranoid/</guid>
      <description>Our continual quest to visit each of the US National parks, prompted us to take a day trip to Carlsbad caverns while in El Paso this weekend.
Oddly enough we were quite familiar with the route has we were only about 11 miles from there this April when we visited Guadeloupe. To get to Carlsbad from El Paso you travel 138 miles on a rather barren and desolate road in the desert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number One Rule of Camping</title>
      <link>/posts/number-one-rule-of-camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/number-one-rule-of-camping/</guid>
      <description>**Updated Below!
Once we finally departed, the kids were ecstatic about our camping trip this weekend. As we were preparing to leave, my son already started talking about the very, important rules of camping, as he’s discovered them over the years.
And the number one, most exciting rule is that **
camping is messy!
**
This one cracked me up, because while it is true, to hear him talk you would think he grew up in a house where he was never allowed to get dirty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Packed Up and No Place To Go</title>
      <link>/posts/all-packed-up-and-no-place-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/all-packed-up-and-no-place-to-go/</guid>
      <description>Van is fully packed… literally, I don’t think we could fit another thing in there. Careful opening the back door, the sleeping bags will fall when you life it up. Kids buckled in. Dog ready to drop off at my friend’s.
Wait, forgot the tip of the fishing rod. Back in the house.
Scott’s needs a ball cap. Back in the house. After packing, repacking, rearranging the car seats, returning to the house, oh 3 or 4 dozen more times, we are set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’ve got the planning bug…</title>
      <link>/posts/ive-got-the-planning-bug/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 20:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ive-got-the-planning-bug/</guid>
      <description>While you might think that the potential pink eye, multiple ear infections, and laryngitis would scare me away from ever taking the circus crew on another national park vacation, it doesn’t. Just call me crazy!
I’ll admit, parts of our Texas vacation wasn’t all we hoped and dreamed it would be.
But, I am glad we went and eager to visit some more national parks.
So this afternoon I sat down to map out a potential trip to Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Great Big Thank You</title>
      <link>/posts/a-great-big-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2009 20:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-great-big-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Sorry to leave you all hanging with my sarcastic tribute to San Antonio…I’ve spend the last 24 hours prepping for and then hosting my son’s 5th birthday…(How did he end up being 5 already)? But, I’ll save that for another post… one involving sinister villains, and superheroes…be sure to come back next week for that one! I do want to clarify, that even though we did spend 4 hours in the urgent care facility, we did have a great time in San Antonio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Antonio Like You’ve Never Seen It!</title>
      <link>/posts/san-antonio-like-youve-never-seen-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 05:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/san-antonio-like-youve-never-seen-it/</guid>
      <description>After 4 days of camping at both Guadalupe and Big Bend NP, the next big destination on our trip was to San Antonio. We were quite excited about showers, and more room to spread out. After checking into our hotel at noon, we were off to see the sights.
Where to first? The Alamo? The Children’s Museum? The River walk? So many choices…
We thought what better place to go to really experience the city than the urgent care clinic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Bend: From Sunup to Sundown</title>
      <link>/posts/big-bend-from-sunup-to-sundown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/big-bend-from-sunup-to-sundown/</guid>
      <description>The sun’s rays cast a bright orange glow on the rocks when it rose in the morning.

As the day went on, the bees came out to pollinate the flora.

As the day progressed, we were able to pose for the very significant sign shot. Click here to learn of it’s high importance.

As the sun began to set the rocks began to change color yet again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh, So You Wanted to See the Actual Parks?</title>
      <link>/posts/oh-so-you-wanted-to-see-the-actual-parks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2009 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/oh-so-you-wanted-to-see-the-actual-parks/</guid>
      <description>I’m trying my best to summarize our almost 2 week vacation, so as to keep you up to date with our circus adventures, without boring you with every.single.picture we took (if you knew how many pics we took, you would realize this is NO.SMALL.FEAT). I realized today though that I haven’t really posted any pictures of the actual parks yet. Hmmm…perhaps I should do something about that.
So, any guesses on which national park this is from?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Times</title>
      <link>/posts/good-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/good-times/</guid>
      <description>picnic lunches
  sweet treats

hot springs

big leaps

dirty hands</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The World’s Most Expensive Pint of Ice Cream</title>
      <link>/posts/the-worlds-most-expensive-pint-of-ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-worlds-most-expensive-pint-of-ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>Besides taking in the beautiful scenery (of which there was much) at Guadalupe and Big Bend National Parks, we really enjoyed being able to just be together (most of the time). Each day at Big Bend we took a very, long picnic lunch. One day we went to the western portion of the park and enjoyed a leisurely picnic. I thought it would be fun to make our own ice cream in coffee cans using a recipe I had found online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It was the best of times, It was the worst of times…</title>
      <link>/posts/it-was-the-best-of-times-it-was-the-worst-of-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 05:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/it-was-the-best-of-times-it-was-the-worst-of-times/</guid>
      <description>I’d say good ol’ Dickens phrase aptly describes our week of camping in Texas. We’ve had us some great times this week… saw some beautiful handiworks of God’s creation and enjoyed time away from everyday life together as a family. I look forward to sharing many such anecdotes and pictures with you over the next few posts, but I gotta admit, we’ve had our “moments” as well.
It was the sickness that got to us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Center Stage</title>
      <link>/posts/sharing-center-stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sharing-center-stage/</guid>
      <description>Since I’m currently camping in the desert with no electricity or WiFi, I called upon a few of my dear blogging friends to fill in during my absence here at the circus. They graciously agreed. So, Tuesday, Wednesday, and Thursday of this week, I will feature a different guest blogger from my blog roll for your reading pleasure. I suggested they write a post that demonstrates how they would fit in here at the circus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes Things Aren’t Exactly Like We Plan</title>
      <link>/posts/sometimes-things-arent-exactly-like-we-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sometimes-things-arent-exactly-like-we-plan/</guid>
      <description>Saturday we ventured out for White Sands, NM. We had high hopes for some sand sledding. I was expecting it to be like this.
Only there is this phenomenon in Texas we recently discovered called Wind Season. Who knew? (Yes, knowledge of this would have been helpful in planning our vacation). So when we arrived at White Sands we discovered something called a sand storm.

And unlike a snow storm, sand storms hurt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yea, So Apparently Licking Windows Is NOT a Good Idea</title>
      <link>/posts/yea-so-apparently-licking-windows-is-not-a-good-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/yea-so-apparently-licking-windows-is-not-a-good-idea/</guid>
      <description>Hmmm…we’re on day 3 of our grand Texas adventure…and the circus crew has come down with quite a few ailments. My hoarse voice has developed into full laryngitis. My son has gotten a case of pink eye. My baby has developed a fever. And the middle child has nothing specific yet, but I did detect a little runny nose this evening.

NICE, huh?
Guess we just wanted to feel at home, so we brought the plague of the past few months along with us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ambitious or Crazy?</title>
      <link>/posts/ambitious-or-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ambitious-or-crazy/</guid>
      <description>We made it. And more amazingly than that. So did our 5 suitcases, pack-n-play, and 3 car seats! We had a very gracious man checking us in who gave us time to sort our bags and let one slide which was slightly over the 50lb limit. Then we were blessed when we went to the car rental agency and got a stow and go van (which will make carting our 5 suitcases around much easier) and Scott was somehow able to talk them into a price several hundred dollars cheaper than the estimate we had gotten online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traveling Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/traveling-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/traveling-circus/</guid>
      <description>Our bags are packed, checked, we’ve passed security, and now the circus crew is sitting in the terminal snacking on bagels, waiting to board the plane for El Paso (well, to Jackson to Huston to El Paso)!
 
You haven’t see the circus till you’ve see 2 adults, three preschoolers, our 8 checked bags and our 4 carry on items go through the check in line and security. Let’s throw in a little reshuffling of items in our bags to try and make all of our bags meet the weight limit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
