<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shuttle launch on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/shuttle-launch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shuttle launch on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 08:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/shuttle-launch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>We FINALLY have BLAST OFF!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-finally-have-blast-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-finally-have-blast-off/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I was a kid and saw the movie Space Camp, I’ve wanted to see a shuttle launch. Last spring when Scott told me that NASA was cancelling their shuttle launch program and their were only 3 left, I began scheming a way to get there and see one.
We planned our entire vacation around the November launch. And while our trip to Florida last November, was one of our best family vacations ever, we didn’t get to see a launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Have Lift Off</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-have-lift-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2011 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-have-lift-off/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I saw the movie Space Camp, it’s been a desire of mine to see a space shuttle launch, up close and in person. I’m not a space nut or anything, but I do find the whole concept of space travel fascinating. And while I don’t have a technical bucket list, so to say, if I did, seeing a launch in person would most definitely be on that list. Which, is why we switched our vacation plans around last fall and took our family to Florida, to try and see the last launch of the Space Shuttle Discovery and one of the last U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3…2…1…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/321/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/321/</guid>
      <description>We chose this year and even this specific week to take our Florida trip because the Space Shuttle Discovery was supposed to make it last launch into space. Both Scott and had always wanted to see a shuttle launch and being as it is one of the last launches ever, we really wanted to take the kids to see this historical event.
The launch was originally planned for Mon Nov 1st.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
