<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fall on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/fall/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fall on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 17:36:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/fall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Fall Favorite</title>
      <link>/posts/a-fall-favorite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-fall-favorite/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love apple picking with my kiddos. 
This year I found a great price on delicious locally grown honey crisp apples at the local grocery store and we enjoyed them all fall and I was so tempted to skip out on apple picking b/c we had already enjoyed such delicious apples this fall. But apple picking is about so much more than the apples for me.
It’s the memories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to the Building!!!</title>
      <link>/posts/back-to-the-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 06:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/back-to-the-building/</guid>
      <description>And so a new year begins… this morning was our first day back at the tutorial. I can’t believe it marks our 6th year of homeschooling. What a blessing this community had been to our family. Here we are starting 2nd, 3rd, and 5th grades!

“And this is my prayer: that your love may abound more and more in knowledge and depth of insight, so that you may be able to discern what is best and may be pure and blameless for the day of Christ, filled with the fruit of righteousness that comes through Jesus Christ—to the glory and praise of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kicking off the Holidays with Family and SNOW</title>
      <link>/posts/kicking-off-the-holidays-with-family-and-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/kicking-off-the-holidays-with-family-and-snow/</guid>
      <description>Nothing like a back seat driver. Especially a 3 year old back seat driver.
At 1 am. On a Snow covered back country road.
[
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/IMG_1958.jpg)
As we slip slided around the roads approaching my parents the other night, I seriously thought we might end up in a ditch and all the while my 3 year old was WIDE awake and chattering non stop about all the snow. He kept saying, “Dad, don’t get in an accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Flip Side</title>
      <link>/posts/the-flip-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-flip-side/</guid>
      <description>The thing that we most fell in love with when we first saw our new house was the back yard. We loved, LOVED the big, private back yard.
Clearly, it was not the fall when we had our love at first sight experience.

We spent the entire day tackling that beloved backyard.

Thankfully, we also made time for a little fun in the leaves.

Leaves can provide a great back drop for some smiley pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supergirl Then and Now</title>
      <link>/posts/supergirl-then-and-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/supergirl-then-and-now/</guid>
      <description>This wasn’t the first time my oldest daughter played the part of Super Girl for Halloween. 4 years ago she had the same role.
2009

2013

She tells me that when she’s 11 she plans to be Super Girl again… guess we are on an every 4 year rotation with this role. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Fall Fun</title>
      <link>/posts/more-fall-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/more-fall-fun/</guid>
      <description>This weekend was full of hayrides and pumpkins. Friday afternoon we went with some families from our 1st graders class to a pumpkin patch. 
It was beautiful. Hay rides are so fun. I am a sucker for them. How can you not have fun riding around on the back of a tractor looking at sunflowers and pumpkins?

My youngest child particularly enjoyed the hay ride and seeing some chickens and goats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fall Tradition</title>
      <link>/posts/a-fall-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 06:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-fall-tradition/</guid>
      <description>Almost every fall, I enjoy taking the kids to the county fair. We’ve been going since my oldest was under a year old. This year my youngest was so super excited. He talked about it for months. “When are we going to go to the fair and see the animals?” We went on Friday morning for the preschool preview day. Then my parents and I returned on Saturday for the girls to perform a gymnastics demo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling for Fall</title>
      <link>/posts/falling-for-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 06:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/falling-for-fall/</guid>
      <description>As much as I hate the cold, I really am a 4 seasons kind of girl. I love the beginning of a new season…. bringing out favorite clothes, decorations, foods, traditions only enjoyed for a season. It’s refreshing and exciting and makes me so grateful for the climate we live in. But, this year, more than most I have been crazy excited about fall. I can’t explain it. But, I’m more giddy than normal about pulling out my jeans and boots and sweaters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Beginning</title>
      <link>/posts/a-new-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-new-beginning/</guid>
      <description>Scott commented the other day that he feels the passage of time more noticeably at the beginning of the school year, rather than on the kids birthdays. I think he’s right.

Especially this year, when I packed up three backpacks and three lunch boxes and lined up 3 kids for pictures at the front door. We have our Kindergartener, on her very first day of school ever. 
Followed by our first grader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Fun 2011</title>
      <link>/posts/fall-fun-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/fall-fun-2011/</guid>
      <description>If we gotta rake and bag all these leaves, we may as well take advantage of the seasonal photo op they provide first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another New School Year</title>
      <link>/posts/another-new-school-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/another-new-school-year/</guid>
      <description>While we’ve been “doing school” at home for the past few weeks for the purpose of reviewing and getting used to the routine, today was the first official start of our new school year.
We homeschool, but also use a tutorial. The kids attend the tutorial twice a week and study at home with me three days a week. So far, I feel it provides the balance our family needs between homeschooling and traditional schooling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even Princesses Have to Work</title>
      <link>/posts/even-princesses-have-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/even-princesses-have-to-work/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Ya Gotta Go….</title>
      <link>/posts/when-ya-gotta-go./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2010 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/when-ya-gotta-go./</guid>
      <description>The outing started out so beautiful and picturesque. The drive there was lovely… leaves just starting to change, sipping my pumpkin spice latte, even the clouds looked “fall like” (amazing how everything looks lovely when the kids aren’t requiring you to referee from the drivers seat…thank you Psalty the Singing Songbook) We got to the farm and the kids happily ate their lunches while I nursed the baby. Then we were off to pick apples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons Learned While Raking Leaves</title>
      <link>/posts/lessons-learned-while-raking-leaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/lessons-learned-while-raking-leaves/</guid>
      <description>1. Two rakes and three kids does not make for a happy equation. 2. Make sure your kids have their shoes securely tied before you begin raking. Otherwise you could rake a pile like this only to have your son tell you it was time to go on a “treasure hunt” to find his missing shoes in said pile.
3. If your going to jump into the pile with the kids, don’t wear baggy jeans.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
