<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>family on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in family on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 18:29:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Another National Park – St. John USVI</title>
      <link>/posts/another-national-park-st.-john-usvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/another-national-park-st.-john-usvi/</guid>
      <description>When we found out the itinerary for the family cruise, Scott and I were super excited to see that the ship would be stopping at St Thomas… this meant that we could take an excursion to St John and visit US Virgin Island National Park!!!
That’s right, another vacation with a sign pic for the circus crew!!

National parks rarely disappoint and St. John was no exception. St John was our family’s favorite day of the vacation (and there were a lot of good days)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birthday in the Caribbean</title>
      <link>/posts/birthday-in-the-caribbean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/birthday-in-the-caribbean/</guid>
      <description>Our youngest daughter turned 10 during our vacation. It was the second year in a row that her birthday fell during our vacation. At first she wasn’t very excited about having to celebrate her birthday away from home….but turns out a Caribbean cruise isn’t too bad a place to celebrate ones birthday.
She has told me in the past that SOMEDAY, she would like to have an ice skating party. Um, Ice skating parties in July can be a tad tricky….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with Grands and Cousins</title>
      <link>/posts/christmas-with-grands-and-cousins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/christmas-with-grands-and-cousins/</guid>
      <description>I LOVE hosting Christmas. And I am so thankful that my extended family allows me that privilege. I am thankful that they all have been willing and able to come year after year so we could share the day together. I don’t take it for granted. I know my parents won’t always be able to travel. I know my BIL and SIL can get stationed so far away that it just doesn’t make a trip to MD possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time with Gana</title>
      <link>/posts/time-with-gana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/time-with-gana/</guid>
      <description>We can not make a trip to the state of California without finding a way to visit Scott’s Nana. Even though California is a big state, and being in California does not necessarily equate being in Nana’s neighborhood. Compared to the east coast, anywhere in California is MUCH, MUCH closer to Nana’s than normal. So, we knew our trip to California, MUST include a visit at Nana’s (or as the kids call her Gana for G reat N ana ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reuniting with Family at Pinnacles National Park</title>
      <link>/posts/reuniting-with-family-at-pinnacles-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/reuniting-with-family-at-pinnacles-national-park/</guid>
      <description>During our trek across California, we wanted to also make time to see some of Scott’s family that live here. Scott’s aunt, uncle, and his cousin and her family live a few hours from Pinnacles National Park and graciously offered to meet us there and spend time with us at the park.

We met at a restaurant called Togo’s… we had never heard of it before, but Scott’s cousin described it as “like subway only better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun in Va</title>
      <link>/posts/fun-in-va/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/fun-in-va/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I escaped down to VA for just shy of 24 hours to spend some time with my SIL and her family. I adore Scott’s sister so a visit to her house was a bright spot in our week. We arrived in the early afternoon with time for me to take the 4 boys to the park while Aunt Karen took the girls to run a few errands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fall Favorite</title>
      <link>/posts/a-fall-favorite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-fall-favorite/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love apple picking with my kiddos. 
This year I found a great price on delicious locally grown honey crisp apples at the local grocery store and we enjoyed them all fall and I was so tempted to skip out on apple picking b/c we had already enjoyed such delicious apples this fall. But apple picking is about so much more than the apples for me.
It’s the memories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With Gratitude</title>
      <link>/posts/with-gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 06:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/with-gratitude/</guid>
      <description>1o years ago Scott and I went before our church and made a commitment before God to raise our son as a disciple of our Lord Jesus Chris. Father’s day weekend, 2004, we rejoiced with our congregation as he was baptized. This was not a sign of our sons salvation. It was the sign of God’s promise to save and cleans sinners who call upon Him. Our son was not saved, but we rejoiced in the seal representing God’s power to save.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Field Trip</title>
      <link>/posts/family-field-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/family-field-trip/</guid>
      <description>This year in History we are studying American History from the explorers to the war on 1812. I love history. It is my favorite part of home schooling. And I am so grateful that we live within driving distance of so many great historical sites. I really wanted to take the kids to Philadelphia for a day trip over spring break. Scott graciously rearranged his work schedule so that he could join us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ringing in a New Year</title>
      <link>/posts/ringing-in-a-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ringing-in-a-new-year/</guid>
      <description>It’s funny how our New Years Eve festivities have changed through the years. Scott and I have never been big party animals, but we did go to downtown Pittsburgh on Dec 31, 1999 to ring in the new millennium with a kiss on the Roberto Clemente bridge. For several years we would watch the fireworks in Annapolis at midnight.
Then we had kids.
And New Years became a stay at home night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Relaxing Christmas</title>
      <link>/posts/a-relaxing-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-relaxing-christmas/</guid>
      <description>It has been a very relaxing Christmas vacation at the circus house. My sister in law and her family came in to town the evening of the 23rd. We had too much fun making cupcakes for the kids for baby Jesus’ bday party on Christmas night. She is an awesome trooper. She happily obliged my request to roll out 19 baby Jesus figurines out of marshmallow fondant at 10:00pm. Seriously, worlds best sister in law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kicking off the Holidays with Family and SNOW</title>
      <link>/posts/kicking-off-the-holidays-with-family-and-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/kicking-off-the-holidays-with-family-and-snow/</guid>
      <description>Nothing like a back seat driver. Especially a 3 year old back seat driver.
At 1 am. On a Snow covered back country road.
[
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/IMG_1958.jpg)
As we slip slided around the roads approaching my parents the other night, I seriously thought we might end up in a ditch and all the while my 3 year old was WIDE awake and chattering non stop about all the snow. He kept saying, “Dad, don’t get in an accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Family is a Growing</title>
      <link>/posts/the-circus-family-is-a-growing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-circus-family-is-a-growing/</guid>
      <description>Since the passing of our beloved dog Maggie, there has been a void in our home. I missed her immensely more than I ever anticipated. And while no dog could ever replace her or what she meant to our family, we felt it time to once again hear the pitter patter of doggie feet in the circus home. But, we needed to wait until we were home from our grand adventure before welcoming a new pup to the family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sweet Celebration</title>
      <link>/posts/a-sweet-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2013 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-sweet-celebration/</guid>
      <description>We celebrated my Dad’s 60th Birthday this week with a party at Hershey park. Dad, Mom, their kids, and their 8 grandkids. 
We had a blast riding the rides, but truly the best part was being together as a family and enjoying watching relationships grow. 

When you’re the oldest cousin sometimes you have to do time in the kiddy rides. He was quite the sport… and was rewarded with roller coaster time in the evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Beautiful Surprise</title>
      <link>/posts/a-beautiful-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-beautiful-surprise/</guid>
      <description>I recall seeing something on Facebook before I went to bed about possible flash freezing or snow. But, I didn’t give it much thought.
When I woke up I peeked behind the curtain to see if anything came of it and I gasped. It was that big white puffy snow that sticks to the branches of trees. My most favorite kind of snowfall. And I laid in bed and watched it fall snuggling with my hubby and kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Muffins and Memories for Breakfast</title>
      <link>/posts/making-muffins-and-memories-for-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/making-muffins-and-memories-for-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>Not sure which I like best about this snapshot, the smiles on the girls faces, my daughters hand in the peanut butter jar or my son sneaking yet another lick out of the bowl….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 5 year old</title>
      <link>/posts/my-5-year-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-5-year-old/</guid>
      <description>She’s my free spirit.
My morning girl.
My glass half full child. She loves to create… always drawing, writing letters or pictures, doodling on any paper she can find. She’s very verbal. When I put her in her room for quiet time, I often think someone has snuck in there with her b/c I hear her talking away—only to discover she’s talking to her self, or reciting things she heard on the radio or TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting</title>
      <link>/posts/reflecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/reflecting/</guid>
      <description>I don’t homeschool because I hate the government. Nor do I homeschool because I think the public school system is all evil. Nor do I homeschool because I want my kids to be smarter than yours. In fact, raising super smart kids isn’t even my main goal of education.
I homeschool because I want to spend the time with my kids. That’s it, in a nut shell.
But, if I may be honest and come clean with you, it’s hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Week!</title>
      <link>/posts/what-a-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 12:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/what-a-week/</guid>
      <description>Spring break was FABULOUS! Oh my, what a treat to have an entire 6 days off of school. It was like a foretaste of summer vacation, (which for this homeschooling family is just around the corner). But before we get back to the books tomorrow, thought I’d share a few of our favorite memories from the week. We crafted…


We made memories with friends


(he had SOO much fun seeing the farm animals at the park with his friends)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Unexpected Treat</title>
      <link>/posts/an-unexpected-treat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/an-unexpected-treat/</guid>
      <description>March was a rough month at the circus. Scott had some deadlines at work which meant he worked a lot of overtime. This happens with his work and we’ve all learned to roll with it, but that doesn’t mean that the long days don’t eventually start to take their toll. On all of us
Which is why it’s been so great the last 2 weeks having Scott around more often. Last Monday he left work at 2 to go to DC with us, on Friday he got home at 5:30 (to which my oldest son asked, “Dad did you take vacation time to get home this early?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DATE DAY</title>
      <link>/posts/date-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/date-day/</guid>
      <description>While we didn’t plan it like this at first, Sunday ended up being date day for each of our 4 kids. Each child ended up with some one on one time with either mom, dad, or Aunt Karen. Good times had by all!
One of the duties of our church deacons is to unlock the church on Sunday mornings. When Scott became a deacon 3 years ago, he started taking one child with him on his deacon duty mornings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love Christmastime</title>
      <link>/posts/i-love-christmastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/i-love-christmastime/</guid>
      <description>Love choosing and cutting down our tree…

Love decorating it and passing on the memories to my children of the precious ornaments hung on our tree…

Love the wonder of the lights…

Love watching them play with toys that only come out once a year…

Love seeing them act out the story of Christ’s birth as they play with their nativity sets

And this year I love listening to the sounds of Christmas carols fill the house as my son plays them on the piano</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Birthday Buddy</title>
      <link>/posts/my-birthday-buddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-birthday-buddy/</guid>
      <description>Growing up, part of me wished for a sister… one to share a room with, share clothes and secrets with…. maybe if I’d have had one, I would know better how to braid my girls hair… I had a great brother, and I would never have traded him for a sister, yet part of me at times felt like I was missing out a little…
When I married Scott I instantly gained in my sister-in-law the sister I had always wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Hour at the Beach</title>
      <link>/posts/an-hour-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/an-hour-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>Most people think that perfect beach weather is a bright sunny day, but we discovered unexpected joy in a trip to the Florida beach on an overcast evening following an afternoon rain storm.

Shuttle launch in the morning, nap in the afternoon, beach in the evening, and free Chick-Fil-A right before bed… it was a perfect day in Florida… totally worth the 32 hours of driving it took to get there and back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Dad</title>
      <link>/posts/my-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-dad/</guid>
      <description>With Fathers Day approaching this weekend and the kids and I brainstorming ways to make it ultra special for the circus dad, I feel it also appropriate to spend some time reflecting on my own father.
Because, when it comes to dad’s, I have been richly blessed. While in the throws of parenthood, I think many a parents wonders, “Is it making a difference? Do my kids even notice?” And the answer is a resounding “Yes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sweet Spring Tradition</title>
      <link>/posts/a-sweet-spring-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-sweet-spring-tradition/</guid>
      <description>When my son was 3, I took him strawberry picking for the first time. It was a special Mommy/Son date prior to the birth of our third child. [
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/IMG_1690.jpg)
 The next year, we returned, but this time it was a family affair.
2009 brought us back to the same farm, this time with friends.

And 2010 found me once again at the fields pregnant, with many small children in tow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Call it Crazy…</title>
      <link>/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</guid>
      <description>This spring I have 3 kids in sports. On 3 different teams. This in addition to the girls both taking gymnastics twice a week and Cub Scouts.
We are busy, busy, busy with games and practices most every night… some nights we’re even double booked.
Many people look at my schedule and call me crazy. Why do you do this to yourself?
The answer is, honestly, two fold. 1. We love it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Many Miles Can We Get Out of This? or Milking This One for ALL its Worth</title>
      <link>/posts/how-many-miles-can-we-get-out-of-this-or-milking-this-one-for-all-itsworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-many-miles-can-we-get-out-of-this-or-milking-this-one-for-all-itsworth/</guid>
      <description>Some of you may remember my post last December (as in 2009) in which I shared one of Scott’s moments of sheer brilliance at the dinner table. Well, I feel the need to tell you that 13 months later and my kids are STILL eating their vegetables to spite their Daddy. I am sure this says something of their character… for which we must spend some time rectifying, but meanwhile my mean spirited little children are eagerly gobbling up their vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Presents Can’t Be Wrapped</title>
      <link>/posts/some-presents-cant-be-wrapped/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/some-presents-cant-be-wrapped/</guid>
      <description>A few moments from this weekend which I wish to savor…
1. My son presenting his gift to his extended family. (One nap time he came up excited to share that he had drawn a picture from each scene in Luke 2. On Christmas he gave one picture to each person. He then laid them all out on the floor and recited the story from memory.)


2. Prepping the Christmas Lasagnas with my daughter… it marked a milestone, in which she was truly helpful in the kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hard Way</title>
      <link>/posts/the-hard-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-hard-way/</guid>
      <description>When cutting down a tree, much like when shopping for a dress, there seems to be an unwritten rule of conduct.
No matter how fabulous it looks, you simply can’t go with the first one you see.
One simply can’t drive to the farm, march down the aisle, and stop at the first decent looking spruce you see.
That would be far too easy. Where would the fun be in that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aren’t They Great?</title>
      <link>/posts/arent-they-great/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/arent-they-great/</guid>
      <description>I didn’t really know my great grandparents. All but one had passed away before I was born and my GG died when I was 2. I have one fleeting memory of her sitting in a chair in my grandparents dining room, but the rest I get from stories and pictures.
October could have been deemed “Great Grandparent Month” at the circus. My children are so blessed to have 4 living great grandparents in their lives today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Dad</title>
      <link>/posts/a-date-with-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-date-with-dad/</guid>
      <description>I got my love of sports from my dad. I can remember watching Pirates games at 5 when he was out of town, just to make me feel closer to him. In high school, my dad would take me to Penn State Football games to watch my cousin play in the Blue Band. I think my dad made sure that we attended every kind of professional sporting event at least once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blessed Assurance</title>
      <link>/posts/blessed-assurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blessed-assurance/</guid>
      <description>5 years ago this month, God took her home to heaven. Though the truth is, Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s/Dementia took Grandma from us long before then. At first she’d just forget what time we’d be leaving for church the next day or when we’d be eating dinner. Later she forgot her grandchildren, children, and eventually even her own identity. Bit by bit the disease took more of her. I remember walking into the care facility the weekend Scott and I had gotten engaged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Hey, Hey, Goodbye!</title>
      <link>/posts/hey-hey-hey-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hey-hey-hey-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>So long summer 2010….
We’ll forever hold you close in our heart for you were the summer that we welcomed dear sweet, squeezable number 4 to our fold.

We enjoyed your lazy hazy days as we spent time playing in our back yard and splashing in our pool…

We enjoyed time with family



We caught our first keeper… and enjoyed time on Nana and Pop’s boat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Mouth of Babes</title>
      <link>/posts/out-of-the-mouth-of-babes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/out-of-the-mouth-of-babes/</guid>
      <description>It’s been one of those days… please tell me you know the ones…took the circus crew to the pediatrician’s for my 3 yr old’s check up. One would have thought by the amount of shrieking that took place in the hall that we were attempting to tie her down and give her 30 shots, when really we just wanted her to take her sandals off and stand on the scale. From that humbling spectacle we were off to the grocery store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America’s Pastime</title>
      <link>/posts/americas-pastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/americas-pastime/</guid>
      <description>I clearly remember the first baseball game I attended with Scott. A coworker had given him the tickets and since we had no plans, we thought, “Sure, why not?” As we drove into Baltimore and hit traffic, Scott was in disbelief, “Could this be game traffic?” He asked. “I had no idea this many people liked baseball.”
Yea… clearly, we aren’t big baseball enthusiasts.
But, thanks to my oldest son, my children are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Like It</title>
      <link>/posts/nothing-like-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nothing-like-it/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we were able to coordinate our schedules and have the opportunity to get together with my brother and his family for some play time. 
What gathering would be complete without a light saber battle?

I loved getting to watch my nephew and nieces play and to observe my brother playing with my children. There is something quite special, and indescribable about watching your children play with your sibling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Plans Change</title>
      <link>/posts/when-plans-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/when-plans-change/</guid>
      <description>When things didn’t work out for us to go camping this weekend as planned, we promised the kids a night of “camping-like” fun at home. Scott came home from work a little early and we cooked up hot dogs and baked beans (a fav here at the circus).
Then we spent the evening fishing on the river.

(more details on the fishing to come later this week)
Camping wouldn’t be complete without Smore’s so we roasted some mallows over the gas stove.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bet You’ve Never Seen an Army Quite Like This One</title>
      <link>/posts/bet-youve-never-seen-an-army-quite-like-this-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bet-youve-never-seen-an-army-quite-like-this-one/</guid>
      <description>Alternate Title: How Your Army Looks When You Have 2 Younger Sisters

I couldn’t help but smile when I looked out the window and saw this scene…makes me laugh when looking at it on the computer as well. Quite a motley crew we have defending the fortress… the leader in his camo’s with his walking stick (or staff as he refers to it), his trusty sidekicks following in their fairy wings, and Uncle Jim covering from behind with the ever elusive fluorescent double barrel shot gun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Table</title>
      <link>/posts/our-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-table/</guid>
      <description>The kids had scattered to the backyard to play while I cleared off the dinner dishes. As I wiped down the dining room table, I couldn’t help but smirk as I looked out over a see of crumbs and wood that is faded in parts due to many a knocked over glass of milk or water. There is an ever present layer of grime that those of you with kids know exactly what I am talking about… something like syrup meets peanut butter meets oatmeal and it just cakes into those nooks and crannies around the edge of the table, giving it that “lived in” feel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crafts that Cross State Lines</title>
      <link>/posts/crafts-that-cross-state-lines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/crafts-that-cross-state-lines/</guid>
      <description>I have many fond childhood memories of working on crafts with my Mema. She’d come to visit and bring her puffy paints and we’d make tee shirts and sweat shirts. Once she even attempted to teach me to crochet… but after a few hours and only a few loops, I opted to let her continue making me anything I wanted crocheted. Now I am grown, with kids of my own, and I must confess, my craft skills don’t look a whole lot different than when I was a kid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess Who’s Back in Town?</title>
      <link>/posts/guess-whos-back-in-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/guess-whos-back-in-town/</guid>
      <description>A year ago today my SIL was due to have her first born, my sweet nephew Eli, who the circus children affectionately call “baby Ewi”. I can’t believe he turns one next week!! He’s in town this week eagerly awaiting the arrival of his daddy from Iraq for his R&amp;amp;R.
I am so thankful that I have a SIL who is willing to travel, b/c even though they live in El Paso, we’ve gotten to see them 4 times this past year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks Mom!</title>
      <link>/posts/thanks-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/thanks-mom/</guid>
      <description>Last week my mom came and spent the week with us. My parents live 5 hrs away from us and even though they do an awesome job of coming to visit for weekends, it always seems like the visit is over before it starts and I am often left wishing I had some more time to spend with them. Having mom here for a week was such a blessing. Not only did she do my laundry for me all week as well as cook our dinners and even do the dishes, but she also shared my days with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Reason I Love Annapolis</title>
      <link>/posts/another-reason-i-love-annapolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 04:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/another-reason-i-love-annapolis/</guid>
      <description>Each year the Blue Angels perform a show at the Naval Academy in celebration of commissioning week. Taking the kids to watch the show has become one of my favorite Annapolis traditions.
 They fly so close you see the pilot!
 Scott says I have to point the crazy small distance between the wings of the first plane and the cockpit of the next – They do corkscrew loops in that formation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Time Traditions</title>
      <link>/posts/spring-time-traditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/spring-time-traditions/</guid>
      <description>For the past 3 years the kids and I have gone to a local strawberry farm to pick our own berries. It is a tradition I cherish. 
We are suburbanites. We don’t even really garden. But, I love for my children to get some real life farm experiences. I love for them to walk down the rows upon rows of plants.

This year my son really went to town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Far We’ve Come</title>
      <link>/posts/how-far-weve-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-far-weve-come/</guid>
      <description>Today I’d like to give a shout out to my maternal grandmother, whom I have lovingly called, “Mema” for as long as I can remember. I have this vivid picture in my mind of me in high school showing her and my Pap how to work our computer. I recall her being completely baffled by it and saying something to the effect of, “You’ll never catch me on that thing!” I remembered there being a picture of the event and when my parents were visiting last week I asked my mom if she knew where it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating the Beginning of the Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/celebrating-the-beginning-of-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/celebrating-the-beginning-of-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>10 years ago we came…spread a blanket out on the sandy shore to watch the sunset. Today we came, with sandwiches and Doritos. This time there was a picnic table where we had spread our blanket. And we watched the sunset mirrored in the faces of our three children.
 
10 years ago it was quiet… we held hands and sat close on the blanket.
Tonight there was sand in our shoes and children squirming….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weekend of Egg-citement!</title>
      <link>/posts/a-weekend-of-egg-citement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-weekend-of-egg-citement/</guid>
      <description>This weekend was full of family fun and excitement! Saturday morning the kids went to the neighborhood egg hunt with both sets of grandparents, while Scott and I went to a wedding reception.

The kids had a blast finding eggs and getting their faces painted. 
(some enjoyed the face paint more than others)
That evening (after my son and I got back from a trip to the the after hours clinic where he was diagnosed with pneumonia), we gathered the grands again to dye Easter eggs with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Fish, Two Fish</title>
      <link>/posts/one-fish-two-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-fish-two-fish/</guid>
      <description>On Friday night we took advantage of the aquarium’s last discount priced Friday night of the season and enjoyed some family fun.

We took 293 pictures during our 3 hours at the aquarium. From those we narrowed down 42 keepers. 
And from those, I have the difficult task of dwindling down some for the blog. 
The kids favorite part of the evening was the dolphin show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eager to Serve</title>
      <link>/posts/eager-to-serve/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 01:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/eager-to-serve/</guid>
      <description>The other day my son told me he wanted to make all of us breakfast the next morning. The only problem with this very sweet gesture was that it was the end of the month and we were at the “creative” stage of the month/meal plan.
Bread? No
Milk? No
Cereal? No
Not much available for a 5 yr old to fix, so I convinced him to wait till after I went grocery shopping on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Valentine’s Tradition</title>
      <link>/posts/our-valentines-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-valentines-tradition/</guid>
      <description>I know that many think Valentine’s day is just a day created by Hallmark. Others think it’s a cheesy holiday for saps. Say what you will, I’ll jump at a chance for a date night with my hubby. And I don’t mind a sweet card and some cinnamon heart candy either.
But, after having kids, Scott and I found it rather difficult to go out for Valentine’s day. Since we don’t hire babysitters, we typically rely on friends or grandparents for babysitting and you can’t ask another couple to babysit for you on Valentine’s Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saying Goodbye</title>
      <link>/posts/saying-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/saying-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>We knew this day was coming for awhile now. In fact, it got pushed back at least twice. But, sadly, the inevitable could not be avoided…after spending 10 weeks on the east coast, aunt Karen and baby Eli headed back to Texas this morning. We have had a blast having them close for so long. It’s been so fun to “pretend” they were local and see them casually for dinners, or at church, or for an overnight every now and then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow Week Math</title>
      <link>/posts/snow-week-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/snow-week-math/</guid>
      <description>Thought you might enjoy a little simple math to recap the week here at the circus. Add together the following totals….
 2 major snowstorms 33 inches of snow fallen 1 official blizzard  
 20 cups of hot chocolate drank 2 types of cookies baked  
 1 Daddy sized igloo built  
 1 sledding hill      0 power outages
 1 sleepover with our cousin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thankful Thursday</title>
      <link>/posts/thankful-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/thankful-thursday/</guid>
      <description>This morning I woke to sounds of my daughter coughing…I stumbled into her room to comfort her and set up her nebulizer, thinking to myself that at least I had gotten 2 hours of uninterrupted sleep. Then my eyes focused a bit more and I took a second look at the clock. It was 6:15, not 1:15!
We slept through the night! I felt much like a new mom the morning after her baby makes it all night without a feeling!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Memories</title>
      <link>/posts/christmas-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/christmas-memories/</guid>
      <description>We have had a wonderful couple of days here at the circus celebrating Jesus’ birthday. We decided to spread the celebrating out over several days rather than cram it all into one day. On Christmas Eve we went to the Children’s service at our church at 4:30. Then we went to Boston Market for our now traditional Christmas Eve dinner before heading back to church for the candlelight service at 6:30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas from the Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/merry-christmas-from-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/merry-christmas-from-the-circus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Since There’s No Place to Go…</title>
      <link>/posts/and-since-theres-no-place-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/and-since-theres-no-place-to-go/</guid>
      <description>Let it Snow, Let it Snow, Let it Snow!!!
Growing up and living in the midAtlantic region means that snow is something we are familiar with, but we don’t encounter on a regular basis. It’s not like we’re living in Houston and a dusting of snow occurs once a decade. But, it also isn’t unreasonable that I don’t go out and purchase snow suits for my kids every winter either. We can typically anticipate seeing snowfall at least once a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weekend of Celebrating</title>
      <link>/posts/a-weekend-of-celebrating/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2009 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-weekend-of-celebrating/</guid>
      <description>What a full and festive weekend we had here at the circus! Friday night Scott and I got all dressed up for a fun and fancy Christmas party! We got to enjoy tasty appetizers, holiday drinks, and the opportunity to sit and chat with old friends. A super way to start the weekend. (Though the baby did not like the cheese dip I ate too much of and I paid for that with an upset stomach later that night).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinary Miracle</title>
      <link>/posts/ordinary-miracle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ordinary-miracle/</guid>
      <description>During this stage of the game, sometimes it’s easy to forget there’s a person growing inside me. Yes, my jeans are fitting more snugly these days and I tend to nod off on the couch each night around 10, but other than that I don’t feel all the different. And so I go through each day making meals, cleaning up messes, and trying to accomplish lessons, errands, and other excursions and quite often forget that all the while there’s a life growing inside of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing Army</title>
      <link>/posts/playing-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/playing-army/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday while the girls spent the day caring for and practicing to hold “baby Ewi” my son spent the day dressed in Camoes and gathering his weapons arsenal to play army with uncle Jim.  I wasn’t exactly sure how much uncle Jim would feel like playing army, since he lives army every day of his life and this was his leave time to see family before deploying to Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon to a Circus Near You</title>
      <link>/posts/coming-soon-to-a-circus-near-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 03:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/coming-soon-to-a-circus-near-you/</guid>
      <description>That’s right folks, we have a new circus member due to arrive here in early June 2010!! And the circus cast couldn’t be more excited!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Peanuts Gang</title>
      <link>/posts/the-peanuts-gang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-peanuts-gang/</guid>
      <description>Those of you that have been visiting the circus for awhile know that I don’t use my kids names on the blogs. I once entertained the idea of pseudonyms but never came up with any I liked. So I’ve pretty much stuck with “ my son,” “my 3 year old daughter” and “my baby” for the past year or so. So far, I have no real intentions to change that, but I did realize last week, that had this been “Life with The Peanuts Gang” or something more catchy, I’d have perfect pseudonyms to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smitten</title>
      <link>/posts/smitten/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 06:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/smitten/</guid>
      <description>This weekend the kids got to meet their newest cousin, “baby Ewi.” They were all quite excited to finally make his acquaintance. The girls have been carrying their dolls around for weeks now feeding, rocking, and putting to sleep their very own “baby Ewi’s.” But my middle child was probably the most smitten, to say the least. She could quite often be found by his side, smiling at him, tickling him and laughing at every noise he made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: A True Gent</title>
      <link>/posts/weekend-thoughts-a-true-gent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekend-thoughts-a-true-gent/</guid>
      <description>Gentleman. I am convinced that if you were to look the word up in the dictionary, you’d have to find a picture of this man.  I first met him at our high school graduation. I remember being taken with the fact that he had one of those sweaters with the reinforced elbows and remarked to Scott how much I loved his genuine “Grandpa sweater” and was convinced he’d be the perfect Worthers Original grandpa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Picking</title>
      <link>/posts/apple-picking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/apple-picking/</guid>
      <description>We came home with so much more than freshly picked apples…

 

we returned with smiles, laughter, and many fond memories
  Visit here or here for more fun with pictures!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holding Fast</title>
      <link>/posts/holding-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/holding-fast/</guid>
      <description>Every now and then at the circus, I find myself enjoying a moment of peace. All too often that peace and quiet is the result of complete and massive destruction going on quietly in another room of the house… say an overflowing sink, or crayon art on the wall, or something else which seems to bind my children in complete quiet. But sometimes, sometimes all is calm and when I fearfully peek around the corner, I catch a moment like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gone Gold Fishing</title>
      <link>/posts/gone-gold-fishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gone-gold-fishing/</guid>
      <description>One Sunday I picked my 2 year old son up from Sunday School and found goldfish in his bin. He had saved some of his snack to share with Mommy and Daddy. My jaw hit the floor. His thoughtfulness both touched and humbled me.
Our church has a fellowship time between services in which you can have some cookies, popcorn, coffee, and lemonade. Once my son was old enough to attend church with us after Sunday School, he got to come join us for the fellowship time as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Than Just the Animals</title>
      <link>/posts/more-than-just-the-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/more-than-just-the-animals/</guid>
      <description>This year in addition to the farm animals, the kids enjoyed some other treats at the county fair. Rides


Cotton Candy
 
And a visit with Spiderman himself

So, what’s your favorite part of the fair? The animals, the rides, the food, or the super heroes?
Visit here or here for more fun with pictures!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun at the County Fair</title>
      <link>/posts/fun-at-the-county-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 03:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/fun-at-the-county-fair/</guid>
      <description>Every fall, since my first born was only 5 months old, I’ve taken my children to the county fair. We don’t by any stretch live in a rural area, so I am sure some of you country folk would laugh and heckle what we call a county fair. But, for my suburbanite children and I, it offers a rare opportunity to see some farm animals up close. It is a fall tradition we look forward to all summer long!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tale of Two Nephews</title>
      <link>/posts/the-tale-of-two-nephews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-tale-of-two-nephews/</guid>
      <description>About 7 months ago we received a phone call that we’d been hoping for, for several years now. My sister in law (Scott’s sister) was pregnant! And there was much rejoicing and squealing at the circus house. Later that same week, we learned that my other sister in law (my brother’s wife) was also expecting a baby! Their due dates were within 2 weeks of each other. And a few months later we found out that they were both expecting boys.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
