<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>friends on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/friends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in friends on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 08:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/friends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Internet Friends</title>
      <link>/posts/internet-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/internet-friends/</guid>
      <description>The internet is a funny thing. I know there are a million and one articles out their all over face book about parents and kids being too distracted… about the negative side effects of being on facebook and blogging… and well, this is not one of them. Nor is this going to be an article in defense of face book or blogging. Truthfully, like just about EVERY SINGLE OTHER MAJOR ISSUE plaguing Momma’s these days, I kinda think moderation is the key… and I also really don’t enjoy debating… so I just kinda stay out of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Week!</title>
      <link>/posts/what-a-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 12:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/what-a-week/</guid>
      <description>Spring break was FABULOUS! Oh my, what a treat to have an entire 6 days off of school. It was like a foretaste of summer vacation, (which for this homeschooling family is just around the corner). But before we get back to the books tomorrow, thought I’d share a few of our favorite memories from the week. We crafted…


We made memories with friends


(he had SOO much fun seeing the farm animals at the park with his friends)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag Day Fun</title>
      <link>/posts/flag-day-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 05:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/flag-day-fun/</guid>
      <description>flag day Noun:
1. June 14, the anniversary of the adoption of the Stars and Stripes as the official US flag in 1777.
2. Justification for purchasing those fun patriotic outfits and crafts b/c “It’s not just for the 4th of July you can use them on Flag Day too”.

The kids enjoyed making their own American Flags out of ribbon. They will serve as a great patriotic decoration in our home through the 4th of July.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Hey, Hey, Goodbye!</title>
      <link>/posts/hey-hey-hey-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hey-hey-hey-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>So long summer 2010….
We’ll forever hold you close in our heart for you were the summer that we welcomed dear sweet, squeezable number 4 to our fold.

We enjoyed your lazy hazy days as we spent time playing in our back yard and splashing in our pool…

We enjoyed time with family



We caught our first keeper… and enjoyed time on Nana and Pop’s boat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Times Two</title>
      <link>/posts/the-circus-times-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-circus-times-two/</guid>
      <description>Because I am used to the chaotic and crazy lifestyle I live, I sometimes forget how it can look to the outsider. It feels normal to me to walk down the street with a gaggle of kids surrounding me, fighting or singing or playing (or all of the above). And when I combine my circus life with that of my close friend (whose blog could also easily be called Life At The Circus as she has 4 boys ages 5, 4, 3 and 3 months) well the chaos only multiplies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Glad That Some Things Never Change</title>
      <link>/posts/so-glad-that-some-things-never-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/so-glad-that-some-things-never-change/</guid>
      <description>Our conversations used to be about teachers and homework, now they are about how we’re going to school our own kids. We used to discuss boys and dream about our future, now many of us are married to those boys and discuss how many children we plan to have. They were the ones I called when Scott first told me he liked me, and when he first kissed me, and when he asked me to be his wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Valentine’s Tradition</title>
      <link>/posts/our-valentines-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-valentines-tradition/</guid>
      <description>I know that many think Valentine’s day is just a day created by Hallmark. Others think it’s a cheesy holiday for saps. Say what you will, I’ll jump at a chance for a date night with my hubby. And I don’t mind a sweet card and some cinnamon heart candy either.
But, after having kids, Scott and I found it rather difficult to go out for Valentine’s day. Since we don’t hire babysitters, we typically rely on friends or grandparents for babysitting and you can’t ask another couple to babysit for you on Valentine’s Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Than Just the Animals</title>
      <link>/posts/more-than-just-the-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/more-than-just-the-animals/</guid>
      <description>This year in addition to the farm animals, the kids enjoyed some other treats at the county fair. Rides


Cotton Candy
 
And a visit with Spiderman himself

So, what’s your favorite part of the fair? The animals, the rides, the food, or the super heroes?
Visit here or here for more fun with pictures!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s so much more friendly with two (or 26)</title>
      <link>/posts/its-so-much-more-friendly-with-two-or-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/its-so-much-more-friendly-with-two-or-26/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;It takes a long time to grow an old friend.&amp;quot; - by John Leonard

Nothing says labor day weekend to me, then a house bursting at the seams with friends. For the past 8 years, we’ve spent labor day with my group of 6 best friends from high school and our growing families. While we’ve changed locations over the years from rustic accommodations, rental homes, and friends houses, some things have remained constant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Sounded Like A Good Idea 3 Months Ago</title>
      <link>/posts/this-sounded-like-a-good-idea-3-months-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/this-sounded-like-a-good-idea-3-months-ago/</guid>
      <description>I saw this line on a tee shirt this weekend at the Annapolis 10 Mile and loved it. But, it cost $27 so I decided instead of buying the tee shirt, I’d make it my blog title. Yea, I was so excited when I signed up back in June to run this race with my high school friends. And somehow 3 months came and went and I ummm didn’t really train adequately for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Real Friend</title>
      <link>/posts/a-real-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 01:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-real-friend/</guid>
      <description>I write to you today with a happy heart. 3 days ago my bloggy world and my real life world collided at lunch in Pittsburgh. As I drove to my meeting place, I was a bit nervous. “What if we run out of things to say? Will she like me when she meets me in person?” It felt quite similar to those first date jitters. (No I wasn’t worried about whether or not she’d kiss me when she dropped me off at the end).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
