<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gymnastics on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/gymnastics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in gymnastics on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 08:52:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/gymnastics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finishing Strong</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/finishing-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/finishing-strong/</guid>
      <description>This weekend marked the end of the gymnastics season for my girls. They both finished the season strong scoring personal bests on more than one event. After the meet I ran into the grocery store to buy some brownie mix to celebrate and I was literally beaming from ear to ear. I felt like I wanted to tell everyone I saw about my girls success. I restrained myself though.
However, I do want to record my emotions and thoughts on here to look back on later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gym Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gym-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 04:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gym-fun/</guid>
      <description>We had a fun weekend at the circus… Friday night swim, Saturday included a trip to the mall to spend birthday money and allowances, Father/Son set up for cub scout day camp week ahead, afternoon at the gym for the girls Open House… and Sunday was filled with a great morning of worship, friends over for the afternoon, and my 7 year old got to perform with her gymnastics friends at the opening of the Baysox game!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Her First Meet (the Good, the Bad, the UGLY)</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/her-first-meet-the-good-the-bad-the-ugly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/her-first-meet-the-good-the-bad-the-ugly/</guid>
      <description>Our 6 year old had her first gymnastics meet this past weekend. I can’t really put into words the feelings of pride I had in watching her. When we first enrolled her in gymnastics 3 years ago, we did so because she was tiny, tough and flexible. It seemed gymnastics might be worth a try for our then 3 year old.
Somewhere in the last 3 years, a light when on inside her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still Playing Catch Up</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/still-playing-catch-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/still-playing-catch-up/</guid>
      <description>Almost done catching up the journal blog on some of the big life happenings round here these past few weeks. Last, but certainly, not least, would be the girls Mini Olympics performances at gymnastics. I LOVE Mini-Olympic time. It’s the one time of year when we get to go on the other side of the glass wall and watch our girls up close. And since I am often entertaining a toddler or taxing around an 8 yr old or running errands, during their practice time, I truly cherish getting the opportunity to watch them perform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monkey See, Monkey Do…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/monkey-see-monkey-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 08:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/monkey-see-monkey-do/</guid>
      <description>Love this picture I snapped of my youngest trying to do a handstand like his sister!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Perfect 10!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-perfect-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-perfect-10/</guid>
      <description>One day my 4 year old came to me with about 8 pony tail holders and asked me to put them all in her hair. I was surprised with how cute it turned out and she was excited when she received compliments on it from her friend at church. After realizing how well it stayed in, I decided it might be worth trying this for gymnastics. (this is it after a night of sleep)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Girl Can Dream</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-girl-can-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 02:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-girl-can-dream/</guid>
      <description>When talking to my oldest daughter about things to look forward to in 2012, I mentioned to her that the Summer Olympics were going to happen in 2012.
“Oh,” she exclaimed, “I’ll be 6, can I be in the Olympics?”
I told her that when she was 6 she can try out for the gymnastics team at her gym, but she has to be 16 to try out for the Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proud Momma</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proud-momma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proud-momma/</guid>
      <description>My girls had their Mini Olympics Show yesterday afternoon and I gotta tell you, I was one proud Momma as I watched them perform. Their class did a floor routine (which was super cute to watch) and then each girl had a chance to perform on the bars, trampoline, and tumble track. 


The event concluded with a trip to the medal stand for each girl and then the opportunity to pose for pictures afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Olympics 2024</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-olympics-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-olympics-2024/</guid>
      <description>Mark your calendars now for the 2024 Olympics… our little gymnast has started training! 
I must say I have truly enjoyed watching her at her gymnastics class this year. Since I can’t even do a forward roll, I am always so amazed as I watch her do back rolls or “flip overs” on the bars. Neither Scott nor I did gymnastics growing up so it is not a sport we would have normally thought of but she is so short, strong and flexible (remember she still sleeps folded in half) that we just had to get her involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Her Chance to Shine</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/her-chance-to-shine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/her-chance-to-shine/</guid>
      <description>After spending many hours on the sidelines watching her big brother play soccer or baseball, today my middle child had a chance to shine in a sport of her own…
GYMNASTICS

And my fearless and flexible tumbler, LOVED it, much like I anticipated she would. 
She told me at the end of class, “Mommy, I’m a gymnast!”
Watch out Shawn Johnson, the 2020 Olympics could be all hers!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
