<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cooking on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/cooking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cooking on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 10:28:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/cooking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Newest Kitchen Helper</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-newest-kitchen-helper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-newest-kitchen-helper/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Cooking at the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/whats-cooking-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/whats-cooking-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>I have found that by planning my meals for the month, I can drastically reduce our families grocery spending. It takes time and a whole lot of effort though. And to be honest the past several months I wasn’t so good about it. But, then Scott and I sat down and took a look at our spending. And we realized that we needed to be a whole lot better about sticking to our budget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Thing I was Planning on Baking</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/good-thing-i-was-planning-on-baking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/good-thing-i-was-planning-on-baking/</guid>
      <description>What is it about stick of butter that my children find so irresistible? Why is it when I have the forethought to set the butter out on the counter to soften, my children see it as invitation to squish it? At least this time, they didn’t use their fingers and smear it all over the counters.
  Thankfully, it wasn’t butter to be spread on bread, but instead I am hoping to bake some cookies this afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For all You Food Network Fans</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/for-all-you-food-network-fans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/for-all-you-food-network-fans/</guid>
      <description>Ever watched one of those food network shows? Paula Dean, Giada, Rachel Ray, Emeril… funny how different their kitchens look from mine….I’ve got kids fighting, the dog barking, and one hand balancing my toddler on my hip, while the other puts dinner in the oven and calls Scott to find out what time he’ll be leaving work. Meanwhile I am emptying the dish washer, wiping up spills, and maybe.. maybe checking face book.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
