<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>summer on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/summer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in summer on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 08:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/summer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>So Long Summer…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-long-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 08:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-long-summer/</guid>
      <description>Ever since we signed our 4 year old up for soccer, he has asked when fall is… and my answer is always, “After Labor Day.”
So with Labor Day behind us, I guess I must officially bid farewell to summer.
If I am honest, summer break is one of my favorite parts of homeschooling… we work hard during the school year, but when our curriculum is done mid to late May, we play hard until fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Class Clown</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-class-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 05:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-class-clown/</guid>
      <description>It seems to be that when you have more than one child… their differences sometimes seem to shine out, and they can kind of fall into different roles. The peacemaker, the organizer…. not that I am advocating type casting your children or anything. I know they can all play different roles at different times.
However, when I asked the kids to pose for a picture at the strawberry patch the other day, my youngest displayed his true colors…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Date with my Son</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-date-with-my-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-date-with-my-son/</guid>
      <description>6 Flags Amusement park offered a free ticket to any K-6 grade student that registered for their Read to Succeed program and completed 6 hrs of non school required reading. As a bonus, the teacher who enrolled the student also got a free ticket. So, that meant this home schooling momma got a ticket for herself and her son to 6 Flags.
I kept track of his reading in the spring and when he completed 6 hrs of recreational reading, unannounced to him, I registered him for the free ticket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He’s Still my Baby</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hes-still-my-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hes-still-my-baby/</guid>
      <description>My lil man reached a major milestone today as he played in the sand. We’ve been going to the beach, splashing in the water and playing in the sand all summer long. And all summer long he has wanted to put fist full upon fist full of sand into his mouth. You’d think eventually cause and effect would come in to play, but he never seemed to mind the mouth full of grit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Hour at the Beach</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-hour-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/an-hour-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>Most people think that perfect beach weather is a bright sunny day, but we discovered unexpected joy in a trip to the Florida beach on an overcast evening following an afternoon rain storm.

Shuttle launch in the morning, nap in the afternoon, beach in the evening, and free Chick-Fil-A right before bed… it was a perfect day in Florida… totally worth the 32 hours of driving it took to get there and back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag Day Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/flag-day-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 05:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/flag-day-fun/</guid>
      <description>flag day Noun:
1. June 14, the anniversary of the adoption of the Stars and Stripes as the official US flag in 1777.
2. Justification for purchasing those fun patriotic outfits and crafts b/c “It’s not just for the 4th of July you can use them on Flag Day too”.

The kids enjoyed making their own American Flags out of ribbon. They will serve as a great patriotic decoration in our home through the 4th of July.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sum, Sum, Summa time!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sum-sum-summa-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/sum-sum-summa-time/</guid>
      <description>With temperatures in the nineties this weekend and heat indexes in the hundreds, I’d swear we were celebrating the 4th of July this weekend rather than Memorial Day. We seemed to have gone from winter to summer, with very little spring in between. Wasn’t it just a few short weeks ago we were bundled up at baseball practice in our coats and hats? 
The kids don’t seem to mind a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Hey, Hey, Goodbye!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hey-hey-hey-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hey-hey-hey-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>So long summer 2010….
We’ll forever hold you close in our heart for you were the summer that we welcomed dear sweet, squeezable number 4 to our fold.

We enjoyed your lazy hazy days as we spent time playing in our back yard and splashing in our pool…

We enjoyed time with family



We caught our first keeper… and enjoyed time on Nana and Pop’s boat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Family Business</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-family-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-family-business/</guid>
      <description>The cool crisp mornings we’ve had lately signal that fall is near. So, this weekend I made good on a summertime promise I made to the kids. We carried out the folding table and chairs…decided on a fair price for our product and made some signs.

While the kids began chanting “25 cent lemonade,” I quickly stirred some country time and water.
They eagerly watched for cars and walkers and when they saw them they’d enthusiastically wave and chant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s to You Simon and Garfunkel</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/heres-to-you-simon-and-garfunkel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/heres-to-you-simon-and-garfunkel/</guid>
      <description>If summer could have a theme song, well then I think this would be mine for the summer of 2010.
 Slow down, you move too fast. You got to make the morning last. Just kicking down the cobble stones. Looking for fun and feelin&#39; groovy.
Ba da, Ba da, Ba da, Ba da&amp;hellip;Feelin&#39; Groovy.
Hello lamp-post, What cha knowin&#39;? I&amp;rsquo;ve come to watch your flowers growin&#39;. Ain&amp;rsquo;t cha got no rhymes for me?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
