<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marriage on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/marriage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marriage on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 06:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/marriage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Anniversary Date in DC</title>
      <link>/posts/anniversary-date-in-dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 06:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/anniversary-date-in-dc/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we snuck away for to celebrate our anniversary. We spent the night in the nations capital. And we had a blast. No agenda. No plan. Just hanging out in DC just the two of us. Confession: I love the monuments in DC. Living in MD, I have seen them a lot. Growing up summer visits from cousins ALWAYS meant trips into DC. And I know they are very touristy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love and Marriage</title>
      <link>/posts/love-and-marriage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/love-and-marriage/</guid>
      <description>I remember when my son was in kindergarten he came home and told me he asked a girl in his class to marry him. “What did she say?” I responded. “No. So I told her,why don’t we wait till we are older to decide.” I cautioned him that should he ever want to propose again, he should talk to us first and then talk to the girls parents first.
I remember this so vividly b/c I knew, I knew there would come a day when he would balk at such a discussion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tee Shirt Love</title>
      <link>/posts/tee-shirt-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tee-shirt-love/</guid>
      <description>Scott has been a huge help and support to me this week… taking time off of work so I can rest up (apparently surgery takes more out of you, then you anticipate)… driving the kids to their activities, helping with school, and meals and cleaning up… So, today, I thought I’d show my appreciation and wear my “My Husband Rocks” tee shirt. My 7 year old looked at my shirt, read it aloud and said, “So, why did you wear that today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sparkle</title>
      <link>/posts/sparkle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sparkle/</guid>
      <description>One of the things I came across while packing for our move was a bottle of jewelry cleaner. As soon as I found it, I scrubbed my wedding rings. As I did, I realized it had been quite awhile since I had cleaned my rings. As I scrubbed, the grime became more and more apparent. I couldn’t believe how brilliantly they sparkled after I cleaned them. When Scott first came me my engagement ring, I couldn’t take my eyes off of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Things I Love About You</title>
      <link>/posts/11-things-i-love-about-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2012 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/11-things-i-love-about-you/</guid>
      <description>Scott, in honor of our anniversary this weekend, I compiled a list of 11 things I love about you.
1. You’re a dreamer.
2. Your not afraid to go for the crazy (take 4 kids on a 22 hour car ride to see a 2 minute rocket launch… sure thing…stop by Times Square for hot dogs on the way to CT for a wedding with 2 toddlers and a very pregnant wife, “I’m in!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just the 2 of us in Chicago</title>
      <link>/posts/just-the-2-of-us-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/just-the-2-of-us-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I got away last week, just the 2 of us, for 3 nights in the Windy City. It was a belated 10 year anniversary gift to ourselves.
And it was WON-DER-FUL!!
The city of Chicago is beautiful. The buildings are unique and interesting… truly works of art in and of themselves. We had so much fun walking around the city and taking in its beauty. The weather was overcast and it rained off and on while we were there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Still the One…</title>
      <link>/posts/your-still-the-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/your-still-the-one/</guid>
      <description>It was one of the best days of my life. Even though it seemed like the time would never arrive, finally it was time. The doors opened, and Scott’s best friend began playing Trumpet Voluntary on his trumpet. And dad and I began our walk down the aisle. I will never forget the look of love in Scott’s eyes as I walked toward him down that aisle. I have a picture of his face on my dresser so I can remember it always.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
