<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>holidays on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/holidays/</link>
    <description>Recent content in holidays on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 09:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/holidays/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Christmastime in the Big Apple</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmastime-in-the-big-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmastime-in-the-big-apple/</guid>
      <description>About a month ago my youngest asked when we would see the Statue of Liberty again. We visited it a few years ago on our way to our Boston Vacation, and it has been a highlight memory of our youngest child ever since. He loves when we spot it on tv or in a picture somewhere. I replied, “Probably the next time we go to New York City.” To which he of course replied, “When can we go to New York City again?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun in Va</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fun-in-va/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fun-in-va/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I escaped down to VA for just shy of 24 hours to spend some time with my SIL and her family. I adore Scott’s sister so a visit to her house was a bright spot in our week. We arrived in the early afternoon with time for me to take the 4 boys to the park while Aunt Karen took the girls to run a few errands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cherishing These Days</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cherishing-these-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cherishing-these-days/</guid>
      <description>It’s hard to believe that my youngest will be school age next year. Seriously, how did that happen? Sometimes when we drop the big kids off at their tutorial on “school at the building days” he will pause outside the Kindergarten room and tell me, “That’s where I go next year Momma and then you will be all alone and so sad.” And my heart kinda breaks a little. Because he is right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Preview</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pumpkin-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pumpkin-preview/</guid>
      <description>We carved our pumpkins tonight….


My second born has always been my tactile child. She loves getting her hands messy… she’s the one who loves the feel of dirt on her skin and apparently is also fond of pumpkin guts on her fingers. She happily squished and sorted seeds.

Her sister was less thrilled with the feel of pumpkin guts on her hands.

But,we were all happy with how the jack-o-lanterns turned out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Field Trip Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/family-field-trip-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/family-field-trip-fun/</guid>
      <description>When we switched out history curriculum this year so that the whole family studies the same period of history (with varying level of work catered to their age level), one of the reasons I was MOST excited was that our field trips would be applicable to all. When our tutorial gave off for Presidents Day, I was eager to take advantage of the day free of book work to go on a field trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hearts and Snow</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hearts-and-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/hearts-and-snow/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the snow fall cancelling our evening activities, we had time to bake and decorate some heart shaped cookies last night.

(it should be noted after my previous post on Red Lake 40… that these cookies were decorated with all natural food dye from Whole Foods)

The snow looked magical as we watched it fall outside our windows. I called the kids down from bed to watch it for a bit and then let them sleep with their blinds open so they could fall asleep watching it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ringing in a New Year</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ringing-in-a-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ringing-in-a-new-year/</guid>
      <description>It’s funny how our New Years Eve festivities have changed through the years. Scott and I have never been big party animals, but we did go to downtown Pittsburgh on Dec 31, 1999 to ring in the new millennium with a kiss on the Roberto Clemente bridge. For several years we would watch the fireworks in Annapolis at midnight.
Then we had kids.
And New Years became a stay at home night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Tradition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-favorite-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-favorite-tradition/</guid>
      <description>We got our tree today!!! 
We started decorating the house yesterday, but it wasn’t quite right without the tree. I don’t think our three year old remembers the Christmas tree b/c after we cut it down and tied it to our van he asked, “Can we keep it in our yard as our Christmas tree?” He had no idea it would go in the house. And then when we added lights, he was beyond excited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kicking off the Holidays with Family and SNOW</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kicking-off-the-holidays-with-family-and-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kicking-off-the-holidays-with-family-and-snow/</guid>
      <description>Nothing like a back seat driver. Especially a 3 year old back seat driver.
At 1 am. On a Snow covered back country road.
[
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/IMG_1958.jpg)
As we slip slided around the roads approaching my parents the other night, I seriously thought we might end up in a ditch and all the while my 3 year old was WIDE awake and chattering non stop about all the snow. He kept saying, “Dad, don’t get in an accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supergirl Then and Now</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/supergirl-then-and-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/supergirl-then-and-now/</guid>
      <description>This wasn’t the first time my oldest daughter played the part of Super Girl for Halloween. 4 years ago she had the same role.
2009

2013

She tells me that when she’s 11 she plans to be Super Girl again… guess we are on an every 4 year rotation with this role. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 1st Dessert</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/april-1st-dessert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/april-1st-dessert/</guid>
      <description>I told the kids I made them brownies for dessert tonight. 
They were a little disappointed to discover the brown
E’s I made for them. 
April Fools!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hunt</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Countless “winter” afternoons were spent sporting flip flops, eating picnic lunches outside, soaking in the warmth of the sun’s rays. And I loved every minute of it, while also inwardly fearing a return of cold weather. I so hate that time of year when you have to keep both warm and cold weather clothes in your drawers because you never know what the weather will do. I love it when you can confidently box up last seasons clothes and fully embrace the new season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number 1 Sign Your Family Might Be a Little Obsessed with Football…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/number-1-sign-your-family-might-be-a-little-obsessed-with-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/number-1-sign-your-family-might-be-a-little-obsessed-with-football/</guid>
      <description>Since it was the first day of spring this week, I decided it might be time to take down the Valentine’s wreath from my door and switch it for my Easter one. Today I thought I’d take it a step further and even pull out my spring/Easter/”leave up till I pull out the red/white/blue decorations for summer around Memorial day” decorations…as I did the girls were ooing and aahing over the little eggs, flowers, chicks and lambs…Then my 6 year old daughter saw the bunny my mother in law had given me a few years ago and said, _“Awh look at the bunny and it’s even holding a football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irish Eyes are Smiling</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/irish-eyes-are-smiling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/irish-eyes-are-smiling/</guid>
      <description>When you start the day with a bowl of our traditional St Patty’s day breakfast of Lucky Charms, you know it’s going to be a good day.
And today was just that.
I was so excited to have St Patrick’s Day fall on a Saturday this year. After our magically delicious breakfast, Scott took the big 3 to my son’s baseball practice. I stayed home to make our lunch (shamrock shaped soft pretzels) while our youngest took a morning cat nap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March Holidays Part 1</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/march-holidays-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/march-holidays-part-1/</guid>
      <description>I had high hopes for Feb with plans in the works for Mardi Gras and Leap Year celebrations, but the stomach bug and a business trip and well the busyness of life, put those on the back burner… perhaps another next time…
March is full of celebrations of its own, so no time to mourn the missed holidays of February… We started off with Dr Seuss’ Birthday on March 2. We had green eggs and</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presidents Day at the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/presidents-day-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/presidents-day-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>Can I make a little confession? I was going to skip Presidents Day… truthfully, it’s a holiday that I’ve only really given a nod to in the past, no real hoopla. And this year it falls right before Fat Tuesday and the end of Mardi Gras… Mardi Gras is another holiday I’ve skipped in the past but for some reason this year I decided to educate the kids on New Orleans food and culture as well as jazz music… (I think it’s b/c of these Family Fun magazine recipes)…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, I know I am a sap…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/yes-i-know-i-am-a-sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/yes-i-know-i-am-a-sap/</guid>
      <description>I love holidays… all holidays… as in Chinese New Year… Ground Hog Day… Mardi Gras…St Patty’s Day… Cinco De Mayo… give me a reason to make a themed meal and I’m in. I love celebrating life with my family.
So, yes… I go a little crazy for Valentine’s Day… even if it is a holiday created by Hallmark…. I’ll still serve heart shaped food for every meal and dress my kids in red.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watching the Christmas Story Unfold</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/watching-the-christmas-story-unfold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/watching-the-christmas-story-unfold/</guid>
      <description>When I saw the sign on the side of highway advertising a Live Nativity, I was instantly interested. I’ve never seen one and thought it would be a great experience for the kids. When talking to a friend I found out more details and made plans to bring them. It was a simple production, put on by a small community church on a cold winter’s night on the side of a busy highway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Best House Yet</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-best-house-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-best-house-yet/</guid>
      <description>We decorated our gingerbread house this weekend…before Christmas this year—astonishing, I know.
The big 3 had a fabulous time.


Unfortunately, our youngest found the experience quite confusing and a tad frustrating. “Why, oh why, aren’t they letting me eat that candy?”

I might have snuck the lil guy a few pieces of candy while they were busy working.


The kids were quite proud of their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Tuba Christmas</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/merry-tuba-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/merry-tuba-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is without a doubt my favorite time of year. I’ve already shared in my last post how I love all the things about Christmas. And I do, even the shopping, baking, prepping for company… I love it all. In fact when Christmas actually gets here I am always a little sad, because truth be told I love the season, the anticipation, the preparation so much that I am sad to see it end when the actual day of Christmas arrives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love Christmastime</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-love-christmastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/i-love-christmastime/</guid>
      <description>Love choosing and cutting down our tree…

Love decorating it and passing on the memories to my children of the precious ornaments hung on our tree…

Love the wonder of the lights…

Love watching them play with toys that only come out once a year…

Love seeing them act out the story of Christ’s birth as they play with their nativity sets

And this year I love listening to the sounds of Christmas carols fill the house as my son plays them on the piano</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Month of Giving Thanks</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-month-of-giving-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-month-of-giving-thanks/</guid>
      <description>This year I decided to follow the example of other friends on face book and post something each day on my status that I was thankful for. It was a really fun way to stop and focus on giving thanks each day. I decided to cut and paste my status updates into a blog post for today so I could record these to look back on later. Here they are starting with today and going backwards to the beginning of November….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Role Play</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/role-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/role-play/</guid>
      <description>Our oldest daughter had a little fun getting into her character for Halloween. When posing for pictures in their costumes, she decided to fully act out the part of Snow White.

I think my favorite part of the reenactment was when she asked us to take her picture sleeping with the apple. &amp;quot;Skip the ol posing by the door with the trick or treat basket, we’ll go for playing dead on the floor with an apple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag Day Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/flag-day-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 05:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/flag-day-fun/</guid>
      <description>flag day Noun:
1. June 14, the anniversary of the adoption of the Stars and Stripes as the official US flag in 1777.
2. Justification for purchasing those fun patriotic outfits and crafts b/c “It’s not just for the 4th of July you can use them on Flag Day too”.

The kids enjoyed making their own American Flags out of ribbon. They will serve as a great patriotic decoration in our home through the 4th of July.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When You Care Enough to Send the Very Best</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-you-care-enough-to-send-the-very-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 06:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-you-care-enough-to-send-the-very-best/</guid>
      <description>Before having kids, I used to go to my local Hallmark store and browse the selection of cards. It seemed there was always SOMEONE who could benefit from a little Hallmark cheer. I love cards. LOVE them… and prior to having kids I was pretty good about buying and sending them.
Somehow though bringing 2, then 3, now 4 active kids into a card store lost its appeal… something about them reaching out of their strollers and pulling card after card onto the floor while I was trying to find that perfect card made it loose its charm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Chicken Pot Pie Sent Me Into a Sad Little State of Panic and Despair</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-chicken-pot-pie-sent-me-into-a-sad-little-state-of-panic-and-despair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-chicken-pot-pie-sent-me-into-a-sad-little-state-of-panic-and-despair/</guid>
      <description>I asked Scott to explain Pi to the kids yesterday as we ate our Chicken Pot Pie in celebration of Pi day (3/14). I knew he would do a better job than I, as I would have probably just showed them the symbol and told them it equaled 3.14
Because folks, that pretty much sums up what I know about Pi.
He however drew them a picture of a circle, taught them about diameter and then went on to tell them that you need a little (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrations</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/celebrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/celebrations/</guid>
      <description>The time is 11:45pm. One tired hubby is doing his best to fall asleep so he can get up the next morning and go to work and provide for his family. Meanwhile his “endearing wife” keeps him awake chattering away about the fun festivities she has planned for the following week.
Because he is a good man, he kindly listens as I tell him about National Pancake Day and why it is celebrated, when I know that truthfully, he wants nothing more than to roll over and fall asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2010</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-2010/</guid>
      <description>Just a few of my favorite pictures of our fun on Christmas morning!
Someone got a lil sleepy waiting up for Santa

The grandparents eagerly waiting for the kids to wake up on Christmas morning.

Does this capture the excitement of Christmas morning, or what? (I wish knew what had just been opened)
 
This tender moment was brought to you by “Lego Star Wars for Wii”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hard Way</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-hard-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-hard-way/</guid>
      <description>When cutting down a tree, much like when shopping for a dress, there seems to be an unwritten rule of conduct.
No matter how fabulous it looks, you simply can’t go with the first one you see.
One simply can’t drive to the farm, march down the aisle, and stop at the first decent looking spruce you see.
That would be far too easy. Where would the fun be in that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apparently he isn’t the most famous of all</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/apparently-he-isnt-the-most-famous-of-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/apparently-he-isnt-the-most-famous-of-all/</guid>
      <description>I got a funny e-mail from my mom this morning. She told me to set the DVR to record Rudolph tonight b/c apparently my 3 yr old needed a refresher in holiday pop culture. According to my mom…
“We were walking in the mall on Black Friday. We went to the Build a Bear shop which had been transformed into Santa&amp;rsquo;s Workshop for Christmas. They had stuffed snowmen and deer and Santa bears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A FULL Heart</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-full-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-full-heart/</guid>
      <description>I have had a fabulous week. We took the week off of school, and aren’t going anywhere but here. This weekend we did some much needed, long overdue DEEP CLEANING. I literally stayed in my PJs till 5:00 on Saturday and started in my bedroom cleaning and organizing till the dust bunnies under my bed were all sucked up by the Dyson! (in the middle of this day when my house looked like a tornado hit, the breakfast dishes were still on the table and I was still in my pjs my MIL showed up to take the kids for a few hours… a blessing so valuable and appreciated I swallowed my pride and opened the door so she could pick up the kiddos)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started a Lil Early This Year</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/getting-started-a-lil-early-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/getting-started-a-lil-early-this-year/</guid>
      <description>Every year I have high hopes for being on top of things in the Christmas season. Last year, as hard as I tried, I was no where near on top of things. In fact, my Christmas cards became New Years cards and weren’t even mailed till the middle of January. 
This year, however, I have high hopes. Thanks to a special promotion from Shutterfly, I have already designed my Christmas cards!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bet Your Harvest Party Never Had One of These</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bet-your-harvest-party-never-had-one-of-these/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bet-your-harvest-party-never-had-one-of-these/</guid>
      <description>We decided to add a little pizazz to our normal morning chaos as we got ready to leave for our tutorial today. Since it’s the last day the tutorial is meeting before Thanksgiving, they had a Harvest Party at the end of the day and the children were encouraged to come in costume.
My son went as an Indian and his little sister went as a Pilgrim. (costumes courtesy of Mommy’s costume bin from her school days… I was Pocahontas one year for Halloween and the “Pilgrim” dress was actually a costume from a church play).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Own Little Rebel Alliance</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-own-little-rebel-alliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 03:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-own-little-rebel-alliance/</guid>
      <description>I’ve always wanted a little Yoda for Halloween.

Queen Amidala made an appearance

We also had Padme Amidala

And, of course,Luke Skywalker.

We’re pretty much, eating, breathing, sleeping Star Wars…24/7 round here these days</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiver Me Timbers!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shiver-me-timbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shiver-me-timbers/</guid>
      <description>Get out your 2011 calendars and circle Sept 19th. It is International Talk Like a Pirate day. I assure you it is one holiday you do not want to miss. (If, by chance, you happen to get the date wrong, ahem, and celebrate it on the 20th per say, no worries, your children won’t know the difference and you can still have just as good of a time). 
We celebrated in 2008, but sadly missed the holiday last year… something about being in my first trimester and starting my first year of home schooling, caused me to forego the optional holidays last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incase You Were Wondering…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/incase-you-were-wondering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/incase-you-were-wondering/</guid>
      <description>This would be why more than one of my children thought chicken came from cows…
 Cow Appreciation Day at Chick-Fil-A is a tradition here at the circus.
We start them young with our indoctrination!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday America</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/happy-birthday-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/happy-birthday-america/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How My Son Decided We Should Celebrate Memorial Day</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-my-son-decided-we-should-celebrate-memorial-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 18:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-my-son-decided-we-should-celebrate-memorial-day/</guid>
      <description>I’ll be honest. When I think Memorial Day celebration, I typically think cook outs and swimming pools. This year being 9 mths preggo, we didn’t really make any big plans for Memorial Day weekend. Scott grilled for us several times and even got out this smoker and cooked a chicken for Monday’s dinner. We went to the park, did a few things around the house and basically took it easy all weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Memorial Day</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/remembering-memorial-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/remembering-memorial-day/</guid>
      <description>In honor of Memorial Day, I thought I’d repost this post from Jan of 09 in which my son first learned of the ultimate sacrifice many of our soldiers make for our country. As we were discussing what Memorial Day was this week, my son asked what we were going to do to celebrate. “So, are we going to the memorial in Annapolis then?” I realized that sadly, Memorial Day typically comes and goes without much thought at all to why we have the day off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weekend of Egg-citement!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-weekend-of-egg-citement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-weekend-of-egg-citement/</guid>
      <description>This weekend was full of family fun and excitement! Saturday morning the kids went to the neighborhood egg hunt with both sets of grandparents, while Scott and I went to a wedding reception.

The kids had a blast finding eggs and getting their faces painted. 
(some enjoyed the face paint more than others)
That evening (after my son and I got back from a trip to the the after hours clinic where he was diagnosed with pneumonia), we gathered the grands again to dye Easter eggs with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Step Closer</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-step-closer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2010 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-step-closer/</guid>
      <description>Since before each of my children were born, my hearts deepest desire has been for them to know the Lord Jesus as their Savior. My son has demonstrated to us numerous times through various conversations that he recognizes he is a sinner and Christ died on the cross to forgive his sins.  My girls have not come to that point yet, but this Easter season we got one step closer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Patty’s Day Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/st-pattys-day-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/st-pattys-day-fun/</guid>
      <description>I typically enjoy donning some green (and forcing encouraging my family to do the same) and serving an Irish fare on the 17th of March. I thought I’d share some of our traditions with you today, as well as some new recipes I got from some friends on face book, in case you wanted to try some at your home on Wednesday. I’m always eager to try new traditions and activities at the circus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for Easter</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/preparing-for-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/preparing-for-easter/</guid>
      <description>I love Christmas. One of the things I love most is that it is celebrated for an entire month. I love the time of preparation and the focus on Christ’s birth.
But without Easter, Christmas truly is meaningless. As awesome as it is that God sent his only Son to earth, it is only the first part of the story. His death on the cross for our sins and the fact that he rose from the dead 3 days later is what gives not just this story, but every life story purpose and meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Valentine’s Tradition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-valentines-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-valentines-tradition/</guid>
      <description>I know that many think Valentine’s day is just a day created by Hallmark. Others think it’s a cheesy holiday for saps. Say what you will, I’ll jump at a chance for a date night with my hubby. And I don’t mind a sweet card and some cinnamon heart candy either.
But, after having kids, Scott and I found it rather difficult to go out for Valentine’s day. Since we don’t hire babysitters, we typically rely on friends or grandparents for babysitting and you can’t ask another couple to babysit for you on Valentine’s Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where was Momma?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/where-was-momma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 05:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/where-was-momma/</guid>
      <description>As I was looking over the pictures we took on Christmas Day in order to make my collage, I commented to Scott that it appears I wasn’t there for Christmas morning as I couldn’t find any shots with me in them. Then I realized I was wrong as I spotted this picture.

Whew…. good thing I was wrong… there is photographic evidence of my existence at Christmas 2009. :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Memories</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-memories/</guid>
      <description>We have had a wonderful couple of days here at the circus celebrating Jesus’ birthday. We decided to spread the celebrating out over several days rather than cram it all into one day. On Christmas Eve we went to the Children’s service at our church at 4:30. Then we went to Boston Market for our now traditional Christmas Eve dinner before heading back to church for the candlelight service at 6:30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas from the Circus</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/merry-christmas-from-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/merry-christmas-from-the-circus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procrastinate Much?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/procrastinate-much/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/procrastinate-much/</guid>
      <description>Only 2 days till Christmas and my to do list today looks like this.
 Clean bathroom- scrub toilet, scrub sink, scrub tub and tile (I write each individually so I can feel more satisfaction when I am done by crossing off 4 things instead of one) Clean guestroom- My parents always say, don’t worry or stress about cleaning up for them. And I appreciate the fact that I can keep things real and not stress out, but… I think I need to clear off a place for them to sleep, don’t you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How this Christmas is Different</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-this-christmas-is-different/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2009 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-this-christmas-is-different/</guid>
      <description>Megan is hosting her annual Sharing Christmas carnival where bloggers can invite their readers into their homes for a sort of Christmas Open House. I tend to use the same decorations each year in pretty much the same locations and since I posted on those here last year, I am not going to redo the same post. Instead I thought I would post on how things are different this year at the circus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weekend of Celebrating</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-weekend-of-celebrating/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2009 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-weekend-of-celebrating/</guid>
      <description>What a full and festive weekend we had here at the circus! Friday night Scott and I got all dressed up for a fun and fancy Christmas party! We got to enjoy tasty appetizers, holiday drinks, and the opportunity to sit and chat with old friends. A super way to start the weekend. (Though the baby did not like the cheese dip I ate too much of and I paid for that with an upset stomach later that night).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: That’s What It’s All About</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/weekend-thoughts-thats-what-its-all-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/weekend-thoughts-thats-what-its-all-about/</guid>
      <description>I am reposting this post from last year because, it’s still what it’s all about and I love reminding myself of that as often as possible.  That’s What It’s All About… December 20, 2008
in Weekend Thoughts
As we were getting ready to go to the tree lighting ceremony downtown my son asked, “Mom, can I tell Santa that he is not what Christmas is all about?”
I love that as we anticipate Christmas, my kids know that we are preparing to celebrate Jesus’ birth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Cookie Exchange: Saltine Brittle</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-cookie-exchange-saltine-brittle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-cookie-exchange-saltine-brittle/</guid>
      <description>This year, I was looking for something simple and inexpensive that the kids could work together with me to make for their teachers. Too much to ask? I hoped not, but nothing was coming to me. And then I remembered this brittle that someone had brought to MOPS a few years ago. It uses saltine crackers. And you can pick up a box of Saltines at Aldi’s for 89 cents… which is perfect since I have to make gifts for SS and Bible Study teachers (times 3) plus neighbors and the tutorial teacher and “don’t forget my gymnastic teacher Mom!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Tradition: Cutting Down Our Tree</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-favorite-tradition-cutting-down-our-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/my-favorite-tradition-cutting-down-our-tree/</guid>
      <description>The hunt begins…
Gloves?

Check.
Tree cart?

Check.
Now to find the perfect tree.
“How about this one I suggest?”
“No, that looks like an angel tree,” my son says. “We need to find a star tree.”
My son doesn’t like when there are too many branches on the bottom as they are harder to cut down. (We always pick spruces and they are quite painful and prickly).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving Recipes: Old and New</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thanksgiving-recipes-old-and-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2009 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thanksgiving-recipes-old-and-new/</guid>
      <description>This year the Thanksgiving menu held some old favs and some new favs as well. Thought I’d share the recipes so you could stick em in your box for next year, or for later this holiday season.
My mom’s apple pie is by far my most favorite apple pie in the world. In fact, I am an apple pie snob and won’t eat any other pie but her recipe. Because, once you’ve had this one, no others compare in my opinion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Treats</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/turkey-treats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/turkey-treats/</guid>
      <description>We’re taking the week off…no tutorial, no home school. V-A-C-A-T-I-O-N! TIME!
Today we made turkey cookies thanks to this post I read last night. Rule number 1, don’t look to close at the example picture here, just quickly look at it to get the idea, then close it. Otherwise, these won’t seem exactly up to snuff. But, we had a blast decorating them and they taste yummy, so who cares if they aren’t picture perfect?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Girl Learns to Fly</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/super-girl-learns-to-fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 03:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/super-girl-learns-to-fly/</guid>
      <description>Visit here or here for more fun with pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trick or Treat Time</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/trick-or-treat-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/trick-or-treat-time/</guid>
      <description>
Super Girl  Bumblebee the Transformer

And our Little Kangaroo

We had a wonderful time playing with and visiting with our neighbors, dressing up in costumes, and begging for candy. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Branded</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/branded/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/branded/</guid>
      <description>My family’s love for Chick-Fil-A goes deep and wide. [
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/IMG_0105.jpg)
The first symbol my son recognized was for Chick-Fil-A. He could “read” it at age 2. And anytime he saw a cursive C he thought it stood for Chick-Fil-A. At that same age, I showed him a symbol for the golden arches and he had no idea what it was. My daughter’s one year scrapbooks both have pages dedicated to their “first Chick-Fil-A” kids meal experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabulous Fourth Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fabulous-fourth-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fabulous-fourth-fun/</guid>
      <description>My little crew in red, white, and blue.
 First time playing with sparklers.
 
Visit here  or here  for more Wednesday picture fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And now for something completely different</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-now-for-something-completely-different/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2009 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/and-now-for-something-completely-different/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been to a few parades in my day. Unlike the kids, I’m not all that surprised by what I see. I’ve come to expect the fire trucks, army tanks, corvettes, marching bands…
This year however, there were a few things I hadn’t seen before. 
Gotta love keeping it green with the organic fertilizer. Not your typical parade entry.
This was probably my favorite though. 
I’m all for safety, really I am, but if that missile accidentally goes off, how much good will that fire extinguisher do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shh, don’t tell…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shh-dont-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 21:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shh-dont-tell/</guid>
      <description>While most of America celebrated Father’s Day yesterday, the circus family did not. Shh…Please don’t tell the circus children. They think Father’s Day is next week, because that’s when we are celebrating it. We paint pumpkins in Nov and build gingerbread houses in Jan, so why can’t we celebrate dear old dad one week late? Yes, we are shamelessly pulling the wool over our innocent children’s eyes.
Scott and I wanted to get away for a weekend alone, just the two of us, as our gift to each other for our 30th birthdays this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Role That Suits Her Well</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-role-that-suits-her-well/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-role-that-suits-her-well/</guid>
      <description>My kids made an important decision this week. After much deliberation, they’ve finally figured out their Halloween costumes for next fall. And really, not a moment too soon… what with 146 days till Halloween, it’s a good thing we’ve got it settled. My son will be Luke Skywalker (he told me this week that he wished when he was a baby we had name him Luke Skywalker). My 3 year old will be Princess Leia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s beginning to look a lot like…Easter</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-beginning-to-look-a-lot-likeeaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 13:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-beginning-to-look-a-lot-likeeaster/</guid>
      <description>Those that have followed me in the past, know I love holidays. Here at the circus we celebrate any time we get a chance. Who doesn’t love some themed treats and fun crafts? But two holidays hold special significance for us. Christmas and Easter
They are not just days to get dressed up and partake of traditions.
And to set them a part we spend a great deal of time, as in weeks, preparing for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Come Let Us Adore Him</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/o-come-let-us-adore-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/o-come-let-us-adore-him/</guid>
      <description>I don’t remember what magazine or book I read it from, but a few years ago I found an idea for having a wise man celebration. For some reason I recall it being on January 6th. And I decided it was a good idea. But that year my entire family got struck with the stomach virus, so we skipped it. But last year and this year we celebrated, thus making it a tradition at our house.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
