<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maggie on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/maggie/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maggie on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 13:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/maggie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Tearful Goodbye</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-tearful-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 13:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-tearful-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>This morning we said a very tearful goodbye to our beloved Maggie dog. She’s been a faithful and loving part of our family for 10 years. When Scott and I brought her home in March of 2003, she was the center of our little family. Then she lovingly welcomed, one child after another to the circus fam. She stood guard under their bassinets and cribs. She gave them something to look at during tummy time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She Has Stolen His Heart</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/she-has-stolen-his-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/she-has-stolen-his-heart/</guid>
      <description>I’ve got pictures of all of my kids as babies snuggling up with our beloved dog… I’ve got the classic shots of them getting a big wet slobbery kiss while they giggle with glee. And Maggie lovingly observing their tummy time activities.
But, of my four children, my youngest is by far the most captivated by our dog. 
He truly loves her. He excitedly greets her when we come home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Reluctantly Photographed</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-reluctantly-photographed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-reluctantly-photographed/</guid>
      <description>My youngest was sitting on the floor “reading” his choo-choo book to our dog Maggie when I had to grab my camera and snap a picture. He then looks over at me and says, “Aww man, No SMILE!”
I said, “Ok, no smile.” and he happily went back to his reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puppy Kisses</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/puppy-kisses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/puppy-kisses/</guid>
      <description>Visit here for more WW posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tag! Your it!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tag-your-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/tag-your-it/</guid>
      <description>Divide and Conquer
That would be the name of the game lately at the circus.
I’ll take the youngest two to the grocery store while Scott takes the older ones with him to build the new to us play set. Or Scott takes the big 3 to the year end baseball ceremony while I stay home with the babe.
At this stage of the game, tag teaming has seemed crucial for surviving and for attempting to keep the household running somewhat smoothly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just a girl and her dog</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-a-girl-and-her-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/just-a-girl-and-her-dog/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She’s lucky!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shes-lucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shes-lucky/</guid>
      <description>Lucky for Maggie today is her special day, otherwise, I don’t think I’d have been so nice about finding this on my couch cushions today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday Maggie!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/happy-birthday-maggie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/happy-birthday-maggie/</guid>
      <description>Our beloved pooch turns 6 today! Where does the time go? We got her two weeks after moving into our new home and before we had kids. One of my fourth grade language arts students loved corgi’s and did a book report on Pembrooke Welsh Corgi’s. He got an A and I was sold on Corgi’s. I distinctly remember him telling me that they were “light shedders and good with kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maggie&#39;s Turn</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/maggies-turn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 20:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/maggies-turn/</guid>
      <description>Being a self proclaimed non dog lover and a mother of three preschoolers, I must admit that the dog is not high on the priority list. Her needs sadly get ignored all too often.
I honestly couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell you that last time poor Maggie had a bath.
But, in the interest of keeping it real, I&amp;rsquo;d say it was at least last spring.
So, today I decided to give her a bath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not quite Cruella Deville</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-quite-cruella-deville/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-quite-cruella-deville/</guid>
      <description>Last night we were walking along the beach in our neighborhood and someone walked by with her two dogs. One big dog passed to our right, the other between my son and I to our left. As this was happening she asked if the kids were ok with dogs. It was then that I realized how I&amp;rsquo;ve taken this fact for granted.
I am not a dog person. When I go to other dog owners homes, you won&amp;rsquo;t see me sitting on the floor playing with the dog or cuddling them on my lap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s One Patient Dog!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thats-one-patient-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thats-one-patient-dog/</guid>
      <description>This Wordless Wednesday highlights our very patient dog.

Note the ear pulling and stroller bashing.

&amp;ldquo;What Mom? I AM being gentle!&amp;rdquo;

For more of my Wordless Wednesdays, click here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
