<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>super hero on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/super-hero/</link>
    <description>Recent content in super hero on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 03:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/super-hero/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>When Superman Takes Up Permanent Residence in Your Dining Room</title>
      <link>/posts/when-superman-takes-up-permanent-residence-in-your-dining-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/when-superman-takes-up-permanent-residence-in-your-dining-room/</guid>
      <description>Exactly one month ago today we had a Superman birthday party for my youngest. In addition to a slew of crepe paper, we hung a giant poster of Superman on the hutch in our dining room.
Last night I noticed that Superman still hangs in my dining room.

He’s hung there for an entire month.
We let him hang there until we moved it up to the boys room. This way it wouldn’t wrinkle or rip until we got around to it, and maybe by leaving it hanging in our dining room we’d be more motivated to get around to it sooner than later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I can fly!</title>
      <link>/posts/i-can-fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 08:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/i-can-fly/</guid>
      <description>“Hey Mom,” he said to me this morning. “I figured out how I can fly like superman, look.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Lessons from Superman</title>
      <link>/posts/life-lessons-from-superman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 08:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/life-lessons-from-superman/</guid>
      <description>Bet you can’t guess what movie we watched this weekend?

little boys dressed as super heroes truly melt my heart… especially this little boy… sitting at breakfast with his tussled hair and sheepish grin…
We had a family movie afternoon yesterday and watched The 1978 Original Superman with the big 3 while our three year old was napping. He woke up in time to catch the heroic finish and then fly around the basement with his cape blazing behind him while the theme music blasted from our stereo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She Really is Super Girl</title>
      <link>/posts/she-really-is-super-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/she-really-is-super-girl/</guid>
      <description>Our little girl really is super girl and she proved it last night. She is crazy tough. So let me cut to the chase and say that her injury was pretty bad. The need for stitches was obvious but even the doctor had not realized at first that it was so deep it would require both internal and external stitches. My girl had been cut deep. The coffee table/toy box had cut all the way to the bone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One Where I Go To Work For Marvel</title>
      <link>/posts/the-one-where-i-go-to-work-for-marvel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-one-where-i-go-to-work-for-marvel/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I didn’t now Bruce Banner from Bruce Wayne and I couldn’t have named an X-Man to save my life. Since my son’s Spiderman party, I’ve been studying up. Doing some self inflicted homework. In the past month I have seen all 3 Spiderman Movies, The Incredible Hulk, The Punisher, and the 3 X Men movies…and tomorrow Scott and I are going on a double date to see the new Wolverine movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Little Spidey</title>
      <link>/posts/my-little-spidey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2009 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-little-spidey/</guid>
      <description>My son is obsessed with all things Spiderman. I remember when he was about 2 and he saw a picture of Spiderman on something in the grocery store. He asked me what that was and I told him Spiderman. I remember he giggled saying that was so silly, to have a spider man. Sometime since then, he got bit by the spidey bug! I love this picture…the smile on his face was worth all the effort it took to make that cake!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
