<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Circus Dad on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/circus-dad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Circus Dad on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 12:28:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/circus-dad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Happy Fathers Day Circus Dad</title>
      <link>/posts/happy-fathers-day-circus-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/happy-fathers-day-circus-dad/</guid>
      <description>They saying becoming a parent changes you. It does. Truly, nothing can prepare you for it. I remember so well the day our first born child entered the world. I remember all the nerves and excitement. One of the things that surprised me the most about becoming a mom was how much I fell even more in love with Scott on that day. I already loved him to pieces. He was already all I could have wanted and more in a husband.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daddy’s Partner</title>
      <link>/posts/daddys-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/daddys-partner/</guid>
      <description>All of my kids have enjoyed pushing the pretend mower along side their Daddy, but I do believe none of them have enjoyed it as much as our youngest. The look of absolute GLEE on his face when he hears Daddy say it’s time for him to go cut the grass is absolutely priceless. 
He even willingly will choose to stay behind with Dad to cut grass and meet the rest of us at the pool MISSING SOME SWIM TIME rather than miss the chance to cut the grass with his Dad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beneath the Rim</title>
      <link>/posts/beneath-the-rim/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 04:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/beneath-the-rim/</guid>
      <description>The highlight of our day at the Grand Canyon for most of the members of our circus crew was a short hike they took into the canyon. 
We all started on the hike, but it was more than this “fraid’ of heights Momma” could handle. The plan was to go to the first tunnel and back, but after about 2 treks on the switchback, I was biting back tears and hating EVERY second of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eye on the Prize</title>
      <link>/posts/eye-on-the-prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 06:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/eye-on-the-prize/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend was our Cub Scout Pack’s Pine Wood Derby race. It is one of the favorite Cub Scout traditions. Scott and our oldest son worked hard on the car.

My son had one focus: speed
He wanted his car to be as fast as possible. Whenever they discussed designs or modifications, speed was always his deciding factor. 


He designed his car to look like Bullet Bill from Wii Mario Kart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tee Shirt Love</title>
      <link>/posts/tee-shirt-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tee-shirt-love/</guid>
      <description>Scott has been a huge help and support to me this week… taking time off of work so I can rest up (apparently surgery takes more out of you, then you anticipate)… driving the kids to their activities, helping with school, and meals and cleaning up… So, today, I thought I’d show my appreciation and wear my “My Husband Rocks” tee shirt. My 7 year old looked at my shirt, read it aloud and said, “So, why did you wear that today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Cake You Can Play With</title>
      <link>/posts/a-cake-you-can-play-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-cake-you-can-play-with/</guid>
      <description>It’s February and that means Blue and Gold banquet season for Cub Scout folks. An annual tradition at our Blue and Gold banquet is the Dad/Lad cake decorating contest. [
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/IMG_9501.jpg)

This is always a fun event in the circus household. Even though all of the baking and decorating is done by Dad and the cub scout… the rest of the kids greatly enjoy observing the fun in the kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Things I Love About You</title>
      <link>/posts/11-things-i-love-about-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2012 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/11-things-i-love-about-you/</guid>
      <description>Scott, in honor of our anniversary this weekend, I compiled a list of 11 things I love about you.
1. You’re a dreamer.
2. Your not afraid to go for the crazy (take 4 kids on a 22 hour car ride to see a 2 minute rocket launch… sure thing…stop by Times Square for hot dogs on the way to CT for a wedding with 2 toddlers and a very pregnant wife, “I’m in!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Out My Back Window</title>
      <link>/posts/looking-out-my-back-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/looking-out-my-back-window/</guid>
      <description>I glanced out my back window on Saturday and saw this

Only, I didn’t just see this precious moment in time, but simultaneously, my mind flashed back to several other similar moments over the past 5 years….
September 2009

August 2008

And, April 2007

One can’t help but notice a few things when observing these father/child bonding moments in the back yard.
1. Believe it or not Scott, we’ve been VERY successful in growing grass in our backyard these past 5 years!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Unexpected Treat</title>
      <link>/posts/an-unexpected-treat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/an-unexpected-treat/</guid>
      <description>March was a rough month at the circus. Scott had some deadlines at work which meant he worked a lot of overtime. This happens with his work and we’ve all learned to roll with it, but that doesn’t mean that the long days don’t eventually start to take their toll. On all of us
Which is why it’s been so great the last 2 weeks having Scott around more often. Last Monday he left work at 2 to go to DC with us, on Friday he got home at 5:30 (to which my oldest son asked, “Dad did you take vacation time to get home this early?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DATE DAY</title>
      <link>/posts/date-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/date-day/</guid>
      <description>While we didn’t plan it like this at first, Sunday ended up being date day for each of our 4 kids. Each child ended up with some one on one time with either mom, dad, or Aunt Karen. Good times had by all!
One of the duties of our church deacons is to unlock the church on Sunday mornings. When Scott became a deacon 3 years ago, he started taking one child with him on his deacon duty mornings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Daddy/Daughter Date…</title>
      <link>/posts/a-daddydaughter-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-daddydaughter-date/</guid>
      <description>Scott took a vacation day on Thursday so he could spend the day with our oldest daughter. First they went with the other kids in her Kindergarten class to see a performance of The Night Before Christmas. Apparently the sets were gorgeous and the play was very well done. Such a treat to go to a live theatre AND to get to see it with her school friends and Dad. I think it was also a treat for Dad to get to see her with her school friends, it’s an aspect of her life that he doesn’t get to see very often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tooth Fairy Is Working Overtime at the Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/the-tooth-fairy-is-working-overtime-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-tooth-fairy-is-working-overtime-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>Since my oldest lost his first tooth, last spring, the tooth fairy has made 4 more visits to the circus. And judging by the giant front tooth dangling from my oldest sons top row, I think she’ll be back again this week!
As you may recall, we pulled my son’s first tooth in a very unconventional manner. His second tooth was pulled the normal way by dad. For his third tooth, he was very eager to pull it himself when his grandparents were here, so they could see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Role Play</title>
      <link>/posts/role-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/role-play/</guid>
      <description>Our oldest daughter had a little fun getting into her character for Halloween. When posing for pictures in their costumes, she decided to fully act out the part of Snow White.

I think my favorite part of the reenactment was when she asked us to take her picture sleeping with the apple. &amp;quot;Skip the ol posing by the door with the trick or treat basket, we’ll go for playing dead on the floor with an apple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tribute to the Circus Dad</title>
      <link>/posts/a-tribute-to-the-circus-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 04:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-tribute-to-the-circus-dad/</guid>
      <description>They say having kids changes things.
And they are right, it does.
I remember so vividly after our first son was born. My heart had grown at least triple in size. As I held him in my arms, it was love, pure love at first sight. But, in addition to that, my love for Scott, had quadrupled as well. I never felt more supported, more cared for, more in awe, than I did that first night after becoming parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forget Something?</title>
      <link>/posts/forget-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 18:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/forget-something/</guid>
      <description>Last week I mentioned on face book that I love how Scott makes me a pot of coffee every morning.
And, I do.
Makes me smile each morning when I come to the kitchen and pour myself a cup.
And I smile again later that morning as I go back to top it off. Again… and again.
Thursday, however, I had to laugh when I went to pour my cup of coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Circus First</title>
      <link>/posts/another-circus-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/another-circus-first/</guid>
      <description>The time had finally come for the tooth to be pulled. While our son was more than ready for it to come out, Dad was secretly uneasy about the venture. “He trusts me” Scott confided to me in the hallway, “What if I hurt him?” Then Scott got another one of his moments of sheer fatherhood brilliance.
“I’ll let him do it,” he declared.
He tied one end of the dental floss to his light saber and the other to his tooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Em or Sit Em?</title>
      <link>/posts/start-em-or-sit-em/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/start-em-or-sit-em/</guid>
      <description>Woa Dad! What are you thinking? Your starting him on your fantasy team?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Lil Cub</title>
      <link>/posts/my-lil-cub/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-lil-cub/</guid>
      <description>6 years ago I watched my lil man proudly hold his head high during tummy time. I was so excited b/c he had recently learned to roll over. He was growing up so fast and I was thrilled with all he was learning and doing. I had no idea that in just 6 short years he’d be at Cup Scout camp with Daddy learning a whole slew of new things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poor Dad, Get’s No Respect</title>
      <link>/posts/poor-dad-gets-no-respect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/poor-dad-gets-no-respect/</guid>
      <description>While capturing this “precious” Father/Son moment the other day…
 my mind instantly flashed back to a similar “bonding” moment between father and son which I captured 6 years ago…

Seems both my boys enjoy sticking their tongues out at dear old Dad!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The sign says what?</title>
      <link>/posts/the-sign-says-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-sign-says-what/</guid>
      <description>This picture cracks me up every time it pops onto our screen saver. Not only do I look incredibly tired and less than thrilled to have my picture taken, but in the background you see Potty= Privacy. What gives, you ask? Why was this dry erase board in your living room for 3 weeks?
Allow me to shed a little light to the back drop of this picture…
Scott took a week off from work after our son was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roady the Helpful Robot</title>
      <link>/posts/roady-the-helpful-robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 19:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/roady-the-helpful-robot/</guid>
      <description>I think we may have a future engineer on our hands. Which quite naturally brings a smile to the face of his engineer father. Last week my son came out one morning and told us he thought up a robot in his mind the night before. He wanted to know if he and Daddy could build it. The timing couldn’t have been better as Scott had taken the week off of work as we welcomed the baby into our family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday to the Circus Dad</title>
      <link>/posts/happy-birthday-to-the-circus-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/happy-birthday-to-the-circus-dad/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I watch my husband as he fathers my kids and he just takes my breath away. 
I love the way he can explain to my son in terms he can understand how just about anything under the sun works. I love the way he pulls the kids aside and talks to them about respecting their momma. I love when he takes one of them with him to church when he has deacon duty so they can have some special one on one time while he unlocks the church classrooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Own MacGyver</title>
      <link>/posts/my-own-macgyver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-own-macgyver/</guid>
      <description>Thought I’d share a glimpse of our dishwasher with you all. Because it cracks me up. Last week I called Scott at work to tell him the dishwasher was gushing water out the sides. One thing I love about Scott, is that when something appears broken, he almost always finds a way to make it work. Seriously, he is not afraid to tear anything apart and “macgyver” it. Which has saved us tons of money over the years… He’s torn apart computers, the washing machine, the dishwasher, our oven, the toilet…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe in Daddy’s Arms</title>
      <link>/posts/safe-in-daddys-arms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 04:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/safe-in-daddys-arms/</guid>
      <description>Tonight is one of those nights when I am extra thankful that God has given me a helpmate in life. And not just any helpmate, but one of the best.
My three year old was getting on the couch this evening, and if you know my girls, you know that they do this with much exuberance, so somewhere during the twirl she slipped and fell back, hitting her head on our toy box/coffee table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Is He Going With This?</title>
      <link>/posts/where-is-he-going-with-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 18:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/where-is-he-going-with-this/</guid>
      <description>My husband is a genius.
Pure genius, I tell you.
We were sitting around the table the other day at dinner. Nothing out of the ordinary. The kids were complaining about eating their green beans. Like I said, nothing unusual.
Then Scott asked my son, “Do you know why parents raise kids?”
“Because their fast.”
Pause…Confusion…
“No, not race, raise, as in, why do they have kids and help them grow up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Hurts</title>
      <link>/posts/love-hurts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/love-hurts/</guid>
      <description>I love this picture. I love it because it shows the kids and my husband engaged in play after a long day of work. 
I also love how the big kids seem to be attacking him b/c he’s got the youngest on his shoulders. Almost as if they are trying to get in on the action and attention. But take a closer look, because if you check out Scott’s face, you’ll find another gem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Déjà vu</title>
      <link>/posts/d%C3%A9j%C3%A0-vu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 03:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/d%C3%A9j%C3%A0-vu/</guid>
      <description>Last week I captured this sweet father/daughter moment. 
Which reminded me an awful lot of a very similar moment captured a year ago.
Funny how life repeats itself, isn’t it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daddy’s Girl</title>
      <link>/posts/daddys-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/daddys-girl/</guid>
      <description>Can you tell she loves her Daddy? You can almost hear her giggle with glee as she hugs him. That’s love…
So pure and sweet
 
   May it only grow stronger with time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesdays in Annapolis</title>
      <link>/posts/wednesdays-in-annapolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wednesdays-in-annapolis/</guid>
      <description>It’s funny how a simple thing like dinner on a Wednesday night can have an dramatic impact on your life. 7 years ago we went out to dinner with another couple in downtown Annapolis on a Wednesday night. If you know anything about summer in Annapolis then you know that Wednesday nights mean sailing races. (Truth is I grew up around here and just learned that fact 7 years ago).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
