<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>football on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/football/</link>
    <description>Recent content in football on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 05:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/football/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Steelers Fans for Life</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/steelers-fans-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 05:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/steelers-fans-for-life/</guid>
      <description>It’s hard enough not living in the home town of your favorite sports team. Even harder than that, is living in the town of the ARCH RIVAL of your favorite sports team. One way that I think we as a family have connected and stayed connected with our Steelers roots, is by making the trek to training camp as often as possible. We missed the last two years, but we went often enough over the past 10 years that the big 3 all remember going and talk about going and consider it a tradition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number 1 Sign Your Family Might Be a Little Obsessed with Football…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/number-1-sign-your-family-might-be-a-little-obsessed-with-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/number-1-sign-your-family-might-be-a-little-obsessed-with-football/</guid>
      <description>Since it was the first day of spring this week, I decided it might be time to take down the Valentine’s wreath from my door and switch it for my Easter one. Today I thought I’d take it a step further and even pull out my spring/Easter/”leave up till I pull out the red/white/blue decorations for summer around Memorial day” decorations…as I did the girls were ooing and aahing over the little eggs, flowers, chicks and lambs…Then my 6 year old daughter saw the bunny my mother in law had given me a few years ago and said, _“Awh look at the bunny and it’s even holding a football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Long #86</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-long-86/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/so-long-86/</guid>
      <description>While he wore the jersey for 14 years, she proudly wore hers for 3. (more than half of her life). It was her first jersey and I always thought it suited her personality well.  As we listened live to Hines bid his tearful goodbye to football this afternoon, we were sad to see him go but as my 7 year old pointed out, “thankful he’s not going to play for the Ravens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We ARE ready for some Steelers Football!!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-are-ready-for-some-steelers-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-are-ready-for-some-steelers-football/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been playing the song on repeat for weeks and now the day is here. Pittsburgh isn’t going to the Super Bowl anymore they are AT the Superbowl! And we are ready to cheer them on for their 7th Superbowl victory!

Even our dog Maggie is sporting the black and gold today!

GO STEELERS!!!!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muted Celebration</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/muted-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/muted-celebration/</guid>
      <description>I’ve never known what it was like to be part of the home town team. Though I was born in Pa, I’ve lived in rival MD since the age of 5, not counting 3 of my 4 years of college. I got my love of football from my dad and my dad brought me up a Steelers girl. I now pass this legacy onto my four children. I just love this pic of our newest Steelers fan, I had to find a reason to sneak this in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Dad</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-date-with-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-date-with-dad/</guid>
      <description>I got my love of sports from my dad. I can remember watching Pirates games at 5 when he was out of town, just to make me feel closer to him. In high school, my dad would take me to Penn State Football games to watch my cousin play in the Blue Band. I think my dad made sure that we attended every kind of professional sporting event at least once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Em or Sit Em?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/start-em-or-sit-em/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/start-em-or-sit-em/</guid>
      <description>Woa Dad! What are you thinking? Your starting him on your fantasy team?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
