<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Traveling Circus 2016 on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/traveling-circus-2016/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Traveling Circus 2016 on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 09:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/traveling-circus-2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Christmastime in the Big Apple</title>
      <link>/posts/christmastime-in-the-big-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/christmastime-in-the-big-apple/</guid>
      <description>About a month ago my youngest asked when we would see the Statue of Liberty again. We visited it a few years ago on our way to our Boston Vacation, and it has been a highlight memory of our youngest child ever since. He loves when we spot it on tv or in a picture somewhere. I replied, “Probably the next time we go to New York City.” To which he of course replied, “When can we go to New York City again?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Full, Fun Last Day of our Adventure</title>
      <link>/posts/the-full-fun-last-day-of-our-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-full-fun-last-day-of-our-adventure/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been home two and a half weeks and I am finally taking time to record the moments of our last day of vacation…. this is proof positive that I am glad I took the time to record our memories while on vacation b/c there is no way I could have gone back and done it once home.
We woke up QUITE cold on our last full day of vacation at Great Basin National Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our last National Park for this vacation!!</title>
      <link>/posts/our-last-national-park-for-this-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 01:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-last-national-park-for-this-vacation/</guid>
      <description>We left Gana’s house around 11 on Saturday. Our destination was Great Basin National Park in eastern Nevada. Our route was ‘the loneliest highway in America’. It was by far our longest drive of the trip, 8 hours with no midpoint destinations. But, of course, we made a few stops. We were not expecting much. We had mentally interpreted “loneliest highway” as “boringest highway” and thought it was going to be 8 hours of unchanging desert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time with Gana</title>
      <link>/posts/time-with-gana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/time-with-gana/</guid>
      <description>We can not make a trip to the state of California without finding a way to visit Scott’s Nana. Even though California is a big state, and being in California does not necessarily equate being in Nana’s neighborhood. Compared to the east coast, anywhere in California is MUCH, MUCH closer to Nana’s than normal. So, we knew our trip to California, MUST include a visit at Nana’s (or as the kids call her Gana for G reat N ana ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunch in San Fran</title>
      <link>/posts/lunch-in-san-fran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/lunch-in-san-fran/</guid>
      <description>I love big cities. D.C., New York City, Boston, Chicago, Seattle, Philadelphia… So, it probably doesn’t surprise anyone, Scott included, that when I was plotting our road trip from Pinnacles NP to his Nana’s north of Sacramento, I insisted we “swing by San Francisco” for lunch on our way. It was an hour drive out of the way (plus whatever time we spent in the city) but I really, really wanted to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reuniting with Family at Pinnacles National Park</title>
      <link>/posts/reuniting-with-family-at-pinnacles-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/reuniting-with-family-at-pinnacles-national-park/</guid>
      <description>During our trek across California, we wanted to also make time to see some of Scott’s family that live here. Scott’s aunt, uncle, and his cousin and her family live a few hours from Pinnacles National Park and graciously offered to meet us there and spend time with us at the park.

We met at a restaurant called Togo’s… we had never heard of it before, but Scott’s cousin described it as “like subway only better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiking to the Falls</title>
      <link>/posts/hiking-to-the-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hiking-to-the-falls/</guid>
      <description>Scott had been hoping for us to take a hike down from Glacier Point to Yosemite Valley. It would be our longest hike, but it would have been all down hill and we would pass both Nevada and Vernal Falls. Given our kids fascination with water falls, this seemed like a fun hike. Unfortunately, we learned too late that there was no shuttle from Yosemite Valley to Glacier Point, and the only way we could do this plan was if we had pre purchased tickets for a special shuttle that left early in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One of America’s Best</title>
      <link>/posts/one-of-americas-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one-of-americas-best/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I visited Yosemite 14 years ago during our trip which shaped all trips. Therefore, it wasn’t a must see for this vacation. And when Scott and I were first plotting out this trip, we kind of waivered as to whether we wanted to include it or not. But, we decided that since Yosemite is one of the quintessential parks and since we were were were going to be SO CLOSE, we owed it to the kids to show them Yosemite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Ol’ Family Fun in the Canyon</title>
      <link>/posts/good-ol-family-fun-in-the-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/good-ol-family-fun-in-the-canyon/</guid>
      <description>Our campground was located pretty much on the border of Sequoia and Kings Canyon National Parks. We woke slowly and had a leisurely breakfast, then headed out to see Kings Canyon.

As we approached the visitor center, we saw a sign for a church service in the park. We were only 5 minutes late so we ran down to join them in worship. It was pretty neat to be able to join with other believers in worship, right there in the midst of God’s creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BIG TREES!</title>
      <link>/posts/big-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 23:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/big-trees/</guid>
      <description>We arrived at Sequoia National Park around 2:00. We had a picnic lunch, stopped by the Visitors Center and headed off to find some big trees.

We took a 4 mile hike in the late afternoon, that as of this point, goes down as my favorite hike of the trip. We started in the populous area of the infamous General Sherman.


Then we hiked the Congress Trail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little break from camping</title>
      <link>/posts/a-little-break-from-camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-little-break-from-camping/</guid>
      <description>After our morning at the beach, we were headed north west to prepare for the next leg of our trip. But before heading to 4 more National Parks, we were in need of hot showers, soft beds, and a washing machine.
Enter, Best Western.

We hadn’t booked a hotel in advance because we weren’t exactly sure how far we’d want to drive on Friday… we knew we wanted to get close to Sequoia National Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tide Pools</title>
      <link>/posts/tide-pools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tide-pools/</guid>
      <description>Since marine life is part of Channel Islands National park, we woke up at 5:30am so we could visit some nearby tide pools while it was low tide.

 
The kids didn’t seem to mind too much though, because the promise of seeing “cool things” was all it took to get them up and at it. Even our late sleeper had a smile on his face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Island Bound!</title>
      <link>/posts/island-bound/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/island-bound/</guid>
      <description>This trip seems to be all about extremes and remoteness. Channel Islands National Park is a group of islands located off the coast of Los Angeles. A visit here gives one a glimpse of what the California coast looked like before it was overpopulated with humanity. You can find vegetation and wild life here that doesn’t exist anywhere else. The signature element of the park however is the rocky cliffs along the waters edge and the marine life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pacific Ocean!!!</title>
      <link>/posts/the-pacific-ocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 01:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-pacific-ocean/</guid>
      <description>After leaving Joshua Tree, we were headed west for the Pacific Ocean. We checked out the visitor center and checked in with the boat company about our day trip the following day. Then we stopped at Subway to grab subs for dinner on the beach. 
We were camping at a State Park which had walking access to the beach. We all greatly enjoyed eating dinner overlooking the ocean and than splashing in the waves afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please can we climb some more?</title>
      <link>/posts/please-can-we-climb-some-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 22:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/please-can-we-climb-some-more/</guid>
      <description>While we pack a lot into these trips, the over all plan is always pretty fluid. Scott and I had always left a second night at Joshua Tree as an option in our itinerary. After a great evening sunset, animal show, morning hike, and visit to the visitors center, the heat of the day had us thinking perhaps we should move on to cooler pastures. The kids however had so much fun climbing around Jumbo Rocks that they unanimously voted we stay the second night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Playground</title>
      <link>/posts/the-ultimate-playground/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-ultimate-playground/</guid>
      <description>Our campsite was at Jumbo Rocks, aptly named being as the campground was nestled amongst big rocks.
 
As with any desert park, the key to hiking is to go early or late. Right after breakfast we set off to hike the Skull Rocks trail. The trailhead was within walking distance of our campsite. Since we were hiking in the early morning, we came across a few animal friends along our way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Tree National Park</title>
      <link>/posts/joshua-tree-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/joshua-tree-national-park/</guid>
      <description>We left the salt flats in Badwater Basin of Death Valley around 10:30am. After heading 45 minutes towards Joshua Tree we came across a road closure and had to turn around. This of course added about 2 hrs to our 4 and a half hour drive to Joshua Tree. I had found a restaurant online in Pioneertown that I had decided would be worth a little extra driving out of our way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Many Sides of Death Valley</title>
      <link>/posts/the-many-sides-of-death-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-many-sides-of-death-valley/</guid>
      <description>Don’t get me wrong. Death Valley is aptly named. It is hot. Like crazy hot. Like 95 degrees at 7am, hot. And it is desolate. Like, LITERAL MIDDLE OF NOWHERE, desolate. Not a soul in site for miles and miles. And of course the signs everywhere warning you of heat stroke and death and the need for water. I get why they call it Death Valley. And quite a lot of the park looks like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Judge a Park By It’s Title</title>
      <link>/posts/dont-judge-a-park-by-its-title/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dont-judge-a-park-by-its-title/</guid>
      <description>When we first began our quest, I assumed Death Valley National Park would be a mere checking off of a box. But, as we started planning and I began researching things to do there, I realized it really was a beautiful and unique park. 
Sunday morning we started out with a relaxing morning at our hotel near the airport in Vegas. We woke up, took showers and took advantage of the complimentary breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Adventure Begins!</title>
      <link>/posts/another-adventure-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 00:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/another-adventure-begins/</guid>
      <description>After much saving and planning, the circus fam set off for another National Park adventure. Our mission: to visit 8 national parks (7 in California and 1 in Nevada).

Because we wanted to maximize our time at the parks, we opted to fly to Las Vegas and rent a van. We plan to camp for 12 of our 17 nights of vacation. The thing about camping is it requires the same amount of stuff for one night away as it does for 5 or 12.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
