<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Army on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/army/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Army on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 18:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/army/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You think I’d know by now…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-think-id-know-by-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/you-think-id-know-by-now/</guid>
      <description>When my son asked if he could bring his light sabers or guns to his sisters first soccer practice, I said no. Because sometimes it is awkward to deal with the whole gun issue out in public.
Obviously I forgot that little boys will turn absolutely anything into a gun.
So today I said what the heck, bring the gun. Which apparently translated to, go crazy, carry a gun in each hand and a concealed weapon… Heck, why not wear the entire uniform!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bet You’ve Never Seen an Army Quite Like This One</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bet-youve-never-seen-an-army-quite-like-this-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bet-youve-never-seen-an-army-quite-like-this-one/</guid>
      <description>Alternate Title: How Your Army Looks When You Have 2 Younger Sisters

I couldn’t help but smile when I looked out the window and saw this scene…makes me laugh when looking at it on the computer as well. Quite a motley crew we have defending the fortress… the leader in his camo’s with his walking stick (or staff as he refers to it), his trusty sidekicks following in their fairy wings, and Uncle Jim covering from behind with the ever elusive fluorescent double barrel shot gun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How My Son Decided We Should Celebrate Memorial Day</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-my-son-decided-we-should-celebrate-memorial-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 18:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-my-son-decided-we-should-celebrate-memorial-day/</guid>
      <description>I’ll be honest. When I think Memorial Day celebration, I typically think cook outs and swimming pools. This year being 9 mths preggo, we didn’t really make any big plans for Memorial Day weekend. Scott grilled for us several times and even got out this smoker and cooked a chicken for Monday’s dinner. We went to the park, did a few things around the house and basically took it easy all weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backyard Warfare</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/backyard-warfare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/backyard-warfare/</guid>
      <description>There is a huge pile of bamboo in our backyard waiting for a run to the dump on Saturday. Until then, it provided the perfect landscape for my son to build a fort and play war. He stayed out there for hours and was so proud of his camouflage. 
Unfortunatly, his gun kinda gives him away.
When I showed this picture to my husband I said it should be called,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
