<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reflections on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/reflections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reflections on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 03:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/reflections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>When Superman Takes Up Permanent Residence in Your Dining Room</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-superman-takes-up-permanent-residence-in-your-dining-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-superman-takes-up-permanent-residence-in-your-dining-room/</guid>
      <description>Exactly one month ago today we had a Superman birthday party for my youngest. In addition to a slew of crepe paper, we hung a giant poster of Superman on the hutch in our dining room.
Last night I noticed that Superman still hangs in my dining room.

He’s hung there for an entire month.
We let him hang there until we moved it up to the boys room. This way it wouldn’t wrinkle or rip until we got around to it, and maybe by leaving it hanging in our dining room we’d be more motivated to get around to it sooner than later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Heavy Heart</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-heavy-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-heavy-heart/</guid>
      <description>I learned this weekend that a friend and former MOPS mentor mom of mine passed away suddenly in her sleep. The suddenness and surprise of her passing took me quite off guard. My heart has been so heavy since I heard the news. Aside from my grandparents who both suffered long illnesses before their death, this is really the first person close to me that I’ve known whose died. She wasn’t just a person that I recognized or said Hi to on Sunday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
