<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Goals on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/goals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Goals on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/goals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Month, New Week, New Goals</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/new-month-new-week-new-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/new-month-new-week-new-goals/</guid>
      <description>February is here. I am happy to say I’ve finally put away all our Christmas decor and while it isn’t completely conquered, I have tamed the laundry beast and gotten somewhat of a grip on the house chores and school work. For now
So, with this new month, I’ve set some goals for some things I’d like to get done around the house. And thanks to two different blogging friends, I have some accountability and inspiration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Thoughts: I’m a Survivor</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/weekend-thoughts-im-a-survivor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/weekend-thoughts-im-a-survivor/</guid>
      <description>Last week I survived the Annapolis 10 Mile Run. I’d like to say that I raced it or ran it, but in actuality I just survived it.
While one might wonder why I am not more excited and proud of such an accomplishment, it is because the year prior, I ran it well. I trained for it all summer and come race day I did my best. Now my best is only about 15 min faster than my survival pace, but the feeling I had when crossing the finish line was worlds different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day One of Training</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/day-one-of-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/day-one-of-training/</guid>
      <description>Well, January came and went and I exercised one day in 2009. This is why I have to set goals for myself. Without a race in my future, I lack the discipline to get off my butt.
So, I’ve set my sights on a Half Marathon in May in one of my favorite cities…Pittsburgh. I am really excited. I checked out the route online and it looks great…we cross two bridges, run downtown a bit, run along the river overlooking the city and my highlight, we run by Heinz Field (home of the Superbowl Champs)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We did it!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-did-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-did-it/</guid>
      <description>Sorry for not posting a post race synopsis yesterday, in the words of my dear sister in law, I was &amp;ldquo;too tired.&amp;rdquo;
 The race was a blast! The weather was gorgeous and the views were beautiful. My favorite was running down Main Street in Annapolis looking down at the harbor. It was incredible! The first 5 miles I felt great. I kept up a steady conversation with Karen and at each mile marker would scream out with glee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carb Loading</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/carb-loading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2008 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/carb-loading/</guid>
      <description>We had a big &amp;ldquo;carbolicious&amp;rdquo; dinner tonight to get ready for the Annapolis 10 Mile Run tomorrow morning&amp;hellip;. my sis in law, my father in law, my two good friends, and I are all running 10 miles tomorrow at 7:45am.
** Wish us luck!!! **</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks for the Advice</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thanks-for-the-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/thanks-for-the-advice/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to all of you that wrote with song suggestions last weekend to help me Pump it Up as I ran 7 miles on Sunday. Some of you asked me to let you know which songs I picked so here goes&amp;hellip;
 Bootylicious-Destiny&amp;rsquo;s Child (b/c when I run I think about looking good for my hubby ) Can&amp;rsquo;t Get Next to You&amp;hellip; Temptations (b/c KP you were right I love the oldies so I went with some Temptations, picked the song b/c I liked to imagine I was running soooo fast no one could get next to me&amp;hellip; ha ha) Unbelievable-EMF (You were right StellaG this song totally brought me back to middle school) Getting Jiggy Wit It&amp;ndash; Will Smith ( b/c I really like Will Smith and it is just so fun) MMMBop-Hanson Bros (again thanks to Stella for a trip down memory lane) Straight Up- Paula Abdul (took KP&amp;rsquo;s advice and went for an 80s&amp;ndash;maybe it is early 90s not sure&amp;hellip; tune I remember singing out loud in the old days&amp;hellip; ya know before American Idol)   This wasn&amp;rsquo;t the only music I download on my MP3 player though&amp;hellip; my friend Megh had made me a mix CD for Christmas of fun, upbeat Christian songs&amp;hellip; I took them and combined them with my 6 new tunes for a fabulous running soundtrack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Agony of Defeat</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-agony-of-defeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-agony-of-defeat/</guid>
      <description>I had a great post written &amp;quot;in my head&amp;quot; Saturday morning. I was setting off to do a 6 mile run. It would have been the longest run I had ever done in my life. Before training for the Annapolis 10 Mile that I am working towards at the end of the summer, the farthest I had run was a 5K (3.1 miles) So, this would have been about twice that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How far did I go?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-far-did-i-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-far-did-i-go/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned here, that I started running this summer. I am following a training schedule to help me reach my goal but it keeps changing the distance that I must run each day. Instead of guestimating (surely it&amp;rsquo;s been a mile by now) or driving the route with the car (like I really feel like loading the kids another time) to try to calculate the distance, my wonderful husband, the engineer, found me an online application made using google maps that is a HUGE help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Running</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-running/</guid>
      <description>Last week I registered for a 10 mile run at the end of August. For over a year now I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to do this. I ran a 5K for the first time when my son was a year old. I ran two more when my 2 year old was 6 mths old. Until last Tuesday, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t run since.
I waited through one of the mildest winter and spring seasons I&amp;rsquo;ve seen here and decided to start running during the week of record breaking heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here We Go!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/here-we-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/here-we-go/</guid>
      <description>I have been playing with the idea of doing a blog for some time. I think it is something I will really enjoy. I have really gotten into reading others blogs. I even have some blog friends who have no idea that I exist, but whose thoughts I read daily and think, &amp;ldquo;wow, these ladies are great. we would totally be friends!&amp;rdquo; Now it is my turn to enter the blog world and share my thoughts and musings with the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
