<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Annapolis on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/annapolis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Annapolis on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 08:06:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/annapolis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our Adventure with Sandy</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-adventure-with-sandy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/our-adventure-with-sandy/</guid>
      <description>For many north of us on the east coast, Sandy was more than an adventure… it was a catastrophe. It was devastation. It was unlike anything I have ever seen first hand or experienced. So, I hesitate to even really blog about our adventure… b/c for us… that’s what it was, an adventure. An escape from the normal day to day living for a few days. A “Staycation” if you will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Mascot Change</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proposed-mascot-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/proposed-mascot-change/</guid>
      <description>Tonight the kids and I were enjoying a walk at the Naval Academy when we spotted a statue of their mascot, the goat, which prompted a rather comical discussion.
We talked about how the goats are the navy mascot, to which my 3 yr old responded, “But mom, goats aren’t scary.” I then said that the Army is afraid of them b/c when they play each other in sports (not war) then they are against each other and don’t want to lose to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesdays in Annapolis</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wednesdays-in-annapolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/wednesdays-in-annapolis/</guid>
      <description>It’s funny how a simple thing like dinner on a Wednesday night can have an dramatic impact on your life. 7 years ago we went out to dinner with another couple in downtown Annapolis on a Wednesday night. If you know anything about summer in Annapolis then you know that Wednesday nights mean sailing races. (Truth is I grew up around here and just learned that fact 7 years ago).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
