<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homemaker on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/homemaker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homemaker on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 10:20:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/homemaker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I love Craigs List</title>
      <link>/posts/why-i-love-craigs-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/why-i-love-craigs-list/</guid>
      <description>I have friends that are super awesome yard salers. They get up at the butt crack of dawn on Saturday morning and drive all over the county finding great deals. They truly impress me and sometimes I think I want to be them, b/c I too like getting good deals.
But, I don’t like getting up at the butt crack of dawn any day of the week, much less Saturday. And I especially don’t like dragging 4 kids around with me all over the county at the butt crack of dawn, worse yet having the kids see stuff that other people are clearing out of their house and begging me if they can then bring it in mine and then me coming home without the outdoor patio table and chairs I’d been wanting but with a bag full of happy meal toys that are now going to clutter up our family room floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Hodgepodge of Circus Updates</title>
      <link>/posts/a-hodgepodge-of-circus-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-hodgepodge-of-circus-updates/</guid>
      <description>What day is it? We’ve been a bit out of sorts here at the circus… snow days and a power outage resulting in a fun sleepover at Nana and Pop’s… …now it is Friday, but sure feels like Monday…. we’re home and trying to play catch up on schoolwork, house work and laundry… good news is, when we are done… we’ll still have the weekend to enjoy! And next week is Super Bowl week… and in case you missed it… Pittsburgh’s Going to the Superbowl!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking on Sunshine</title>
      <link>/posts/walking-on-sunshine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/walking-on-sunshine/</guid>
      <description>Those of you that follow me on facebook or twitter, or have spent any time round these circus parts, know that I whine quite a bit about laundry. Recently, however, I made a startling discovery. Rather than being the bane of my existence as I once thought, it is in fact, the key to my happiness?
Say wha??
Last May, I set out with a quest to get entirely caught up on my laundry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Student Once Again</title>
      <link>/posts/a-student-once-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2010 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-student-once-again/</guid>
      <description>I do not consider myself to be either creative or crafty. And most of the time I am ok with that. Even though my mom and grandma are both talented seamstresses, I’ve often joked that I missed out on the sewing gene.
The truth is that sewing seems to require patience and an aspiration for perfection. And for me, close enough is usually more than good enough. But close enough doesn’t seem to work when sewing, b/c you kinda want your dresses to be straight and your sleeves even.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Table</title>
      <link>/posts/our-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/our-table/</guid>
      <description>The kids had scattered to the backyard to play while I cleared off the dinner dishes. As I wiped down the dining room table, I couldn’t help but smirk as I looked out over a see of crumbs and wood that is faded in parts due to many a knocked over glass of milk or water. There is an ever present layer of grime that those of you with kids know exactly what I am talking about… something like syrup meets peanut butter meets oatmeal and it just cakes into those nooks and crannies around the edge of the table, giving it that “lived in” feel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tag! Your it!</title>
      <link>/posts/tag-your-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tag-your-it/</guid>
      <description>Divide and Conquer
That would be the name of the game lately at the circus.
I’ll take the youngest two to the grocery store while Scott takes the older ones with him to build the new to us play set. Or Scott takes the big 3 to the year end baseball ceremony while I stay home with the babe.
At this stage of the game, tag teaming has seemed crucial for surviving and for attempting to keep the household running somewhat smoothly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Date Which Will Live in Circus Infamy</title>
      <link>/posts/a-date-which-will-live-in-circus-infamy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-date-which-will-live-in-circus-infamy/</guid>
      <description>** May 3, 2010 **
Write it down folks. Circle it on your calendar. I’ve dreamed of this day for months. I’ve gotten so close only to be thwarted.
But, folks… it finally happened.
The circus family is caught up on laundry.
I know, I never thought it would happen either. Friday afternoon I washed my Christmas table cloth. This evening, I dry cleaned our sweaters with one of those handy Woolite Dry Cleaning sheets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Month, New Week, New Goals</title>
      <link>/posts/new-month-new-week-new-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/new-month-new-week-new-goals/</guid>
      <description>February is here. I am happy to say I’ve finally put away all our Christmas decor and while it isn’t completely conquered, I have tamed the laundry beast and gotten somewhat of a grip on the house chores and school work. For now
So, with this new month, I’ve set some goals for some things I’d like to get done around the house. And thanks to two different blogging friends, I have some accountability and inspiration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Me Humble</title>
      <link>/posts/keeping-me-humble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2009 16:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/keeping-me-humble/</guid>
      <description>I was feeling pretty good about myself this week. Got a little boost of energy with week 12 and began to tame this household which I had slacked off on over the first trimester. Finally, I can leave the guest bedroom door open as well as the master bed room. I even cleaned out the van which had reached its height of total messiness, threw away all that trash crammed in around the car seats and brought in the plethora of coats and shoes which were strewn all over the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will the Real Crystal please stand up?</title>
      <link>/posts/will-the-real-crystal-please-stand-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/will-the-real-crystal-please-stand-up/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve been following my tweets or facebook statuses over the past few weeks, then you know I have been crazy cleaning girl here lately. In addition to my late night bathroom scrubbing and Friday night painting parties, today I did something I’ve never done before.
I got a friend to watch my kids so I could do house work.
I’ve had a friend watch the kids so I could go to the OB, or to a school interview, even for some volunteering at the preschool, but for house work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tackling the Entry Way</title>
      <link>/posts/tackling-the-entry-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tackling-the-entry-way/</guid>
      <description>Recently I decided the entry way to our home needed a face lift. For the past 6 years I’ve had a narrow card table covered with a table cloth and some seasonal decor on the top. Sounds classy huh?
Well last month I decided my table had to go. This left me with a bare white wall. 
Nothing says “home sweet home” like a big empty wall of blah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am Not Sure What Has Come Over Me</title>
      <link>/posts/i-am-not-sure-what-has-come-over-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/i-am-not-sure-what-has-come-over-me/</guid>
      <description>Something strange must be in the air here at the circus,b/c this week I’ve been cleaning like I haven’t cleaned since I was nesting. Seriously, last night at 9:00 Scott came home from sailing to find me scrubbing the baseboards of our bathroom with a toothbrush. If he hadn’t heard the kids screaming for him from their bedroom, I am sure he’d have thought he went into the wrong house!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Hard (or hardly working)</title>
      <link>/posts/working-hard-or-hardly-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/working-hard-or-hardly-working/</guid>
      <description>My son is quite the little entrepreneur. The other night after dinner my husband was reading the girls a book and I sat on the couch to read a little myself. I looked over to see what my son was up to and discovered he had put all the dishes in the sink, and was scrubbing the dining room table. He even asked where the sandwich bags where so he could bag up the leftovers and put them in the fridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Jam Circus Style</title>
      <link>/posts/making-jam-circus-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/making-jam-circus-style/</guid>
      <description>If you’re anything like me, you don’t really need one more reason to enjoy carbs. Yet, I can’t help but share my favorite. One of my mom’s most highly requested recipes growing up was for her strawberry jam. She always got a kick out it when people asked her if she would please share it.
So, here’s the family secret.
Yup, buy yourself a box of Sure Jell, add 4 cups of crushed berries, and 4 cups of sugar, and you are set!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circus Menu</title>
      <link>/posts/circus-menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/circus-menu/</guid>
      <description>Between baseball practice, swim lessons, sailing races, and deacon meetings, our evenings can get quite busy. And one thing my family is passionate about is their food. Not so keen on skipping diner. So, to keep dinner on the table, I have found it is helpful to have a plan. I must confess I used to be much better about the plan. I’d write up my meal plan for the month and then make my grocery list based on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Believe in Magic?</title>
      <link>/posts/do-you-believe-in-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/do-you-believe-in-magic/</guid>
      <description>I seriously wonder what moms did before the internet. Where did you go when you were looking for that cookie recipe you can’t find in your recipe box, or to check for tips on how to bring your child’s fever down, or to seek help tips for crayon removal?
A few weeks ago when I discovered this
 after my daughter’s naptime, I left a face book status that I was wondering how to get marker off of a baby doll face and within the hour I had 15 helpful tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowed Out!</title>
      <link>/posts/snowed-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2009 10:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/snowed-out/</guid>
      <description>Well, we got our snow. About 7 inches of it in fact. Waited till the night of March 1st to arrive, but hey at least we finally got our real snow fall, right? Scott said perhaps my “snowman” day was the necessary prerequisite for the snowfall. But, with all this beautiful, white, fluffy stuff, we also got…
a power outage
Nice, huh? At around 1:30 am I was giving my daughter a nebulizer treatment for her asthma when the power started flickering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 5 Minutes in the Spotlight</title>
      <link>/posts/my-5-minutes-in-the-spotlight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-5-minutes-in-the-spotlight/</guid>
      <description>Check it out…I am the featured tackle this week at 5 Minutes for Mom!!! Go ahead and click here and read about what I tackled this week at the circus! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Daybook</title>
      <link>/posts/my-daybook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-daybook/</guid>
      <description>My Daybook: Monday January 12 **Outside my window&amp;hellip;**the sun is shining brightly and Christmas lights still hang on the front of the house (though no longer on the roof…we’re half way there) **I am thinking&amp;hellip;**I really need to stop putting off folding the laundry piled beside my bed I am thankful for&amp;hellip; the Steelers victory last night advancing them to the AFC Championship **From the learning room…**working on Catechism questions From the kitchen&amp;hellip; Scott will be making pancakes for him and the kids for dinner tonight **I am wearing&amp;hellip;**jeans and my Steelers Superbowl XL Champions Tee I am creating&amp;hellip; I am not that creative, I do hope to tackle hemming my sons pants this week, does that count?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Come Let Us Adore Him</title>
      <link>/posts/o-come-let-us-adore-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/o-come-let-us-adore-him/</guid>
      <description>I don’t remember what magazine or book I read it from, but a few years ago I found an idea for having a wise man celebration. For some reason I recall it being on January 6th. And I decided it was a good idea. But that year my entire family got struck with the stomach virus, so we skipped it. But last year and this year we celebrated, thus making it a tradition at our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One&#39;s for You Mom...</title>
      <link>/posts/this-ones-for-you-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/this-ones-for-you-mom/</guid>
      <description>When I was little if you wanted to make my mom mad, all you had to do was ask her who was visiting when she was cleaning house. Oh how I remember the look she&amp;rsquo;d get on her face when I would say that&amp;hellip;.seems my turn has come&amp;hellip;

After decorating our cookies yesterday, I realized it was time to deep clean my kitchen. Once I scrubbed down the icing covered counter, it only made me realize how scummy the other counters looked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas at the Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/christmas-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 19:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/christmas-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll just go ahead and admit that I am a big bloggy dork, because since Megan first mentioned her Sharing Christmas carnival, I have been eagerly looking forward to it. Yes, I even wrote it in on my calendar. The idea is to share your home at Christmas.. kinda like an Open House&amp;hellip; only you get to go in your PJ&amp;rsquo;s and you don&amp;rsquo;t have to struggle to find small talk (yea, can&amp;rsquo;t tell I am an introvert, can you)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Christmas Tree</title>
      <link>/posts/o-christmas-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2008 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/o-christmas-tree/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite Christmas traditions is cutting down our tree. I absolutely love having a real tree. The rush of choosing just the right one to bring home is such fun. I also really like that no tree looks exactly alike or perfect. We&amp;rsquo;ve had a few that we&amp;rsquo;ve brought home and thought&amp;hellip;.&amp;ldquo;Ooo, didn&amp;rsquo;t realize it was crooked at the farm.&amp;rdquo; The imperfections always add to the charm though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall&#39;s Last Big Hurrah!</title>
      <link>/posts/falls-last-big-hurrah/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/falls-last-big-hurrah/</guid>
      <description>This weekend our family tackled the leaves in our yard. And really when I say our family, I mean, my husband. The rest of us came out to hold rakes, snap pictures, and jump in huge piles. Daddy was the one still raking in the cold all by himself when everyone else when inside to warm up and take naps. Yea, I know my husband rocks.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of what it looked like before he got to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Fun Night at the Grocery Store</title>
      <link>/posts/family-fun-night-at-the-grocery-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/family-fun-night-at-the-grocery-store/</guid>
      <description>The Safeway near us closed down for the past year so they could tear it down and build a bigger, more modern grocery store. I must say I am pretty excited about this because now I don&amp;rsquo;t have to drive as far to get my groceries.
Perhaps, I got a little too excited.
When I got the flier in the mail about their &amp;ldquo;grand opening preview party&amp;rdquo; on Thursday night, I started making plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Beginning to Look A Lot Like...Christmas?</title>
      <link>/posts/its-beginning-to-look-a-lot-like...christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/its-beginning-to-look-a-lot-like...christmas/</guid>
      <description>Ya know I love holidays&amp;hellip;we go all out with food, clothing, decor and not just for Christmas. I&amp;rsquo;m sporting the leprechaun hat for St Patty&amp;rsquo;s day, serving up enchiladas and corona on Cinco De Mayo, and partying it up on
International Talk Like a Pirate Day.
I was quite proud of myself this week when I finished buying my kids their Halloween costumes. I mean it isn&amp;rsquo;t even October yet, and we&amp;rsquo;ve got the Spiderman, Princess, and Lady Bug bought and hanging in the closet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind Closed Doors</title>
      <link>/posts/behind-closed-doors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 06:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/behind-closed-doors/</guid>
      <description>Those of you that have read my blog in the past, know I am all about keeping it real&amp;hellip;so, this week I&amp;rsquo;m taking you behind those closed doors and showing you what I don&amp;rsquo;t typically share with anyone.
Our Master Bedroom
The bedroom is supposed to be a place of calm and relaxation&amp;hellip;where you can rest&amp;hellip;a place of rest and rejuvenation. I read somewhere that you should decorate it with things that are sentimental and special to the two of you, a place that is yours as a couple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Little Motivation Can Do</title>
      <link>/posts/what-a-little-motivation-can-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/what-a-little-motivation-can-do/</guid>
      <description>After posting the very real life pictures of the inside of my van last week, I wanted to show you all how very different it looks now. :-) Wanna know the secret for my successful transformation? Friday was my son&amp;rsquo;s first day of preschool and at his school the teachers and administrators come to your vehicle to get your kid out in the morning and drop him off at pick up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep it Real- Check out My Wheels</title>
      <link>/posts/keep-it-real-check-out-my-wheels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/keep-it-real-check-out-my-wheels/</guid>
      <description>Jessica has a fun carnival where she helps keep us bloggers real. The deal is you gotta take pictures of the assignment as is, no tweaking for the cameras. This week she wanted to see &amp;ldquo;how we roll&amp;rdquo; as in what our vehicle looks like.
The funny thing about this is that when I saw the assignment I thought to myself, &amp;ldquo;how lucky for me I just cleaned the van out last week when we got back from camping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Bag of Tricks</title>
      <link>/posts/my-bag-of-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-bag-of-tricks/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I was given a voucher for a free gallon of milk from a certain grocery store. Today I finally made it back to the store but when I went to pull the voucher from my purse, I had a bit of trouble finding it. When I got home I decided it was time to clean out my purse.
I really could put Mary Poppins to the test for who has more in her lovely bag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bottom of the List</title>
      <link>/posts/bottom-of-the-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bottom-of-the-list/</guid>
      <description>Anyone want to guess what this picture shows&amp;hellip;.

That is the roof of our &amp;quot;white&amp;quot; Ford Escape. I guess you could say its been awhile since car washing made it to the top of the to-do list. You know it&amp;rsquo;s time to go it again when your kid hears the term &amp;lsquo;car wash&amp;rsquo; and responds with a giggle, &amp;quot;You can&amp;rsquo;t wash cars! That&amp;rsquo;s silly!&amp;quot; Ummm&amp;hellip;.yea&amp;hellip;the last time we washed our car this is what my son looked like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping It Real</title>
      <link>/posts/keeping-it-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/keeping-it-real/</guid>
      <description>Our pastor has been talking a lot lately about being transparent. As a Christian I too often present the world with a false squeaky clean image that gives the appearance that I think am perfect. Of course, everyone knows that no one is perfect so, when they see me ACTING perfect they know it is a false charade. What kind of credibility does that bring? No, I am far from perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A No Thank You Bite</title>
      <link>/posts/a-no-thank-you-bite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-no-thank-you-bite/</guid>
      <description>[] (https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/06/w4mewed1.jpg)
&amp;quot;Ew, gross!&amp;quot; &amp;quot;I don&amp;rsquo;t like it!&amp;quot; How many of you have had this response after working hard to prepare a new dish for you family? It can be quite frustrating especially if you know they&amp;rsquo;ll like it b/c they like every single one of the ingredients in it or worse yet, they devoured it the last time you made it and now won&amp;rsquo;t even try it.
My husband and I have always insisted the our kids at least try a bite of whatever it is we&amp;rsquo;re eating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mom vs The Fridge</title>
      <link>/posts/mom-vs-the-fridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mom-vs-the-fridge/</guid>
      <description>When asked what it was like to get the power back on Friday, I replied &amp;quot; A lot of work.&amp;quot;
After throwing away the spoiled food inside of my fridge and freezer, this is what I faced.

After an hour of scrubbing&amp;hellip;

Here are a few tips I learned from the cleaning process.
 If your power goes out and everything in your fridge spoils, clean out the freezer BEFORE the power comes back on and all the melted stuff in your freezer refreezes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Life without Power</title>
      <link>/posts/the-circus-life-without-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-circus-life-without-power/</guid>
      <description>As my husband mentioned here, we lost power this week. The first thing I did when the power came back on?
Brush my teeth?
No
Shower?
No
Go to the bathroom?
No
I posted this on the internet so &amp;ldquo;the world&amp;rdquo; could know we are back. Aren&amp;rsquo;t you glad to know I&amp;rsquo;ve got my priorities right?
It&amp;rsquo;s been a fun few days around here. Really, it could have been so much worse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WE&#39;RE BAAAAAAAAACK!!!!!!!!!!!</title>
      <link>/posts/were-baaaaaaaaack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/were-baaaaaaaaack/</guid>
      <description>After 44 hours with no electricity and thus no running water, phone, or internet, I am happy to report, that we are back in action! WAHOO!!!! I have lots to post on our adventures over the past few days, but right now I have toilets to flush and hands to wash&amp;hellip; but I am working on getting the kids down for their nap and then you better believe I&amp;rsquo;ll be online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will you be my friend?</title>
      <link>/posts/will-you-be-my-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/will-you-be-my-friend/</guid>
      <description>Are you familiar with facebook? I sure have gotten a chuckle out of it. I went to a girls night out last month and listened to my friends ask, &amp;ldquo;Are you my friend?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;How can I get more friends?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Why aren&amp;rsquo;t you my friend?&amp;rdquo; I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but laugh as it sounded so much like middle school.
But, I finally broke down yesterday and got a Facebook account. I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten those e-mails saying, &amp;ldquo;Your friend Jane has a facebook account, sign up too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day in the Life...</title>
      <link>/posts/a-day-in-the-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-day-in-the-life/</guid>
      <description>Ever had one of those days where you take one step forward only to take two steps back? That&amp;rsquo;s what my days felt like this week&amp;hellip; the good news is that my older two have been playing very well together, so well that I haven&amp;rsquo;t felt the need to go to playgroup or find a play date to get us all out of the house. They&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed playing their various pretend games in one section of the house, while I was able to work on something productive in a different part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What&#39;s For Dinner May 12-18th</title>
      <link>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner-may-12-18th/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner-may-12-18th/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Monday again and time to post this weeks meal plan. Be sure to click on the link above if you want to see what other people are serving their families this week. I have discovered many fun new recipes from participating in this carnival.
 Monday: Tonight is my last MOPS meeting of the year. Since I arrive early for set up, I skip dinner and eat at the meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s what&#39;s for dinner...May 5th-11th</title>
      <link>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner...may-5th-11th/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner...may-5th-11th/</guid>
      <description>I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share my 4 year olds favorite lunch sandwich with you all this week. Those of you feeling a bit adventurous might want to give it a try. You put peanut butter on one slice of bread, grape jelly on the other (nothing new here) and in the middle you place a slice of cheese and a few slices of ham. He invented it, he LOVES it and has eaten it every day for lunch for the past few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I try to give the very best...</title>
      <link>/posts/i-try-to-give-the-very-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/i-try-to-give-the-very-best/</guid>
      <description>If any of you are like me you love buying cards. Actually, if your anything like me you have three kids and you used to love buying cards. I remember the good old days when a friend and I would go to Hallmark and spend too much time reading, laughing, picking out cards. It was relaxing. I enjoyed finding those perfect cards to give to people. I enjoyed it so much that I would eagerly try to come up with people whose birthdays or special days were approaching somewhere in the next month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s what&#39;s for dinner.... April 28-May 4th</title>
      <link>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner....-april-28-may-4th/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner....-april-28-may-4th/</guid>
      <description>I think all of the nice spring weather has thrown a wrench on my meal plans&amp;hellip; last week we ate hot dogs three times in 5 days&amp;hellip; the weather was so stinking gorgeous that we had to grill and all I had in the freezer was hot dogs, so the kids were VERY happy. When my 2 year old sees hot dogs in the fridge she says, &amp;ldquo;hot dogs daddy make&amp;rdquo; (Truth is Daddy makes anything that is on the grill, but hot dogs is the meat of choice for the kids) Anyway, here&amp;rsquo;s to more than just hot dogs!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accidentally on Purpose</title>
      <link>/posts/accidentally-on-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/accidentally-on-purpose/</guid>
      <description>I started a policy at our house a few months ago which said, &amp;ldquo;Dessert only on Weekends.&amp;rdquo; My son is a great policeman on this and will ask throughout the week, &amp;ldquo;Is it the weekend yet?&amp;rdquo; If I serve dessert during the week, he often calls me out on it, but always happily partakes. I must confess the last few weeks I have really gone lax on this policy&amp;hellip; it was his birthday, or we had company over, or ummm we had leftovers&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behold the Power of Oxiclean</title>
      <link>/posts/behold-the-power-of-oxiclean/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/behold-the-power-of-oxiclean/</guid>
      <description>I have been singing the praises of oxiclean for some time now. It has gotten poop, tomato sauce, mud, and spit up out of my clothes for years. This Easter I REALLY put it to the test. We were dying eggs with the kids. My two year old had just plopped her egg into the red dye when she tipped the mug to peer into it and check out her handiwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menu Plan Monday- April 21st-April 27th</title>
      <link>/posts/menu-plan-monday-april-21st-april-27th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 04:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/menu-plan-monday-april-21st-april-27th/</guid>
      <description>I have really enjoyed having people stop by to check out my recipes. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll stick around awhile and learn more about the circus life here. It has also been a ton of fun for me to find new recipes to throw into the mix by visiting the other postings on Menu Plan Monday.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s cooking at my place this week!!
Monday: Another MOPS meeting for me which means Daddy and the kiddos are having pancakes again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurray for the Pack-n-Play!!</title>
      <link>/posts/hurray-for-the-pack-n-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hurray-for-the-pack-n-play/</guid>
      <description>If you read my blog post from Sunday you know that getting my laundry washed, dryed, folded, and put away is a big challenge for me. Today I found a way to help speed along that process. Even though my kids have an entire toy room which they can play in, they begged me to let them play in the pack-n-play while I folded laundry. Yes, that is correct, I actually said to my two and four year old, &amp;ldquo;If you fight or hit each other in there, you will have to come OUT of the pack-n-play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UGH!!</title>
      <link>/posts/ugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ugh/</guid>
      <description>Last night I got a chocolate craving. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like doing a ton of work to feed this craving so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d bake some No Bake Cookies. Growing up this was often the cure for a chocolate craving with minimal effort. When I opened my cabinet to get out the sugar I noticed a sticky brown residue on the container.
&amp;quot;Uh-oh&amp;quot; I thought.
Upon further investigation I found molasses covering the entire shelf, the box of aluminum foil, the pancake box, the corn muffin box and still no molasses jar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bane of My Existence</title>
      <link>/posts/the-bane-of-my-existence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-bane-of-my-existence/</guid>
      <description>bane
(bn) n. **** A source of persistent annoyance or exasperation
When talking about laundry to my husband, I typically describe it as the &amp;ldquo;bane of my existence.&amp;rdquo; No matter how hard I try to get it washed, folded, and put away, I typically fall short of accomplishing all 3 of those steps. Most often I get it washed, dried, and dumped on to our guest bed (which my husband now affectionately calls his dresser).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The End of the World as We Know it</title>
      <link>/posts/the-end-of-the-world-as-we-know-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-end-of-the-world-as-we-know-it/</guid>
      <description>If my geographic area is hit with a EMP, nuclear bomb, or a Katrina like natural disaster, I hope that it does not come at the end of the month. If we are left to fend for ourselves at the end of the month than my family&amp;rsquo;s future would be bleak, as you can see by this photo taken this morning of my refrigerator. How long can a sack of potatoes, 2 dozen eggs, a jar of spaghetti sauce and some American cheese really last you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll that Beautiful Bean Footage!</title>
      <link>/posts/roll-that-beautiful-bean-footage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/roll-that-beautiful-bean-footage/</guid>
      <description>My kids love kidney beans. When I was introducing solids to my first born I was very cautious. I was so afraid he would choke on things that I took it painfully slow. And he really wasn&amp;rsquo;t interested in meat for awhile. (the joys of chicken nuggets and hot dogs as staples in our diet, didn&amp;rsquo;t come until his was older) My pediatrician suggested I give him kidney beans. She said they were a great source of protein and they were soft and chewy so I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to freak out about him choking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
