<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>baby birds on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/baby-birds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in baby birds on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 10:33:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/baby-birds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Not Exactly the Life Lesson I was Hoping For</title>
      <link>/posts/not-exactly-the-life-lesson-i-was-hoping-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/not-exactly-the-life-lesson-i-was-hoping-for/</guid>
      <description>When I told you of the never ending science lessons going on at the circus this summer, I was excited about my children getting to watch the baby birds grow until they were old enough to fly from the nest. We learned that Daddy Robins help Mommy’s feed their babies, as we saw both the Mom and Dad at the nest at the same time. By day 3 we even started seeing their little beaks peak out over the top of the nest in our “Robin cam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer School</title>
      <link>/posts/summer-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/summer-school/</guid>
      <description>Just because it is summer, doesn’t mean we have to stop learning here at the circus. God presented us with a wonderful science lesson, right in our back yard. The best part is, I don’t even have to do any prep work for the lessonsA very brave and trusting Momma Robin built a nest under our deck. Apparently, she doesn’t require peace and tranquility to feel safe as our crew stomps back and forth across our deck belting out songs or squeals or tantrums from morning till night.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
