<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sleep on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/sleep/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sleep on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 17:31:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/sleep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Late Night Cleaning Spree</title>
      <link>/posts/late-night-cleaning-spree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/late-night-cleaning-spree/</guid>
      <description>The other night I came up to kiss the girls goodnight and found them voluntarily cleaning their room. And folks,I don’t mean stuffing toys under their beds and clothes down the laundry shoot. I found them in the closet sorting and they asked me for a laundry basket and a trashcan. It was already past their bed time, but they were clearly in the cleaning mode. And I know when it comes to things like Deep Cleaning you gotta embrace the mood when it hits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Someone’s Been Sleeping in my Bed</title>
      <link>/posts/someones-been-sleeping-in-my-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/someones-been-sleeping-in-my-bed/</guid>
      <description>When we walked through the house with the kids, after we knew we had won the contract, they eagerly checked out their bed rooms to call dibs on which would be the boys room and which would be the girls room. The boys chose one of the 2 “kids rooms” and the girls petitioned for the master bed room. After all they pointed out, “it has a bathroom right off of it and we go to the bathroom in the middle of the night, not you guys” and “it has the laundry shoot in their too so we’d be sure to put away all our dirty clothes” and it had plenty of room for their bunk bed and dressers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>While They Were Sleeping</title>
      <link>/posts/while-they-were-sleeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/while-they-were-sleeping/</guid>
      <description>It’s always fun to peek in on my kiddos when they are sleeping. Sometimes because it gives me a good chuckle, sometimes because it tugs at my heart strings, and sometimes just because it sets my mind at ease to see them sleeping snuggly in their rooms. Last night as I was crawling into bed, I realized I hadn’t peeked in on them. I don’t know if I’m the only Mom out there like this, but when I realize I forgot, I just can’t shake it off… I have to go b/c sometimes this little quirky fear will rise up “What if the one night I didn’t check on them something was wrong?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even Super Man Sleeps</title>
      <link>/posts/even-super-man-sleeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/even-super-man-sleeps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Needs a Bed?</title>
      <link>/posts/who-needs-a-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/who-needs-a-bed/</guid>
      <description>I’ve written before about the crazy places and positions I’ve found my kids sleeping in. It appears child number 4 is no exception to the random sleeping locations of the circus crew.
Last night, when I went upstairs for bed, I found him asleep in his door way like this.

Today at nap time, I again went up the stairs to find him out of his room. 
It appears he’s taken a preference for sleeping in the hallway/landing area of our home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Cold Turkey</title>
      <link>/posts/going-cold-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/going-cold-turkey/</guid>
      <description>For the past four and half years, this has been her “go to” position for comfort. 
As a baby it was great… she totally self soothed… no pacifiers to chase down or beloved blankey to snuggle. Just pop her index and middle fingers in her mouth backwards and start rubbing her ear (or twirling her hair) and she could instantly calm herself to sleep. We knew of course this would have it’s trade off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brothers…</title>
      <link>/posts/brothers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/brothers/</guid>
      <description>It’s been really neat to watch the bond between my oldest and youngest. Our baby was the answer to his older brothers prayers, as he longed to have a little brother. I’ll never forget the look of pure joy when he found out he finally had a baby brother. I know he can’t wait for the day when they can truly play together, but for now it is so neat to see the love between them blossom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hug and Roll</title>
      <link>/posts/hug-and-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hug-and-roll/</guid>
      <description>My youngest often wakes up early in the morning… you know that tricky hour of the day when it isn’t yet time for anyone to be awake but yet close enough to morning that if you let him cry it out a bit they’ll probably wake up and it’s way earlier than you want more than one child up seeing as it’s earlier than you even want to be up. You know that time of the night/morning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sisters Sleeping Side by Side</title>
      <link>/posts/sisters-sleeping-side-by-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sisters-sleeping-side-by-side/</guid>
      <description>More times than not, when I peek in on my girls before heading to bed, I find them sleeping together. Sometimes this means they are both down on the bottom bunk.

Sometimes, it means they are side by side in their drawers (truthfully I find them like this almost as often as I find them in the bottom bunk). 

Sometimes they are both on the floor. (haven’t found them like that in the last 2 weeks)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flashbacks</title>
      <link>/posts/flashbacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/flashbacks/</guid>
      <description>Every now and then, when I peek in on my oldest daughter before going to sleep, I’ll see something which instantly takes me back to her infancy. 
And even though she’ll be 6 in a few short weeks, I see her as this sweet little 8 month old in her crib, sleeping folded in half. I’ll remember how she used to sleep like this every.single night… and suddenly all these pictures of her sleeping like this pass through my mind like a slide show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He Spoils Us</title>
      <link>/posts/he-spoils-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/he-spoils-us/</guid>
      <description>Time and time again our fourth child has blown us away with his easy going, flexible, happy-go-lucky approach to life. It has made the transition to a family of 6, for this family on-the-go, SO MUCH easier—a fact I am truly, truly grateful for.
This weekend, he really went above and beyond our expectations though.
Not only did he fall asleep in the tent both nights, while the rest of us were out at the camp fire, but he even napped in the tent Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Such a Time As This?</title>
      <link>/posts/for-such-a-time-as-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/for-such-a-time-as-this/</guid>
      <description>There are all kinds of people in the world. Some morning people, some night owls. I truly think your propensity towards one or the other is an inborn part of your personality. True, you can work on becoming more of a morning person (and society pretty much dictates this to some degree), ones natural inclination, I think, is innate.
For a glimpse of this, one must simply observe my two daughters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Visions of Super Bowl Victories Dance in Their Heads. . .</title>
      <link>/posts/and-visions-of-super-bowl-victories-dance-in-their-heads.-.-./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/and-visions-of-super-bowl-victories-dance-in-their-heads.-.-./</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Babies Don’t Keep</title>
      <link>/posts/babies-dont-keep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/babies-dont-keep/</guid>
      <description>My lil guy isn’t a newborn anymore. I’ve known it for awhile.. he’s eating solids, vocalizing, and working on crawling. But, recently, I also realized his days of simply sleeping in my arms are fleeting. He’s working himself into a rhythm… sleeping through the night… taking 2 solid naps a day…The days of just holding my tiny, sleeping newborn in my arms are over. So on those random Sunday afternoons when he falls asleep in my arms, I am going to stay put and savor the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>While You Were Sleeping</title>
      <link>/posts/while-you-were-sleeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/while-you-were-sleeping/</guid>
      <description>I found my 3 yr old like this during nap time today… it seems baby doll has been displaced from her bed. 
It reminded me of a picture I snapped a few weeks ago of both on my girls as we found them when we peeked in on them before going to bed.

YES… they are both sleeping INSIDE of their drawers!
And since I am sharing sleeping pics, why not share a few of my lil man snoozing as well?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Morning Math</title>
      <link>/posts/early-morning-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 09:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/early-morning-math/</guid>
      <description>Math has never been my strong suit (except in 3rd grade, I did awesome with the multiplication tables and was the class champ at around the world, but that was b/c all I had to do was memorize facts and not understand the process)
Anyway, as I was saying… math has never been my gifting… and math at 3 am is certainly not my gifting. So, I calculated the hours again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slumber Parties</title>
      <link>/posts/slumber-parties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/slumber-parties/</guid>
      <description>I think I’ve mentioned before that my oldest three all share a room. This week the kids have started taking turns sleeping with the baby. Sunday night the boys got to sleep together. My oldest was so excited about sharing a room with his little brother. I couldn’t help but snap a picture as I peeked in on them before going to bed. 
When I went to look in on the girls I found them both cuddled up together on the floor… it appears they decided to have a sleep over of their ownThe next night my oldest daughter wanted to sleep with the baby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where’s Waldo?</title>
      <link>/posts/wheres-waldo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wheres-waldo/</guid>
      <description>My daughter sleeps with so many animals, pillows, dolls, and blankets in her bed, that sometimes when I go in to kiss her before I go to bed, I can’t find her. One night I thought I saw her and then realized I almost kissed her cabbage patch doll. Can you find her in the pile? It reminds me of the old Where’s Waldo books.
Here’s a closer look… there she is!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Girls Will Sleep Anywhere</title>
      <link>/posts/my-girls-will-sleep-anywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-girls-will-sleep-anywhere/</guid>
      <description>I went in to wake my daughter from nap time today and found her like this. 
I’m not sure if she fell asleep while playing or if she was just doing all she could to keep herself from falling asleep. Either way, looks rather uncomfortable to me.
Then there’s her sister.
We looked down during a soccer game a few weeks ago and found her like this.
Yes, that would be my youngest asleep ON the soccer field, during a game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Much Has Changed</title>
      <link>/posts/not-much-has-changed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/not-much-has-changed/</guid>
      <description>Here’s my daughter sleeping in her crib at 8 months old.
 And here she is at 14 mths old. Still enjoys sleeping “folded in half”, as we refer to it.
 
Earlier this week when my husband went in to kiss the kids goodnight, he found her at 3 and 1/2 sleeping in the very same position she favored as an infant.  I would think with age this position would grow more impossible and uncomfortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Girl That Knows What She Wants</title>
      <link>/posts/a-girl-that-knows-what-she-wants/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-girl-that-knows-what-she-wants/</guid>
      <description>Apparently my daughter’s week long rebellion was against sleeping alone in her crib and not on sleeping in general. Tuesday was a break through day for us!
She napped and slept through the night without screaming for hours first.
As I said goodnight to her in her sister’s bed, she had the BIGGEST grin on her face. Seriously, I have never seen a kid so excited about sleeping in a bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agree to Disagree</title>
      <link>/posts/agree-to-disagree/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/agree-to-disagree/</guid>
      <description>Scott and I see eye to eye on most things. When it comes to parenting though, we have one major disagreement&amp;hellip;
pajamas
I think they are cute and cuddly and so adorable.
Scott thinks they are impractical and a complete waste of time. &amp;quot;Why do we need to change them just to sleep,&amp;quot; He asks.
I have a hard time coming up with a real compelling reason.
&amp;quot;Because they look so cute in them,&amp;quot; is typically my reply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks Mr Turtle</title>
      <link>/posts/thanks-mr-turtle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/thanks-mr-turtle/</guid>
      <description>When my oldest daughter was born my son wanted to get her this musical turtle he saw at Target for her crib. Every time we went to Target he would push the buttons to make it play music and he would ask if he could get it for his sister. We didn&amp;rsquo;t think it was necessary.
He was still insistent about it when our third child was born so we decided to let him get it for his sister for Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sneaking a Little Shut Eye</title>
      <link>/posts/sneaking-a-little-shut-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sneaking-a-little-shut-eye/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for visiting! Since you&amp;rsquo;re here, stay awhile&amp;hellip; Might I suggest this post or this one?To view other peoples, check out 5 Minutes for Mom or visit Wordless Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busted!</title>
      <link>/posts/busted/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/busted/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday when we were out running errands my son told me,
&amp;ldquo;Mom, I am going to be really good at nap time today.&amp;rdquo;
I was in the midst of trying to find the things on my mental list and push the cart with three kids on it, so I muttered something like, &amp;ldquo;good honey&amp;rdquo; and continued on. My son was so excited because after nap time we were going to plant flowers in our yard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Than Time and a Half</title>
      <link>/posts/better-than-time-and-a-half/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/better-than-time-and-a-half/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m only one week into my blogging adventure and I already had to skip a day. Yesterday was one of THOSE days. Those of you with kids, know what I mean. It started Friday night when all 3 of my kids woke at various points throughout the night coughing, moaning and generally not feeling well (thankfully, no puking occurred). The &amp;ldquo;night&amp;rdquo; ended for good at 6:20 when I was up giving my son water, then my daughter a nebulizer treatment for her asthma and as soon as I finished, I heard the baby crying for me to nurse her!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
