<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pregnancy on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/pregnancy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pregnancy on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 18:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/pregnancy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Meeting the Circus Family</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/meeting-the-circus-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/meeting-the-circus-family/</guid>
      <description>Our son was born at 10:27pm. Unfortunately, because he was born so late, his brother and sisters didn’t get to meet him until the next morning. We loved the first night with him but it felt like the birthing process was somehow incomplete until we were all together. When the moment finally came Scott brought them up and they eagerly ran to the bed to meet him. 
When I told them his name, my son’s face light up as it registered that he got the baby brother he was longing for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s a Boy!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a-boy/</guid>
      <description>This week we welcomed a new member to our family. 
Our sweet baby boy was born this week…
weighing in at 8 lbs 14 oz and measuring 20” long. 
It was love at first sight for all of us. We really can’t get enough of him, so it seems.  I can’t wait to fill you in on the labor story and share the pictures from his fist visit with his big brother and sisters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to Get Recalibrated</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/time-to-get-recalibrated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/time-to-get-recalibrated/</guid>
      <description>Check out the size of these diapers!! Have you seen anything so little? It’s been a long time since we’ve had diapers that small around here… I think I forgot how tiny they were. 
Seriously, my hand is bigger than the diaper!!

Granted my swollen hands are bigger than a lot of things these days so maybe that wasn’t the best bench mark, but still….what a tiny little bottom we’re going to be wiping soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to Place Your Bet</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/time-to-place-your-bet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/time-to-place-your-bet/</guid>
      <description>I had a dream last night that I accidentally opened the envelope and found out we were having a girl.
If your wondering how one can accidentally open the envelope, it’s actually not to hard to do b/c yesterday I was cleaning out some papers to be filed and saw a sealed blank envelope and thought, “What is that?” Thankfully, before opening it, I saw the name of the sonogram office in the corner and realized what it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimme a Break</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gimme-a-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/gimme-a-break/</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to make oral reading more fun, I gave my son the option of picking any location in our house to do his reading time.  He chose my closet.
Would not have been my first choice, but no worries, to the closet we went… I brought a pillow for me to sit on as the floor isn’t so comfy for this 9 mth pregnant momma. My son looked at me and said, “Hey, how come you aren’t sharing that pillow with me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Tag</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shadow-tag/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/shadow-tag/</guid>
      <description>Visit here  or here  for more picture fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Things People Will Say to a Big Belly</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-things-people-will-say-to-a-big-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-things-people-will-say-to-a-big-belly/</guid>
      <description>In the past week I’ve had some humorous discussions about my ever growing belly. I had forgotten the funny things kids will do and say to a women with a big belly. I was teaching 3 rd grade when I was pregnant with my son and my students were a never ending source of comical observations on my pregnant belly.
But, my own children are quite used to pregnancy. They get it more than most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Letter to My Baby</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-letter-to-my-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-letter-to-my-baby/</guid>
      <description>Dear Sweet Baby of Mine,
Every time I sit down or lay down I can feel you move around inside of me. You are more active than any of your sisters or brother were in the womb. Perhaps you are trying to tell us already that you are eager to jump in and join in the chaos and fun that is our family. The feeling of you turning over or kicking and punching my sides…it’s almost as if you are saying, “Hey Mom!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 weeks to go!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/11-weeks-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/11-weeks-to-go/</guid>
      <description>More Wednesday pics can be found here or here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Circus Crew Visits the OB</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-crew-visits-the-ob/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-circus-crew-visits-the-ob/</guid>
      <description>I typically schedule my OB appointments for first thing in the morning so that the kids can stay home with Scott. This time however, his work schedule didn’t cooperate, so I brought the circus crew with me for my check up. I knew at 28 weeks they wouldn’t be doing an exam, so I felt comfortable having them tag along. I did come prepared with coloring books, crayons, snacks, and even lollipops which I saved for the very end if they were “super stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Envelope</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-envelope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-envelope/</guid>
      <description>There is an envelope sitting unopened on our kitchen counter. It’s been sitting there sealed tight since January 6th. The contents of this envelope bear great repercussions for our entire family. Many people question why we even have the envelope. We could have known what was inside of it 8 weeks ago.
But we like to be surprised. (of find some strange joy in self-torture)
So, we turned our heads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Thing I’ve Got Thick Skin!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/good-thing-ive-got-thick-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/good-thing-ive-got-thick-skin/</guid>
      <description>Last night I was holding my girls on my lap when they began to play a little rough. I reminded them that there was a baby in my belly and they needed to be gentle. My 4 yr old then said, “Mom, I don’t think you really have a baby in your belly. I think it is just food.”
I assured her there really is a baby in there and reminded her that she’s seen the baby’s picture and heard the heart beat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s a…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/its-a/</guid>
      <description>BABY!!!!!

This morning we had our sonogram appointment. While it is our fourth pregnancy, I try as hard as I can to not take anything for granted. I don’t think I realized how much I was “holding my breath” so to speak before the appointment. Words can’t adequately express the feelings of thanksgiving that overwhelmed me when the tech and then the doctor told us that everything looked healthy and normal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Baby Bump Part 1 of ?</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-baby-bump-part-1-of-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-baby-bump-part-1-of-/</guid>
      <description>That’s right folks… a little tiny baby bump is making his or her appearance into the world. I alluded to the fact earlier when I mentioned I was now in maternity clothes. And I figured, why not share this bump with the rest of you? Because for some unexplainable reason we seem to enjoy looking at others increasing waistbands and what other time in my life would I willingly post a picture of my belly for the world to see?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinary Miracle</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ordinary-miracle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/ordinary-miracle/</guid>
      <description>During this stage of the game, sometimes it’s easy to forget there’s a person growing inside me. Yes, my jeans are fitting more snugly these days and I tend to nod off on the couch each night around 10, but other than that I don’t feel all the different. And so I go through each day making meals, cleaning up messes, and trying to accomplish lessons, errands, and other excursions and quite often forget that all the while there’s a life growing inside of me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
