<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home school on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/home-school/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home school on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 10:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/home-school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Week at School…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-week-at-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/this-week-at-school/</guid>
      <description>I feel like we are off to a pretty good start this school year and we are settling into a routine.
The hardest part for me about home schooling and the part I like the LEAST is the juggling act of wearing both the hat of mom and the hat of teacher. The kids don’t understand that my making them do a subject they don’t like doesn’t make me a mean mom, it makes me their teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to the Building!!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/back-to-the-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 06:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/back-to-the-building/</guid>
      <description>And so a new year begins… this morning was our first day back at the tutorial. I can’t believe it marks our 6th year of homeschooling. What a blessing this community had been to our family. Here we are starting 2nd, 3rd, and 5th grades!

“And this is my prayer: that your love may abound more and more in knowledge and depth of insight, so that you may be able to discern what is best and may be pure and blameless for the day of Christ, filled with the fruit of righteousness that comes through Jesus Christ—to the glory and praise of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nesting</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/nesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/nesting/</guid>
      <description>I feel like the month of August is much like the 9th month of pregnancy. I go into crazy nesting mode as I gear up for another school year. There is the ordering of curriculum… then the purchasing of school supplies… then the organizing of the binders… and cracking open that homeschool cabinet which ALWAYS turns into the junk closet over the summer. Ya know, the “Company is coming and I need a place to hide all these papers and misc junk from the kitchen counters,” place….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching My Breath</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/catching-my-breath/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/catching-my-breath/</guid>
      <description>Gah! It seems MORE than a month has gone by since I last updated the ol’ blog. What a time it was too. The whirlwind of the end of the school year. Last week we had our last day at the tutorial followed by their year end assembly. Wahoo!!! All those snow days we kept our nose to the grind stone are paying off now baby! I was so proud as I watched them get up front and recite all of the things they had memorized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Field Trip</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/family-field-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/family-field-trip/</guid>
      <description>This year in History we are studying American History from the explorers to the war on 1812. I love history. It is my favorite part of home schooling. And I am so grateful that we live within driving distance of so many great historical sites. I really wanted to take the kids to Philadelphia for a day trip over spring break. Scott graciously rearranged his work schedule so that he could join us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“We are Scientists”</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-are-scientists/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/we-are-scientists/</guid>
      <description>This week I took my girls on a field trip with their classmates from our tutorial. We visited a Science Center run by the local school system. The kids learned how to observe the world around them and record those observations. They studied bugs and wild life found in our area as well as learned about camouflage and even played a game to reinforce the concept.
They got to use almost all of their senses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Field Trip Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/family-field-trip-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/family-field-trip-fun/</guid>
      <description>When we switched out history curriculum this year so that the whole family studies the same period of history (with varying level of work catered to their age level), one of the reasons I was MOST excited was that our field trips would be applicable to all. When our tutorial gave off for Presidents Day, I was eager to take advantage of the day free of book work to go on a field trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When You Give a Mom a Minute...</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-you-give-a-mom-a-minute/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/when-you-give-a-mom-a-minute/</guid>
      <description>My own paraphrase of a very busy 30 minute period of time here at the circus on our first day back at school at home, based on the &amp;ldquo;If you give a&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo; book series. There is no embellishment here. This is how it really went down at the circus house this morning.
If you give a mom a minute, she&amp;rsquo;ll sneak a peak at facebook.
And when she sneaks a peak at facebook, she&amp;rsquo;ll see one of her friends posted a crock pot recipe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures of our Life</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pictures-of-our-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/pictures-of-our-life/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t had time to really update the blog lately. In fact, I have found my days to be quite full now that we are in full swing with our school and extra curricular activities. Bursting at the seams full. But, I have whipped the camera out a few times, so I decided today to download them and at least try to preserve some memories of everyday life around here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to School!!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/back-to-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/back-to-school/</guid>
      <description>Because our homeschool tutorial meets on a Mon-Thurs schedule and the board doesn’t like to start the year on a partial week, we are THE LAST PEOPLE IN THE WORLD (or so it feels like) to start back to school. But, today we finally had our turn for the morning poses on the front step. 
Another school year is upon us. We had an EPIC summer. One for the record books… and I while I didn’t tackle every project on my summer to do list, we are starting the year off a little more organized than last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another School Year Complete</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/another-school-year-complete/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/another-school-year-complete/</guid>
      <description>That’s right, today is our last day of school at the building. 
As we prepare to leap into summer… let’s take a quick peek back at day 1.

Look how much they’ve grown just physically this year! I can’t believe it’s our last day of Kindergarten, 1st grade, an 3rd grade.

They got to dress down for the last day of school. (Can you tell it’s been a chilly spring?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is Here!!</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-is-here/</guid>
      <description>When I walked outside today and felt warmth, my heart was instantly happy. It’s a balmy 75 degrees today and I.LOVE.IT!! This is my ideal temp. I love being able to walk around in flip flops and head out the door without thought of a jacket. I love not being at all chilly. So of course when I picked the kids up from tutorial today, I brought my trusty ball cap because I knew we’d be staying after for football, and flower picking, chatting with friends, and the latest development in after school play time….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Clean Once Again Proves Himself to be a Worthy tool in the Arsenal of Motherhood</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mr.-clean-once-again-proves-himself-to-be-a-worthy-tool-in-the-arsenalof-motherhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mr.-clean-once-again-proves-himself-to-be-a-worthy-tool-in-the-arsenalof-motherhood/</guid>
      <description>I don’t really know what it is that possesses a child to just randomly on a whim pick up that crayon and suddenly decide to make the world (or in this case the bathroom) his canvas. We have crayons out every single day in our house. I do my best when I see a stray one on the floor to nab it lest it suddenly look inviting to my toddler. But, truly they are laying on the school table, in reach, every single day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Little Trick that Has Been HUGE for us in School This Year</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-new-little-trick-that-has-been-huge-for-us-in-school-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 09:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-new-little-trick-that-has-been-huge-for-us-in-school-this-year/</guid>
      <description>We are three weeks in to our new school year. I think I FINALLY have all the kids correct curriculum (missed a few things I when I ordered it this summer) and their books organized in a way that works for them, me, and their tutors at the tutorial. I’ve done things a little differently this year, and SO FAR, it has helped our days to run more smoothly. First of all, I’ve committed to waking up before the kids every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Answer to Everyone’s Question</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-answer-to-everyones-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-answer-to-everyones-question/</guid>
      <description>Lately, I’ve been asked several times what I do with my 2 year old while I am teaching the older 3. Here’s your answer. 
Yes, that would be pen mark up and down the corner of the walls in my dining room. Yes, he did that yesterday morning while I was working with the big kids in the other room and thought that scraping sound was the sound of him scraping oatmeal of his cereal bowl with a spoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Beginning</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-new-beginning/</guid>
      <description>Scott commented the other day that he feels the passage of time more noticeably at the beginning of the school year, rather than on the kids birthdays. I think he’s right.

Especially this year, when I packed up three backpacks and three lunch boxes and lined up 3 kids for pictures at the front door. We have our Kindergartener, on her very first day of school ever. 
Followed by our first grader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Reading</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-reading/</guid>
      <description>I love to read. I love when you get to that point in the novel, where you literally can not put it down and find yourself speed reading/skipping words just to quickly make it to the next part and find out what happens. One of our goals in educating our children was to make readers out of them. This was hard at first with our son as reading didn’t come naturally to him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/reflecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/reflecting/</guid>
      <description>I don’t homeschool because I hate the government. Nor do I homeschool because I think the public school system is all evil. Nor do I homeschool because I want my kids to be smarter than yours. In fact, raising super smart kids isn’t even my main goal of education.
I homeschool because I want to spend the time with my kids. That’s it, in a nut shell.
But, if I may be honest and come clean with you, it’s hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mummies and Butterflies…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mummies-and-butterflies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/mummies-and-butterflies/</guid>
      <description>Our tutorial had its Science/History night on Monday. As with any special event, it’s taken a few days to come up for air following all the pre event preparations…. As I watched tired mother’s dragging ginormous projects into the gym on Monday morning, I realized this is one of the major reasons we’re at our tutorial. Science/History night gives them an opportunity to get up in front of a group of people and perform something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day with Fish and Friends</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-day-with-fish-and-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-day-with-fish-and-friends/</guid>
      <description>We had a super fun time at the aquarium today for our tutorial fieldtrip. And although we’ve taken the kids two other times over the past 7 years, I think they had way more fun getting to go with their friends…which proves Piglet was right, “It&amp;rsquo;s so much more friendly with two.” (or 40)

Having gone twice before, I kinda wasn’t expecting to enjoy it as much as I had before… yet, I found myself amazed yet again at the incredible creatures our God has created…and I saw things I have never seen before…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Book Smarts</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/beyond-book-smarts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/beyond-book-smarts/</guid>
      <description>Education is about so much more than book smarts. I’ve known this for awhile and believed it to my core. In fact, this fact alone has dictated so many decisions we make in raising our children, especially since we home school and want to make sure that they are learning more than just “reading, writing, and arithmetic.”
Yesterday and today our school time was “interrupted” so that I could spend time one on one disciplining a child for behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life With 2</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-with-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/life-with-2/</guid>
      <description>Now that my oldest 2 are at their tutorial two days a week, I find myself with just 2 children at home on those mornings. It is a truly odd feeling and a dynamic I am not yet used to. Though I am sure it is nothing compared to the strangeness I’ll feel next year when I am left with only my lil man two days a week. I am hoping to use this time to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another New School Year</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/another-new-school-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/another-new-school-year/</guid>
      <description>While we’ve been “doing school” at home for the past few weeks for the purpose of reviewing and getting used to the routine, today was the first official start of our new school year.
We homeschool, but also use a tutorial. The kids attend the tutorial twice a week and study at home with me three days a week. So far, I feel it provides the balance our family needs between homeschooling and traditional schooling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing up Fast</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/growing-up-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/growing-up-fast/</guid>
      <description>There were moments, many moments, this year when I doubted. I wondered if I was giving him what he needed, if he was on par with where the public school was. I wondered what I was thinking, was it worth the battles, and the mess around my house. Days when I shoved school work aside as I put dinner on the table before quickly rushing out the door for practice. Truthfully, the hardest thing for me is the mess… is letting the mess go so we can concentrate on school work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Call it Crazy…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-call-it-crazy/</guid>
      <description>This spring I have 3 kids in sports. On 3 different teams. This in addition to the girls both taking gymnastics twice a week and Cub Scouts.
We are busy, busy, busy with games and practices most every night… some nights we’re even double booked.
Many people look at my schedule and call me crazy. Why do you do this to yourself?
The answer is, honestly, two fold. 1. We love it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Busy…</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-busy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/keeping-busy/</guid>
      <description>People often ask me what the girls do while I am doing homeschooling with my oldest child.

On Tuesday the answer was “take all the cushions off the couch and every single blanket and pillow they owned and build a fort”


 If I am distracted enough they even smoke a stogie or two in their fort. (just kidding those would be pretzel rods…I promise, but doesn’t this bottom picture look sketchy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Chicken Pot Pie Sent Me Into a Sad Little State of Panic and Despair</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-chicken-pot-pie-sent-me-into-a-sad-little-state-of-panic-and-despair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/how-chicken-pot-pie-sent-me-into-a-sad-little-state-of-panic-and-despair/</guid>
      <description>I asked Scott to explain Pi to the kids yesterday as we ate our Chicken Pot Pie in celebration of Pi day (3/14). I knew he would do a better job than I, as I would have probably just showed them the symbol and told them it equaled 3.14
Because folks, that pretty much sums up what I know about Pi.
He however drew them a picture of a circle, taught them about diameter and then went on to tell them that you need a little (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Giant Leap Forward</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-giant-leap-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 18:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-giant-leap-forward/</guid>
      <description>Reading has not come without its share of battles and tears for my son. Last year, he truly HATED to read and it was such a struggle for us. I at times found myself wondering if I was really meeting his needs by homeschooling. Part of me kept telling myself, “He is a boy. He’ll get it, it just takes time. Don’t worry.” But another part said, “Am I doing a good enough job?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Exactly the Life Lesson I was Hoping For</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-exactly-the-life-lesson-i-was-hoping-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/not-exactly-the-life-lesson-i-was-hoping-for/</guid>
      <description>When I told you of the never ending science lessons going on at the circus this summer, I was excited about my children getting to watch the baby birds grow until they were old enough to fly from the nest. We learned that Daddy Robins help Mommy’s feed their babies, as we saw both the Mom and Dad at the nest at the same time. By day 3 we even started seeing their little beaks peak out over the top of the nest in our “Robin cam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer School</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/summer-school/</guid>
      <description>Just because it is summer, doesn’t mean we have to stop learning here at the circus. God presented us with a wonderful science lesson, right in our back yard. The best part is, I don’t even have to do any prep work for the lessonsA very brave and trusting Momma Robin built a nest under our deck. Apparently, she doesn’t require peace and tranquility to feel safe as our crew stomps back and forth across our deck belting out songs or squeals or tantrums from morning till night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teacher’s Helper</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/teachers-helper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/teachers-helper/</guid>
      <description>My daughter really is a very patient teacher’s assistant. She will sit quietly without ever saying a word and listen to her big brother as he sounds out the words to read the Bible story each night. It is quite precious.
And the other day I discovered that having her quiz him on flashcards is the perfect way to let her be involved in school. She happily sits and holds the cards up for him and will praise him when he gets the answers correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3rd Quarter Evaluation</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/3rd-quarter-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/3rd-quarter-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>Last year when we decided to home school our son, we said that we would take it a year at a time, and evaluate our situation each year as we planned for the next. Well, the time has come for us to make plans for next fall and we have decided to continue home schooling using our tutorial for first grade. (or grammar I as the classical folks like to call it)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bird Watching</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bird-watching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 05:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/bird-watching/</guid>
      <description>When I came out to the kitchen to make breakfast this morning, I felt a cold draft. I then noticed my son sitting in the sliding glass door. 
He told me he was listening to the birds in the backyard. They were offering up a beautiful melody. One thing I love about life with small children is that they help you to stop and take notice of the everyday miracles in the world around you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field Trip Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/field-trip-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/field-trip-fun/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite parts about home schooling has been the field trips. We have tutorial sessions on Mon and Wed. Tues we have school at home and typically it is a catch up day for me around the house. I try to keep Tuesdays open as I need that day to just be at home. Thursdays we have school at home, plus BSF in the morning, and often a play date over lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection on Home Schooling</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/reflection-on-home-schooling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2009 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/reflection-on-home-schooling/</guid>
      <description>Well, I am about one month into my homeschooling experience and thought I’d reflect on it.
I love it!
You know I waffled and prayed and struggled with the decision. It wasn’t like I knew from the minute I brought him home from the hospital that I’d be a home schooling mom. As I prepped our “classroom” I was still clinging to the fact that at any moment I could change my mind and enroll him at the local public school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Watched Pot</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-watched-pot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2009 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-watched-pot/</guid>
      <description>Its funny to me how many “old sayings” run through my head on any given day.
For example, “Don’t cry over spilled milk.” I must repeat that to myself at least twice a week&amp;hellip; “Don’t cry over spilled milk… DON’T CRY over spilled milk… (and in my head I also add quite often, don’t make anyone else cry over spilled milk.”
So, I had to laugh when my son and I were doing science this afternoon and we were talking about the various states of water.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
