<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dates on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/dates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dates on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 06:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/dates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Anniversary Date in DC</title>
      <link>/posts/anniversary-date-in-dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 06:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/anniversary-date-in-dc/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we snuck away for to celebrate our anniversary. We spent the night in the nations capital. And we had a blast. No agenda. No plan. Just hanging out in DC just the two of us. Confession: I love the monuments in DC. Living in MD, I have seen them a lot. Growing up summer visits from cousins ALWAYS meant trips into DC. And I know they are very touristy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DATE DAY</title>
      <link>/posts/date-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/date-day/</guid>
      <description>While we didn’t plan it like this at first, Sunday ended up being date day for each of our 4 kids. Each child ended up with some one on one time with either mom, dad, or Aunt Karen. Good times had by all!
One of the duties of our church deacons is to unlock the church on Sunday mornings. When Scott became a deacon 3 years ago, he started taking one child with him on his deacon duty mornings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Daddy/Daughter Date…</title>
      <link>/posts/a-daddydaughter-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-daddydaughter-date/</guid>
      <description>Scott took a vacation day on Thursday so he could spend the day with our oldest daughter. First they went with the other kids in her Kindergarten class to see a performance of The Night Before Christmas. Apparently the sets were gorgeous and the play was very well done. Such a treat to go to a live theatre AND to get to see it with her school friends and Dad. I think it was also a treat for Dad to get to see her with her school friends, it’s an aspect of her life that he doesn’t get to see very often.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
