<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guest Post on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/guest-post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guest Post on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 20:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/guest-post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dwell Well</title>
      <link>/posts/dwell-well/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dwell-well/</guid>
      <description>My last guest blogger for this week is Monica. I stumbled across Monica’s blog shortly after I started blogging last year and was instantly hooked. She and her husband Keith have been married a little longer than Scott and I and we both have three kids around the same ages. Her love for the Lord, her husband, and her children shines through in each of her posts. We’ve had the chance to chat back and forth via e-mail and I am certain if she lived in town instead of across the Atlantic, we would certainly enjoy spending time together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time for a Short Stop</title>
      <link>/posts/time-for-a-short-stop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 20:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/time-for-a-short-stop/</guid>
      <description>Today’s guest blogger is Sarah. Sarah is one of the few bloggers I read, whom I know in real life. My freshman year of college at Towson, Sarah lived on the floor above me. I was in Bible study with her through RUF and we hung out numerous times throughout the year. When my family moved and I transferred schools, we lost touch. We found each other on face book this past summer and I’ve been hooked on her blog ever since!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say Hello to Happy</title>
      <link>/posts/say-hello-to-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/say-hello-to-happy/</guid>
      <description>Today, I bring to you Rebecca from A Happy Heart. Rebecca has been a faithful commenter here at the circus for several months. Her encouraging and humorous comments have flowed into numerous e-mail exchanges between the two of us. Without actually meeting her in person, she has crossed the line from “virtual friend” to “real friend” and I look forward to meeting her face to face next month. She has two adorable preschoolers, two helpful tween stepdaughters, and another little bun in the oven due to arrive in time for Thanksgiving this fall.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
