<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meals on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>/tags/meals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meals on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 18:48:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/meals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Meatless Wednesdays… and Fish</title>
      <link>/posts/meatless-wednesdays-and-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/meatless-wednesdays-and-fish/</guid>
      <description>At the end of last year Scott and I went out for a big fun day date. As we thought back over the year and looked ahead at the new year we talked about things we wanted to do differently in the coming year. Scott had a few suggestions on the food front. One was that we eat more meatless dinners. He was not advocating we go vegetarian…(good thing too b/c this meat and potato loving gal would have surely lasted all of 2 days at best) the other was that we starting eating more fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Cooking at the Circus</title>
      <link>/posts/whats-cooking-at-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/whats-cooking-at-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>I have found that by planning my meals for the month, I can drastically reduce our families grocery spending. It takes time and a whole lot of effort though. And to be honest the past several months I wasn’t so good about it. But, then Scott and I sat down and took a look at our spending. And we realized that we needed to be a whole lot better about sticking to our budget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gana’s French Toast</title>
      <link>/posts/ganas-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ganas-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>I love my husband’s Nana. She’s a remarkable lady. I loved her for years, just based on hearing about her from her grandson and reading her sweet letters. Then, I flew to California and met her. And I loved her as my own Nana!! When I walked in her side door, I instantly felt at home. I sat down at her table and never wanted to leave again.
Gana (as my kids call her b/c she is their Great Nana) is famous for her quince jam, her tacos, and her French toast (among many other things).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Branded</title>
      <link>/posts/branded/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/branded/</guid>
      <description>My family’s love for Chick-Fil-A goes deep and wide. [
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/07/IMG_0105.jpg)
The first symbol my son recognized was for Chick-Fil-A. He could “read” it at age 2. And anytime he saw a cursive C he thought it stood for Chick-Fil-A. At that same age, I showed him a symbol for the golden arches and he had no idea what it was. My daughter’s one year scrapbooks both have pages dedicated to their “first Chick-Fil-A” kids meal experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Long?</title>
      <link>/posts/how-long/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 03:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-long/</guid>
      <description>Dinner time….the family all gathered around the table, enjoying a delicious meal, talking about the day, laughing and enjoying one another…statistics say that families that consistently eat dinner together tend to raise healthier, more well behaved children, then families that don’t. So, what are we doing wrong?
More often than not the Circus Family eats breakfast and dinner together as a family. More often than not our dinner “hour” is more like a dinner hour and a half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What&#39;s For Dinner May 12-18th</title>
      <link>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner-may-12-18th/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner-may-12-18th/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Monday again and time to post this weeks meal plan. Be sure to click on the link above if you want to see what other people are serving their families this week. I have discovered many fun new recipes from participating in this carnival.
 Monday: Tonight is my last MOPS meeting of the year. Since I arrive early for set up, I skip dinner and eat at the meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s what&#39;s for dinner...May 5th-11th</title>
      <link>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner...may-5th-11th/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner...may-5th-11th/</guid>
      <description>I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share my 4 year olds favorite lunch sandwich with you all this week. Those of you feeling a bit adventurous might want to give it a try. You put peanut butter on one slice of bread, grape jelly on the other (nothing new here) and in the middle you place a slice of cheese and a few slices of ham. He invented it, he LOVES it and has eaten it every day for lunch for the past few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s what&#39;s for dinner.... April 28-May 4th</title>
      <link>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner....-april-28-may-4th/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/heres-whats-for-dinner....-april-28-may-4th/</guid>
      <description>I think all of the nice spring weather has thrown a wrench on my meal plans&amp;hellip; last week we ate hot dogs three times in 5 days&amp;hellip; the weather was so stinking gorgeous that we had to grill and all I had in the freezer was hot dogs, so the kids were VERY happy. When my 2 year old sees hot dogs in the fridge she says, &amp;ldquo;hot dogs daddy make&amp;rdquo; (Truth is Daddy makes anything that is on the grill, but hot dogs is the meat of choice for the kids) Anyway, here&amp;rsquo;s to more than just hot dogs!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menu Plan Monday- April 21st-April 27th</title>
      <link>/posts/menu-plan-monday-april-21st-april-27th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 04:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/menu-plan-monday-april-21st-april-27th/</guid>
      <description>I have really enjoyed having people stop by to check out my recipes. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll stick around awhile and learn more about the circus life here. It has also been a ton of fun for me to find new recipes to throw into the mix by visiting the other postings on Menu Plan Monday.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s cooking at my place this week!!
Monday: Another MOPS meeting for me which means Daddy and the kiddos are having pancakes again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menu Plan Monday- April 14th-20th</title>
      <link>/posts/menu-plan-monday-april-14th-20th/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/menu-plan-monday-april-14th-20th/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to all of you who stopped by and read my site and my meal plan last week. It was fun to have some new visitors on my site! Here is this week&amp;rsquo;s menu plan at our house.
    Monday : Pancakes and Scrambled Eggs Tonight is Mommy&amp;rsquo;s Night out as I have a MOPS meeting so Daddy will be cooking breakfast for dinner tonight for him and the kiddos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menu Plan Monday</title>
      <link>/posts/menu-plan-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/menu-plan-monday/</guid>
      <description>I have found that I save a ton of grocery money as well trips to the grocery store, by making a monthly meal plan. I write on my calendar my meals for the month. Then, I make my grocery lists based on that and theoretically, I have all I need for us to eat for the month (with the exception of produce and milk, which I have to return to the store multiple times for).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The End of the World as We Know it</title>
      <link>/posts/the-end-of-the-world-as-we-know-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-end-of-the-world-as-we-know-it/</guid>
      <description>If my geographic area is hit with a EMP, nuclear bomb, or a Katrina like natural disaster, I hope that it does not come at the end of the month. If we are left to fend for ourselves at the end of the month than my family&amp;rsquo;s future would be bleak, as you can see by this photo taken this morning of my refrigerator. How long can a sack of potatoes, 2 dozen eggs, a jar of spaghetti sauce and some American cheese really last you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roll that Beautiful Bean Footage!</title>
      <link>/posts/roll-that-beautiful-bean-footage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/roll-that-beautiful-bean-footage/</guid>
      <description>My kids love kidney beans. When I was introducing solids to my first born I was very cautious. I was so afraid he would choke on things that I took it painfully slow. And he really wasn&amp;rsquo;t interested in meat for awhile. (the joys of chicken nuggets and hot dogs as staples in our diet, didn&amp;rsquo;t come until his was older) My pediatrician suggested I give him kidney beans. She said they were a great source of protein and they were soft and chewy so I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to freak out about him choking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
