<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cousins on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/cousins/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cousins on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 14:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/cousins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with Grands and Cousins</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-with-grands-and-cousins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/christmas-with-grands-and-cousins/</guid>
      <description>I LOVE hosting Christmas. And I am so thankful that my extended family allows me that privilege. I am thankful that they all have been willing and able to come year after year so we could share the day together. I don’t take it for granted. I know my parents won’t always be able to travel. I know my BIL and SIL can get stationed so far away that it just doesn’t make a trip to MD possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun in Va</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fun-in-va/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/fun-in-va/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I escaped down to VA for just shy of 24 hours to spend some time with my SIL and her family. I adore Scott’s sister so a visit to her house was a bright spot in our week. We arrived in the early afternoon with time for me to take the 4 boys to the park while Aunt Karen took the girls to run a few errands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break = Cousin Fest</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-break-cousin-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/spring-break-cousin-fest/</guid>
      <description>Last week was spring break at the circus. It was an action packed week full of family fun. We played lots and lots of games, rode bikes, and the trampoline was pretty much in use non stop. We had Aunt Karen and the boys here from Sun night till Tuesday.  
Wednesday we went to Philly and Thursday night my parents and my nieces and nephew came to town till Easter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kicking off the Holidays with Family and SNOW</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kicking-off-the-holidays-with-family-and-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/kicking-off-the-holidays-with-family-and-snow/</guid>
      <description>Nothing like a back seat driver. Especially a 3 year old back seat driver.
At 1 am. On a Snow covered back country road.
[
](https://latc.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/IMG_1958.jpg)
As we slip slided around the roads approaching my parents the other night, I seriously thought we might end up in a ditch and all the while my 3 year old was WIDE awake and chattering non stop about all the snow. He kept saying, “Dad, don’t get in an accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fall Tradition</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-fall-tradition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 06:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-fall-tradition/</guid>
      <description>Almost every fall, I enjoy taking the kids to the county fair. We’ve been going since my oldest was under a year old. This year my youngest was so super excited. He talked about it for months. “When are we going to go to the fair and see the animals?” We went on Friday morning for the preschool preview day. Then my parents and I returned on Saturday for the girls to perform a gymnastics demo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sweet Celebration</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-sweet-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2013 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/a-sweet-celebration/</guid>
      <description>We celebrated my Dad’s 60th Birthday this week with a party at Hershey park. Dad, Mom, their kids, and their 8 grandkids. 
We had a blast riding the rides, but truly the best part was being together as a family and enjoying watching relationships grow. 

When you’re the oldest cousin sometimes you have to do time in the kiddy rides. He was quite the sport… and was rewarded with roller coaster time in the evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Fun</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cookie-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/cookie-fun/</guid>
      <description>The most favorite Christmas cookie for the circus fam to make is sugar cookies. Messiness + sugar = pure bliss for the circus crew!!


  This year we enjoyed rolling and cutting the cookies with our cousin Eli. 

 It was also the first year that the youngest circus crew member got to participate in the cooking making fun. And by participate, I of course mean, eating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Presents Can’t Be Wrapped</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-presents-cant-be-wrapped/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/some-presents-cant-be-wrapped/</guid>
      <description>A few moments from this weekend which I wish to savor…
1. My son presenting his gift to his extended family. (One nap time he came up excited to share that he had drawn a picture from each scene in Luke 2. On Christmas he gave one picture to each person. He then laid them all out on the floor and recited the story from memory.)


2. Prepping the Christmas Lasagnas with my daughter… it marked a milestone, in which she was truly helpful in the kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Like It</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/nothing-like-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/nothing-like-it/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we were able to coordinate our schedules and have the opportunity to get together with my brother and his family for some play time. 
What gathering would be complete without a light saber battle?

I loved getting to watch my nephew and nieces play and to observe my brother playing with my children. There is something quite special, and indescribable about watching your children play with your sibling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
