<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>faith on Life At The Circus</title>
    <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/faith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in faith on Life At The Circus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 06:29:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/tags/faith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>With Gratitude</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/with-gratitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 06:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/with-gratitude/</guid>
      <description>1o years ago Scott and I went before our church and made a commitment before God to raise our son as a disciple of our Lord Jesus Chris. Father’s day weekend, 2004, we rejoiced with our congregation as he was baptized. This was not a sign of our sons salvation. It was the sign of God’s promise to save and cleans sinners who call upon Him. Our son was not saved, but we rejoiced in the seal representing God’s power to save.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/reflecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/reflecting/</guid>
      <description>I don’t homeschool because I hate the government. Nor do I homeschool because I think the public school system is all evil. Nor do I homeschool because I want my kids to be smarter than yours. In fact, raising super smart kids isn’t even my main goal of education.
I homeschool because I want to spend the time with my kids. That’s it, in a nut shell.
But, if I may be honest and come clean with you, it’s hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desiring to be a Woman of Faith</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/desiring-to-be-a-woman-of-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/desiring-to-be-a-woman-of-faith/</guid>
      <description>Years ago my Mom and I attended a Women of Faith Conference…I believe our first was when I was in college. We drove to Cleveland, OH to attend the conference. We left refreshed and inspired and vowing to make it a tradition to attend some sort of spiritual conference together as often as we could. Since then, we’ve attend Women of Faith, Beth Moore, and a few women’s retreats together. I appreciate the opportunity to worship, and grow alongside my mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sparkle of a True Princess</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-sparkle-of-a-true-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/the-sparkle-of-a-true-princess/</guid>
      <description>“Momma, don’t we look beautiful?”
As I praised them for their lovely fashion choices and snapped picture upon picture of their dress up fun, it dawned on me that this was an opportunity to reinforce what true beauty is. Ya know, I said. To be truly beautiful, you have to be kind and loving to others. In fact, you can be wearing the prettiest dress ever, but if you act mean and unkind to others, you aren’t beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Step Closer</title>
      <link>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-step-closer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2010 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>LifeAtTheCircus.github.io/posts/one-step-closer/</guid>
      <description>Since before each of my children were born, my hearts deepest desire has been for them to know the Lord Jesus as their Savior. My son has demonstrated to us numerous times through various conversations that he recognizes he is a sinner and Christ died on the cross to forgive his sins.  My girls have not come to that point yet, but this Easter season we got one step closer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
